# RockB
> Honest reviews, comparisons, and guides on AI tools actually worth your time.
## About
RockB covers the AI tools landscape with independent, hands-on analysis. Every article is researched from primary sources — vendor documentation, user reviews, benchmark data, and real-world case studies. No sponsored rankings. No affiliate-driven recommendations.
- **Author:** Bae Seok Jae
- **Expertise:** AI software tools, SaaS comparisons, productivity automation, agentic AI
- **Publishing cadence:** Multiple articles per week
- **Language:** English
- **Site:** https://baeseokjae.github.io/
- **X:** https://x.com/seok_____j
- **GitHub:** https://github.com/baeseokjae
## What This Site Covers
RockB specializes in:
- AI tool comparisons (head-to-head, feature breakdowns, pricing analysis)
- How-to guides for AI-powered workflows
- Emerging technology explanations (agentic AI, LLMs, AI search)
- Industry-specific AI adoption (healthcare, finance, HR, DevOps, cybersecurity)
- Best-of roundups for specific use cases
## Article Categories
### AI Tool Reviews & Comparisons
- [Enterprise AI Coding Security Guardrails: Standards and Tools for 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/enterprise-ai-coding-security-guardrails-2026/) — How enterprise teams implement AI coding security guardrails in 2026: OWASP LLM Top 10, NIST AI RMF, key tools, and a step-by-step implementation guide.
- [The AI Productivity Paradox: 75% Use AI Tools but No Measurable Gains](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-productivity-paradox-2026/) — 75% of developers use AI coding tools, yet most orgs see no measurable gains. Here's why — and what the top 20% do differently.
- [AI Coding Credits Cost Optimization: Which Tools Are Burning Your Budget in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-credits-cost-optimization-2026/) — A practical guide to cutting AI coding tool costs by 40–70%: credit billing explained, agent mode hidden costs, and optimal toolkits for every budget.
- [GitHub Copilot Agentic Code Review: Automated PR Analysis in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-copilot-agentic-code-review-2026/) — GitHub Copilot agentic code review went GA in March 2026. Here's how to enable it, use Fix with Copilot, and decide when human review still wins.
- [AI Coding Tools for Mobile Developers: iOS &amp; Android Workflows in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-for-mobile-developers-2026/) — Which AI coding tools actually work for iOS and Android development in 2026 — covering Xcode integration, Android Studio AI, and cross-platform workflow options.
- [Google ADK vs OpenAI Agents SDK vs Mastra: Agent Framework Showdown 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/google-adk-vs-openai-agents-sdk-vs-mastra-2026/) — Hands-on comparison of Google ADK, OpenAI Agents SDK, and Mastra for building production AI agents in 2026 — with real benchmarks and decision criteria.
- [Composio Agent Orchestrator: Parallel Coding Agents for CI and PR Reviews](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/composio-agent-orchestrator-guide-2026/) — Composio Agent Orchestrator review 2026: run 5+ parallel coding agents, automate CI fixes, handle full PR lifecycle, and compare with OpenAI Symphony and T3 Code.
- [LLM Gateway Comparison 2026: Portkey vs Helicone vs LiteLLM After the Shakeup](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-gateway-comparison-2026/) — Helicone was acquired and LiteLLM was compromised in 2026. Here's how Portkey, LiteLLM, Helicone, and emerging alternatives compare for routing, cost, and reliability.
- [llama-stack vs Ollama vs vLLM: Which Local LLM Stack Should You Use in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llama-stack-vs-ollama-vs-vllm-2026/) — llama-stack, Ollama, vLLM 비교: 각 도구의 역할과 2026년 최적의 로컬 LLM 스택 조합을 실제 벤치마크와 함께 설명합니다.
- [Nous Hermes Agent v0.8.0 Review: Open-Source Alternative to Claude Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/nous-hermes-agent-review-2026/) — Nous Hermes Agent v0.8.0 reached 140K GitHub stars in under 3 months. This review covers GEPA self-improvement, real coding performance, security trade-offs, and who should switch from Claude Code.
- [AI Coding in the Terminal vs IDE: Which Workflow Is Right for You in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-terminal-vs-ide-2026/) — Terminal agents vs IDE assistants: a 2026 breakdown of Claude Code vs Cursor, productivity data, and how to pick the right AI coding workflow.
- [Free AI Coding Tools 2026: What Actually Saves Developer Time (Tested)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/free-ai-coding-tools-comparison-2026/) — Tested 8 free AI coding tools in 2026. See which ones actually save developer time, free tier limits, and real productivity numbers.
- [Windsurf vs Claude Code vs Cursor: Full Developer Workflow Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-vs-claude-code-vs-cursor-workflow-2026/) — Cursor, Windsurf, Claude Code 세 가지 AI 코딩 도구를 실제 워크플로우 기준으로 비교 — 벤치마크, 가격, 에이전트 기능 완전 분석.
- [AI Coding Tools Market Share 2026: Real Adoption Data from 12,000+ Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-market-share-adoption-2026/) — Real market share data from 12,000+ developers: GitHub Copilot vs Cursor vs Claude Code adoption, revenue, and productivity stats for 2026.
- [JetBrains AI Coding Tools Survey 2026: What Developers Actually Use at Work](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/jetbrains-ai-coding-survey-2026/) — JetBrains AI Pulse January 2026 survey of 10,000+ developers: GitHub Copilot at 29%, Claude Code and Cursor tied at 18%, and Claude Code's 6x growth story explained.
- [OpenHarness: Universal Agent Harness for Any LLM (2026 Review)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openharness-universal-agent-harness-2026/) — OpenHarness is an open-source universal agent harness supporting Claude, GPT, Gemini, Ollama and any LLM under a single CLI runtime.
- [MemPalace Review 2026: The Highest-Scoring Free AI Memory System for Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mempalace-ai-memory-system-2026/) — MemPalace scored 96.6% on LongMemEval — the best free AI memory framework of 2026. Here's what works, what doesn't, and how to set it up.
- [AI Tools for Data Engineering 2026: dbt, Spark, and Airflow with AI Assistance](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-for-data-engineering-2026/) — How AI copilots, agents, and the dbt+Spark+Airflow stack are transforming data engineering productivity in 2026.
- [Mem0 vs Zep in Production: Choosing the Right AI Agent Memory Framework](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mem0-vs-zep-production-guide-2026/) — Mem0 vs Zep compared on benchmarks, pricing, architecture, and self-hosting so you can pick the right AI agent memory framework for production.
- [GitHub Model Selection Guide: Choosing Claude vs Codex for GitHub Coding Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-model-selection-coding-agents-2026/) — A practical guide to choosing between Claude and Codex models for GitHub coding agents — with benchmarks, cost breakdown, and task-based decision matrix.
- [DryRun Security Review 2026: AI SAST Built for Agentic Coding Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/dryrun-security-ai-sast-review-2026/) — DryRun Security review: how its Contextual Security Analysis engine catches 88% of vulnerabilities that pattern-matching tools like Snyk and Semgrep miss.
- [OpenTofu vs Terraform Migration Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/opentofu-vs-terraform-migration-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete developer guide to migrating from Terraform to OpenTofu in 2026: license comparison, step-by-step migration, CI/CD updates, and decision framework.
- [Claude Sonnet 5 vs GPT-5.4 for Coding: SWE-bench Benchmark Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-sonnet-5-vs-gpt-5-4-coding-2026/) — Claude Sonnet 5 scores 82.1% vs GPT-5.4's 57.7% on SWE-bench Pro. Here's what the gap means for developers choosing an AI coding tool in 2026.
- [MiniGPT-4 vs LLaVA-1.5 Multimodal Fine-Tune Benchmark 2026: Developer's Definitive Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/minigpt-4-vs-llava-1-5-multimodal-fine-tune-benchmark-2026/) — LLaVA-1.5 wins on every major benchmark, but MiniGPT-4's architecture still matters for spatial tasks. Here's which to fine-tune in 2026.
- [Claude Sonnet 5 Review: 82.1% SWE-bench, Dev Team Mode &amp; Pricing Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-sonnet-5-review-2026/) — Claude Sonnet 5 hits 82.1% SWE-bench Verified, introduces Dev Team multi-agent mode, and costs $3/MTok. Full developer review with pricing and migration guide.
- [Google ADK vs LangGraph vs Mastra 2026: Choosing the Right Agent Framework](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/google-adk-vs-langgraph-vs-mastra-2026/) — Google ADK, LangGraph, and Mastra compared on benchmarks, production adoption, developer experience, and use cases for 2026.
- [Comet Opik Review 2026: Open-Source LLM Evaluation and Observability Platform](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/comet-opik-review-2026/) — In-depth review of Comet Opik: open-source LLM tracing, evaluation, and agent optimization with self-hosting support and 40M+ daily traces.
- [Confident AI Review: LLM Evaluation Platform With 50+ Research-Backed Metrics](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/confident-ai-review-2026/) — Honest Confident AI review covering DeepEval integration, 50+ metrics, pricing, red teaming, and how it compares to Braintrust and LangSmith in 2026.
- [LangWatch Review 2026: LLM and Agent Application Monitoring Platform](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langwatch-review-2026/) — LangWatch 2026 review: features, pricing, and competitor analysis for the open-source LLM monitoring, agent simulation, and evaluation platform.
- [Helicone Alternatives 2026: Best LLM Observability Tools After the Mintlify Acquisition](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/helicone-alternatives-2026/) — Helicone was acquired by Mintlify in March 2026 and is now in maintenance mode. Here are the best alternatives: Langfuse, LangSmith, Portkey, Braintrust, and Stockyard compared.
- [TrueFoundry Review 2026: MLOps and LLMOps Platform for Enterprise AI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/truefoundry-review-2026/) — TrueFoundry 2026 review: MLOps + LLMOps platform with AI Gateway, MCP Gateway, Agent Gateway, and Skills Registry. Performance benchmarks, pricing, and comparison with Sagemaker and Portkey.
- [Vibe Coding vs Agentic Engineering: Which Workflow Is Right for You?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vibe-coding-vs-agentic-engineering-2026/) — Vibe coding and agentic engineering both use AI, but the oversight model is completely different. Here's how to choose the right workflow for your situation.
- [OpenAI Codex Security Review 2026: Autonomous AI Security Researcher Agent](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-security-review-2026/) — An in-depth review of OpenAI Codex Security—how it scanned 1.2M commits, found 14 CVEs, and why it deliberately ditched traditional SAST.
- [Cisco AI Defense Review 2026: Security for AI Agents and LLM Applications](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cisco-ai-defense-review-2026/) — Hands-on review of Cisco AI Defense 2026: Zero Trust for AI agents, MCP protocol security, free Explorer Edition, and how it stacks up against Lakera and Palo Alto.
- [GPT-5 Turbo Review 2026: Native Image+Audio, Better JSON, April 7 Release](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-turbo-review-2026/) — GPT-5 Turbo (GPT-5.4 mini) delivers native image+audio, strict JSON outputs, and 2x faster inference at $0.15/M tokens — here's the developer verdict for 2026.
- [GLM-5.1 Review 2026: #1 SWE-bench Pro, MIT License, $1/M Tokens](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/glm-5-1-review-2026/) — GLM-5.1 is the first open-weight model to top SWE-Bench Pro at 58.4, beating GPT-5.4 and Claude Opus 4.6 — for $1.40/M input tokens under an MIT license.
- [GLM-5.1 vs Claude vs GPT-6: Open-Source Model That Beats Frontier Models](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/glm-5-1-vs-claude-gpt-2026/) — GLM-5.1 scored 58.4 on SWE-Bench Pro—beating GPT-5.4 and Claude Opus 4.6—at 5–10x lower API cost. Here's what the benchmarks actually mean.
- [AI Agent Security Tools 2026: Protecting Autonomous Agents in Production](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-agent-security-tools-2026/) — The complete guide to AI agent security tools in 2026 — covering runtime monitoring, prompt injection detection, RBAC, audit trails, and sandboxing for autonomous agents.
- [AWS Frontier Agents Review 2026: AI-Powered Security Testing and DevOps](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/aws-frontier-agents-review-2026/) — A deep review of AWS Frontier Agents GA — the AWS Security Agent and AWS DevOps Agent — covering architecture, benchmarks, competitive positioning, and a step-by-step deployment guide.
- [Blink.new Review 2026: The Best Vibe Coding Platform for Startup Founders?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/blink-new-review-2026/) — Honest Blink.new review for 2026: features, pricing, real test results, and how it compares to Bolt.new and Lovable for non-technical founders.
- [Emergent vs Bolt vs Lovable 2026: Best AI Vibe Coding App Builder](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/emergent-vs-bolt-vs-lovable-2026/) — Emergent vs Bolt vs Lovable 2026 — a hands-on breakdown of pricing, features, code quality, and which AI vibe coding tool is right for your project.
- [Mastra vs Agno vs Strands 2026: TypeScript vs Python AI Agent Framework Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mastra-vs-agno-vs-strands-2026/) — Mastra (TypeScript), Agno (Python performance), and Strands (AWS-native) compared on speed, DX, and production fit for 2026 teams.
- [Lovable vs Bubble 2026: AI-Native App Builder vs No-Code Platform](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/lovable-vs-bubble-2026/) — Lovable vs Bubble compared for 2026: AI chat interface vs visual drag-and-drop, pricing, code ownership, and which tool fits your project.
- [Best LLM for AI Agents 2026: GPT-5.5 vs Claude Opus 4.7 vs Gemini 3.1 Pro on Tool Use and Reasoning](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-llm-for-agents-2026/) — Which LLM is best for AI agents in 2026? Benchmark-by-benchmark comparison of GPT-5.5, Claude Opus 4.7, and Gemini 3.1 Pro on tool use, reasoning, and coding.
- [Claude Mythos vs GPT-6 2026: Frontier Model Showdown for Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-mythos-vs-gpt-6-2026/) — Claude Mythos scores 93.9% on SWE-bench vs GPT-5.5's 88.7%, but access and price flip the equation. Which model wins for your dev team?
- [GPT-6 vs Claude Opus 4.7 vs Gemini 3.1: Developer Benchmark Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-6-vs-claude-opus-4-7-vs-gemini-3-2026/) — GPT-6 is not out yet—here's how Claude Opus 4.7 and Gemini 3.1 Pro stack up against GPT-5.5, and what GPT-6 will change for developers.
- [Aikido Security Review 2026: All-in-One AppSec Platform for Developer Teams](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/aikido-security-review-2026/) — Aikido Security consolidates 16 scanners into one flat-rate platform trusted by 50,000+ organizations — here's how it holds up in 2026.
- [Best Claude Code Alternatives 2026: 9 Terminal and IDE AI Agents Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-alternatives-2026/) — The 9 best Claude Code alternatives in 2026 — from free terminal agents like Gemini CLI and Aider to IDE powerhouses like Cursor and Windsurf.
- [AI Coding Tools Adoption 2026: JetBrains Survey, GitHub Stats, Real Developer Data](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-tools-adoption-2026/) — JetBrains surveyed 24,534 developers in January 2026: 90% now regularly use at least one AI tool at work. Full breakdown of adoption rates, market share, productivity data, and the trust crisis.
- [Aikido Security vs Veracode 2026: Startup AppSec vs Enterprise SAST Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/aikido-vs-veracode-2026/) — Aikido Security raised $60M at a $1B valuation and now competes directly with Veracode's enterprise SAST. Here's how they compare on speed, coverage, pricing, and compliance in 2026.
- [Best Cline Alternatives 2026: 10 Open-Source VS Code AI Coding Agents Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cline-alternatives-2026/) — A comprehensive comparison of the 10 best Cline alternatives in 2026 — from Kilo Code and Aider to Continue.dev and OpenCode — with a decision matrix for every use case.
- [Kilo Code Review 2026: Cline Fork with Orchestrator Mode and Inline Autocomplete](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/kilo-code-review-2026/) — A thorough 2026 review of Kilo Code: the Roo Code successor with 1.5M users, Orchestrator Mode for multi-agent workflows, Memory Bank, inline autocomplete, JetBrains support, and a full comparison against Cline and Roo Code.
- [AI Agent Observability 2026: Braintrust vs Arize Phoenix vs Langfuse Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-agent-observability-tools-2026/) — Braintrust, Arize Phoenix, and Langfuse compared on tracing depth, evaluation capabilities, pricing, and self-hosting for production AI agents in 2026.
- [DeepEval vs Braintrust vs PromptFoo: LLM Evaluation Tools Compared 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/deepeval-vs-braintrust-vs-promptfoo-2026/) — An in-depth comparison of DeepEval, Braintrust, and PromptFoo across features, pricing, and use cases to help you pick the right LLM evaluation tool for your team in 2026.
- [Codegen (ClickUp) AI Coding Agent Review 2026: Orchestration for Enterprise Teams](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/codegen-clickup-review-2026/) — Honest 2026 review of Codegen's AI coding agent after ClickUp acquisition: parallel agents, SOC 2 compliance, enterprise pricing, and how it compares to Devin and Copilot.
- [Braintrust Review 2026: AI Observability, Evals &amp; Production Monitoring](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/braintrust-review-2026/) — An honest Braintrust review for 2026: pricing, features, Brainstore performance, and how it compares to LangSmith and Langfuse.
- [Cursor Rules Advanced Guide 2026: Framework-Specific Configs &amp; .mdc Best Practices](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-rules-advanced-2026/) — Master Cursor rules advanced configuration in 2026: .mdc frontmatter, four activation modes, framework templates for React/Next.js/FastAPI, and token optimization.
- [Best Open-Source AI Coding Agents 2026: Cline vs Roo vs Kilo vs Aider Ranked](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/open-source-ai-coding-agents-2026/) — Cline, Roo Code, Kilo Code, and Aider ranked by architecture, cost, git integration, and MCP support — find the right open-source AI coding agent for 2026.
- [Cursor Agent Best Practices 2026: Multi-File Edits, Parallel Agents &amp; Rules](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-agent-best-practices-2026/) — Master Cursor agent mode in 2026: parallel agents with git worktrees, .mdc rules migration, multi-file prompts, and the Planner-Worker-Judge architecture.
- [Daytona Review 2026: Sub-90ms AI Agent Code Execution Infrastructure](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/daytona-review-2026/) — Hands-on Daytona review: sub-90ms cold starts, open-source self-hosting, LangChain/Claude integration, and head-to-head comparison with E2B and Modal.
- [Faros AI Review 2026: Measure the Real ROI of AI Coding Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/faros-ai-coding-analytics-guide-2026/) — Faros AI review 2026: how the engineering intelligence platform measures real ROI from AI coding tools across 22,000 developers.
- [Best MCP Servers for Developers in 2026: Top 15 to Install Now](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-mcp-servers-for-developers-2026/) — The 15 best MCP servers for developers in 2026—curated by category, with security tips and starter stack recommendations.
- [Langflow vs n8n vs Dify: Which AI Workflow Tool Should Developers Choose?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langflow-vs-n8n-vs-dify-2026/) — A direct comparison of Langflow, n8n, and Dify for production AI workflows in 2026. Use-case-driven guide to picking the right tool.
- [Amp vs Claude Code vs GitHub Copilot: Agentic Coding Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/amp-vs-claude-code-vs-copilot-2026/) — Amp vs Claude Code vs GitHub Copilot compared head-to-head: benchmarks, pricing, context windows, and which tool fits your 2026 workflow.
- [GLM-5 and GLM-5.1 Review: Zhipu AI's Frontier Models for Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/glm-5-developer-review-2026/) — A developer-focused review of GLM-5 and GLM-5.1: benchmarks, pricing, self-hosting options, and when to choose them over GPT-5 or Claude.
- [Pieces for Developers Review 2026: LTM Memory + MCP Integration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/pieces-for-developers-review-2026/) — An honest 2026 review of Pieces for Developers: LTM-2.7 memory engine, MCP server integration, pricing, real drawbacks, and who should actually use it.
- [Blaxel Review 2026: Persistent AI Agent Sandbox with 25ms Resume](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/blaxel-review-2026/) — Blaxel 2026 review: persistent AI agent sandbox with 25ms resume times. See how it compares to E2B, Daytona, and Modal for long-running autonomous agents.
- [E2B vs Daytona vs Blaxel: AI Agent Code Execution Sandbox Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/e2b-vs-daytona-vs-blaxel-2026/) — E2B vs Daytona vs Blaxel: a head-to-head sandbox comparison covering cold starts, state persistence, pricing, and which provider fits which agentic workload in 2026.
- [Langflow vs n8n vs Flowise vs Dify: Full 4-Way AI Builder Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langflow-vs-n8n-vs-flowise-vs-dify-4way-2026/) — Langflow, n8n, Flowise, and Dify compared head-to-head across RAG pipelines, multi-agent systems, business automation, debugging, self-hosting, and production readiness for 2026.
- [Base44 Review 2026: The AI App Builder for Non-Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/base44-review-2026/) — Hands-on Base44 review 2026: pricing, features, Wix acquisition impact, and how it compares to Bolt.new and Lovable for non-developers.
- [Cursor vs Windsurf vs Claude Code Pricing: Full 2026 Comparison](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-vs-windsurf-vs-claude-code-pricing-2026/) — All three tools converged at $20/month Pro in 2026. Here is what actually separates them — token efficiency, hidden agent costs, and where your money goes.
- [Base44 vs Lovable vs Bolt: Which AI App Builder Wins in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/base44-vs-lovable-vs-bolt-2026/) — Base44 vs Lovable vs Bolt.new in-depth comparison for 2026: pricing, stack, code ownership, and which AI app builder fits your use case.
- [Grok 4 vs Claude Opus 4 vs Gemini 2.5 Pro: Best Coding Model Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/grok-4-vs-claude-opus-4-vs-gemini-coding/) — Grok 4, Claude Opus 4, and Gemini 2.5 Pro each lead a different benchmark in 2026. Here's which coding model actually fits your workflow, budget, and stack.
- [Windsurf vs Cursor for Solo Developers in 2026: Honest Comparison](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-vs-cursor-solo-developers-2026/) — Windsurf and Cursor both cost $20/month in 2026. Here's which AI IDE wins for solo devs based on real workflows, free tier, and agent quality.
- [C3 Code Review 2026: Enterprise AI Coding Platform That Turns Natural Language Into Production Apps](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/c3-code-enterprise-review-2026/) — Hands-on review of C3 Code, C3 AI's enterprise platform that converts natural language prompts into production-grade AI applications.
- [AI Code Security in Agentic Workflows 2026: SAST Tools for Cursor and Claude Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-code-security-agentic-workflows-2026/) — 92% of AI-generated codebases contain critical vulnerabilities. Here's how to secure agentic coding workflows with the right SAST tools in 2026.
- [GLM-5V-Turbo Review 2026: Zhipu AI Multimodal Agent Model](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/glm-5v-turbo-review-2026/) — GLM-5V-Turbo is Zhipu AI's native multimodal agent model with 94.8 Design2Code score, 202K context, and $1.20/M input pricing — the full developer review.
- [AI Agents SDK Comparison 2026: Strands vs OpenAI SDK vs Mastra](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-agents-sdk-comparison-2026/) — Side-by-side technical comparison of the three most important AI agent SDKs in 2026 — AWS Strands, OpenAI Agents SDK, and Mastra — covering features, pricing, and which to pick for your use case.
- [AI Coding Agents Enterprise Comparison 2026: Claude Code vs Cursor vs GitHub Copilot](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-agent-comparison-enterprise-2026/) — Enterprise comparison of Claude Code, Cursor, and GitHub Copilot in 2026 — compliance, security, pricing at scale, and deployment requirements.
- [AI Coding CLI Tools Comparison 2026: Claude Code vs Codex vs Gemini CLI vs Junie](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-cli-tools-comparison-2026/) — A direct benchmark comparison of Claude Code, Codex CLI, Gemini CLI, and Junie by accuracy, pricing, context window, and CI/CD integration for 2026.
- [AI Developer Tools Adoption Statistics 2026: The Complete Data](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-developer-tools-statistics-2026/) — 90% of developers now use at least one AI tool at work. Here is the complete 2026 dataset on adoption, market share, productivity impact, trust, ROI, and the benchmark numbers that actually matter.
- [AI for Contract Management &amp; Legal Review 2026: Best Tools for Document Analysis](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-contract-management-legal-review-2026/) — Compare the top AI contract management and legal review tools of 2026—Harvey AI, Ironclad, Spellbook, and more—with pricing, use cases, and ROI data.
- [AI for Healthcare 2026: Clinical NLP, Ambient Scribes, and Medical AI Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-healthcare-clinical-nlp-2026/) — The AI healthcare market hits $45.2B in 2026. Here is what clinical teams need to know about ambient scribes, clinical NLP, medical imaging AI, drug discovery, and compliance.
- [AI Terminal Coding Tools 2026: Claude Code vs Codex CLI vs Gemini CLI vs OpenCode](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-terminal-coding-tools-comparison-2026/) — A direct comparison of the four leading AI terminal coding agents in 2026: Claude Code, Codex CLI, Gemini CLI, and OpenCode — covering features, benchmarks, pricing, and which tool fits which team.
- [Amp Code Review 2026: Sourcegraph's Autonomous Coding Agent Tested](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/amp-code-review-2026/) — A hands-on review of Amp Code, Sourcegraph's autonomous coding agent. Covers multi-model routing, parallel subagents, Oracle Mode, Amp Tab, pricing, and how it stacks up against Cursor and Claude Code in 2026.
- [ChatGPT Super App Review 2026: Unified AI Platform with Codex, Atlas, and GPT-6](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/chatgpt-super-app-2026/) — Full review of the ChatGPT Super App 2026: Codex coding agent, Atlas browser automation, GPT-5.5 benchmarks, pricing, and a head-to-head comparison with Claude and Gemini.
- [Claude Code vs Codex CLI vs Gemini CLI 2026: Terminal AI Agents Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-codex-cli-gemini-cli-2026/) — Claude Code, Codex CLI, and Gemini CLI compared on benchmarks, pricing, setup, and real-world performance for 2026.
- [Cline vs Cursor vs GitHub Copilot 2026: VS Code AI Agent Showdown](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cline-vs-cursor-vs-copilot-2026/) — A direct comparison of Cline, Cursor, and GitHub Copilot in 2026: features, pricing, agent capabilities, and which tool fits which developer profile.
- [Comp AI Compliance Platform Review 2026: Open-Source Agentic Compliance](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/comp-ai-compliance-platform-guide-2026/) — Comp AI review 2026: open-source agentic compliance platform for SOC 2, HIPAA, ISO 27001, and GDPR—compared to Vanta, Drata, and Secureframe.
- [Cursor 3 vs Google Antigravity 2026: Which AI IDE Wins?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-3-vs-antigravity-2026/) — A direct comparison of Cursor 3 and Google Antigravity in 2026 — covering SWE-bench scores, Agents Window vs Manager View, pricing, context windows, MCP support, and security compliance.
- [Cursor Pro vs Pro Plus: Which Plan Is Right for You in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-pro-vs-pro-plus-2026/) — A direct comparison of Cursor Pro ($20/month) and Cursor Pro Plus ($40/month) covering parallel agents, Design Mode, context windows, enterprise security, and the exact scenarios where the higher tier pays for itself.
- [Cursor vs Windsurf vs Antigravity 2026: Agentic IDE Showdown](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agentic-ide-cursor-windsurf-antigravity-2026/) — A direct comparison of Cursor, Windsurf, and Google Antigravity across benchmarks, pricing, security, and parallel agent capabilities to find the best agentic IDE in 2026.
- [Cursor vs Windsurf vs GitHub Copilot 2026: Best AI Code Editor Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-vs-windsurf-vs-copilot-2026/) — Cursor, Windsurf, and GitHub Copilot compared for 2026 — features, pricing, agent modes, and which tool fits your team.
- [Gemma 4 vs Llama 4 vs Qwen 3: Best Open-Source LLM for Developers 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemma-4-vs-llama-4-vs-qwen-3-2026/) — Gemma 4 vs Llama 4 vs Qwen 3 2026: benchmarks, context windows, licensing, GPU requirements, and which open-source LLM wins for developer use cases.
- [Gumloop vs n8n vs Zapier 2026: AI-Native Automation Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gumloop-vs-n8n-vs-zapier-2026/) — A direct technical comparison of Gumloop, n8n, and Zapier in 2026 — covering AI architecture, pricing models, integration depth, and which platform actually belongs in your stack.
- [Kimi K2 vs Claude Opus vs GPT-5 Coding 2026: Moonshot's Model Benchmark](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/kimi-k2-vs-claude-vs-gpt5-coding-2026/) — A direct benchmark comparison of Kimi K2.5, Claude Opus 4.6, and GPT-5.3-Codex for coding in 2026. SWE-Bench, Terminal-Bench, LiveCodeBench, and pricing analysis.
- [LangGraph vs CrewAI vs AutoGen 2026: Which AI Agent Framework Should You Use?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langgraph-vs-crewai-vs-autogen-2026/) — LangGraph, CrewAI, and AutoGen compared for 2026. Architecture trade-offs, performance benchmarks, token costs, and a decision guide to pick the right AI agent framework for your project.
- [LLM Observability Tools Comparison 2026: LangSmith vs Langfuse vs Helicone vs Arize](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-observability-tools-comparison-2026/) — Compare LangSmith, Langfuse, Helicone, and Arize AI for LLM observability in 2026—pricing, features, and which tool fits your stack.
- [Mistral Small 4 Review 2026: EU-Compliant, Open-Weight, $0.40/M Input](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mistral-small-4-review-2026/) — Mistral Small 4 is a 119B MoE model unifying reasoning, vision, and coding in a single open-weight release with full GDPR compliance and Apache 2.0 licensing.
- [Modal vs Replicate 2026: Best Serverless ML Deployment for Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/modal-vs-replicate-ml-deployment-2026/) — Modal vs Replicate 2026 compared: cold starts, pricing, throughput, and which serverless ML platform fits your stack.
- [Workato vs Zapier vs n8n 2026: Enterprise Automation Platforms Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/workato-vs-zapier-vs-n8n-2026/) — A direct comparison of Workato, Zapier, n8n, and Make in 2026 — covering pricing, integrations, governance, and which platform fits your team.
- [DAST Tools Comparison 2026: Top 10 AI-Powered Dynamic Security Testing Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/dast-tools-comparison-2026/) — Compare the top 10 AI-powered DAST tools for 2026 — accuracy, CI/CD fit, API coverage, pricing, and which tool best matches your team's needs.
- [Zep AI Review 2026: Temporal Knowledge Graphs for Agent Memory](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/zep-ai-agent-memory-review-2026/) — Zep AI uses temporal knowledge graphs to give agents persistent, relationship-aware memory — outperforming Mem0 by 15 points on LongMemEval.
- [AI Coding Tools SOC 2 Compliance 2026: Enterprise Security Scorecard](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-tools-enterprise-soc2-compliance-2026/) — SOC 2 Type II compliance scorecard for 7 AI coding tools in 2026 — data residency, HIPAA, FedRAMP, zero-retention options compared.
- [AI for Legal Contract Analysis 2026: Tools, Use Cases, and ROI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-legal-contract-analysis-2026/) — AI contract analysis in 2026 cuts review time by 80% and attorney hours by 50-70%—market hits $5.59B. Best tools, ROI data, and implementation guide.
- [AI Risk Management &amp; Fraud Detection 2026: Tools, Methods, and Best Practices](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-fraud-detection-2026/) — AI fraud detection market hits $14.7B in 2025. Compare top tools, methods, and compliance requirements for financial services in 2026.
- [AI Workflow Automation Benchmarks 2026: Real Performance Data Across Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-workflow-automation-benchmarks-2026/) — Real 2026 benchmark data for n8n, Make, and Zapier: throughput, latency, cost at scale, AI step speed, and reliability metrics compared.
- [Best AI Coding Agents 2026: Full Comparison of 7 Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-agents-full-comparison-2026/) — Full comparison of the 7 best AI coding agents in 2026 — benchmarks, pricing, context windows, and which tool fits your workflow.
- [Goose AI Agent Review 2026: Block's Open-Source Local Coding Agent](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/goose-ai-agent-review-2026/) — Goose AI agent review 2026: Apache 2.0 open-source coding agent, 15+ LLM providers, 70+ MCP extensions, local Ollama support, and comparison to Claude Code and Aider.
- [Junie CLI Review 2026: JetBrains Terminal AI Agent with BYOK Support](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/junie-cli-review-2026/) — Junie CLI reviewed: JetBrains' terminal AI agent with BYOK for Anthropic/OpenAI keys, autonomous tasks, Git awareness, and IDE integration.
- [OpenAI o3 vs Claude Sonnet 2026: Reasoning Models for Developers Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-o3-vs-claude-reasoning-2026/) — OpenAI o3 vs Claude Sonnet 4.6 in 2026: benchmarks, pricing, API usage, and which reasoning model wins for your dev workflow.
- [Snyk vs Semgrep 2026: SAST Comparison for AI-Generated Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/snyk-vs-semgrep-comparison-2026/) — Snyk vs Semgrep 2026: accuracy, false positive rates, IDE integration, pricing, and which SAST tool wins for AI-generated code security.
- [Vellum AI Platform Review 2026: Best LLM Evaluation and Testing Tool?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vellum-ai-llm-evaluation-2026/) — Vellum AI 2026 review: prompt management, evaluation pipelines, A/B testing, and production monitoring for LLM teams. Pricing, comparisons, and verdict.
- [Windsurf vs Kiro for Enterprise Teams 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-vs-kiro-enterprise-2026/) — Windsurf Cascade Hooks vs Kiro MCP Registry: a deep-dive enterprise comparison covering compliance, data residency, and security architecture.
- [Gemma 4 Review 2026: Google's Best Open-Source Model Yet?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemma-4-review-2026/) — Gemma 4 review: benchmarks, model variants, Apache 2.0 license, and how it stacks up against Llama 4, GPT-4, and Claude in 2026.
- [Dify vs Flowise 2026: Which Open-Source AI Workflow Builder Wins?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/dify-vs-flowise-comparison-2026/) — Dify vs Flowise compared for 2026: features, self-hosting requirements, RAG pipelines, pricing, and which to pick for your team.
- [Claude Code Enterprise vs GitHub Copilot Enterprise 2026: Deep Comparison for Engineering Leaders](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-enterprise-github-copilot-2026/) — Claude Code hits 80.9% SWE-bench vs Copilot's inline-first model. Which enterprise AI coding tool wins for your team in 2026?
- [Corgea Review 2026: AI-Native SAST That Fixes Vulnerabilities Automatically](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/corgea-ai-sast-review-2026/) — Corgea review 2026: AI-native SAST that auto-generates fix PRs, 80% remediation effort reduction, GitHub/GitLab integration, and how it compares to SonarQube and Semgrep.
- [Cursor 3 Review 2026: Agent-First IDE, Parallel Agents, and Design Mode](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-3-review-2026/) — Cursor 3 review: $29.3B valuation, 8 parallel agents via git worktrees, Design Mode, Glass interface, and 78.2% SWE-bench score.
- [Grok 4 Review 2026: xAI Flagship Model, grok-code-fast, Benchmarks and API](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/grok-4-review-2026/) — Grok 4 review 2026: xAI flagship reasoning model, grok-code-fast coding variant, 2M context window, API setup, and benchmarks vs Claude Opus 4.7 and GPT-5.5.
- [Make vs n8n 2026: Which Open-Source Automation Tool Wins?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/make-vs-n8n-comparison-2026/) — Make vs n8n 2026: operations vs executions billing, 1,500+ connectors vs 400+ nodes, self-hosting, AI features, and which platform fits your team.
- [Neurolink AI Framework Review 2026: One SDK for 12+ LLM Providers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/neurolink-ai-framework-review-2026/) — An honest review of NeuroLink AI framework by Juspay: unified access to 13+ LLM providers, native MCP integration, and enterprise HITL in one TypeScript SDK.
- [Gumloop Review 2026: AI-Native Workflow Automation Platform](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gumloop-review-2026/) — Gumloop review 2026: AI-native automation platform, credit pricing, 125+ integrations, $50M Series B, and who should use it vs Zapier and n8n.
- [SonarQube AI CodeFix Review 2026: Is It Worth It for Developer Teams?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/sonarqube-ai-codefix-review-2026/) — SonarQube AI CodeFix review 2026: how it works, pricing tiers, bring-your-own-LLM support, performance vs CodeRabbit, and whether it's worth the Enterprise cost.
- [Taskade AI Agents Review 2026: No-Code Multi-Agent Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/taskade-ai-agents-review-2026/) — Taskade AI agents review 2026: Genesis no-code builder, multi-agent teams, flat-rate pricing, and how it compares to Zapier, Make, and n8n for business automation.
- [Best Local LLM Models 2026: Benchmarks, Hardware, and Use Cases](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-local-llm-models-2026/) — The best local LLM models in 2026 ranked by benchmarks, with hardware requirements, runtime tool comparisons, and use case recommendations.
- [AI Browser Agents Comparison 2026: Comet vs Browser-Use vs Operator](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-browser-agents-comparison-2026/) — Comet, Browser-Use, and Operator compared head-to-head on benchmarks, pricing, real-world performance, and enterprise readiness in 2026.
- [Best CodeRabbit Alternatives in 2026: Top AI Code Review Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/coderabbit-alternatives-comparison-2026/) — The 7 best CodeRabbit alternatives in 2026 ranked by accuracy, price, and platform—Qodo Merge, Greptile, BugBot, and more.
- [DeepSeek V4 Review 2026: 50x Cheaper Than GPT-5.4?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/deepseek-v4-review-2026/) — DeepSeek V4-Pro delivers near-frontier coding performance at $1.74/M input tokens — 70-80x cheaper than GPT-5.4 Pro. Here's what that means for developers.
- [Perplexity Comet Browser Review 2026: AI Browser Worth Switching?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/perplexity-comet-browser-review-2026/) — Perplexity Comet browser review 2026: features, privacy risks, CometJacking security flaws, and whether it's worth replacing Chrome.
- [MCP Streamable HTTP Production Guide 2026: stdio vs Streamable HTTP](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-production-guide-streamable-http-2026/) — Complete guide to choosing and deploying MCP transports in 2026: stdio vs Streamable HTTP, auth, scaling, and platform recipes for Cloudflare, AWS ECS, and Kubernetes.
- [Langflow Review 2026: Visual AI Workflow Builder for LLM Orchestration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langflow-review-2026/) — Langflow review 2026: 100K GitHub stars, MCP server export, RAG pipelines 10x faster — plus honest limits and alternatives.
- [Power Automate vs Zapier vs n8n 2026: Enterprise Automation Showdown](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/power-automate-vs-zapier-vs-n8n-2026/) — Power Automate vs Zapier vs n8n 2026: real pricing numbers, GDPR compliance, AI agent features, and which enterprise automation platform wins for your use case.
- [Cubic.dev Review 2026: The Honest Developer's Take on AI Code Review](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cubic-dev-ai-code-review-2026/) — An honest Cubic.dev review for 2026: benchmarks, pricing, real team results, and when it beats CodeRabbit and GitHub Copilot.
- [AI Workflow Automation Cost Comparison 2026: n8n vs Zapier vs Make at Scale](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-workflow-automation-cost-comparison-2026/) — Real cost math comparing n8n, Zapier, and Make.com for AI workflows at scale — billing models, self-hosting, and where each platform wins.
- [Activepieces vs n8n 2026: Open-Source Automation Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/activepieces-vs-n8n-comparison-2026/) — Activepieces vs n8n 2026: pricing model differences, integration counts, self-hosting options, AI agent capabilities, and which open-source automation platform fits your team.
- [Lindy AI Review 2026: No-Code AI Agent Automation Platform](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/lindy-ai-review-2026/) — Hands-on Lindy AI review covering pricing, features, Gaia voice agent, Autopilot, and how it compares to Zapier, Make, and n8n in 2026.
- [AnythingLLM Review 2026: Local AI Knowledge Base and Agent Runtime](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/anythingllm-review-2026/) — An honest 2026 review of AnythingLLM covering RAG, agent runtime, MCP support, Docker setup, and how it compares to Open WebUI and PrivateGPT.
- [Cursor BugBot Review 2026: AI Security Checks in Every PR](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-bugbot-review-2026/) — Honest Cursor BugBot review: benchmarks, pricing, Autofix, learned rules, and how it stacks up against CodeRabbit and GitHub Copilot.
- [Sweep AI Review 2026: GitHub Issue to PR Automation — Is It Worth It?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/sweep-ai-review-2026/) — Honest Sweep AI review for 2026: 92% issue resolution rate, GitHub-native workflow, pricing vs Devin, and whether the JetBrains pivot changes the value proposition.
- [GPT-6 Review 2026: OpenAI's New Flagship Model — Benchmarks, API, and Developer Use Cases](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-6-review-2026/) — GPT-6 pre-training is done but not yet released. Here's every confirmed fact, benchmark projection, and API detail developers need to plan ahead.
- [Best AI SAST Tools 2026: Snyk vs Semgrep vs Checkmarx vs Corgea Ranked](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-sast-tools-comparison-2026/) — Ranked comparison of the best AI SAST tools in 2026: Snyk Code vs Semgrep vs Checkmarx vs Corgea — accuracy, false positive rates, AI auto-fix, and pricing.
- [VS Code vs Cursor vs Windsurf vs JetBrains AI 2026: Which IDE Should You Use?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vscode-cursor-windsurf-jetbrains-comparison-2026/) — Cursor leads on speed (72% autocomplete acceptance), Windsurf wins enterprise, VS Code + Copilot is safest. Full 2026 comparison with benchmarks and pricing.
- [Roo Code Review 2026: Open-Source Cline Fork with Multi-Agent Mode](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/roo-code-review-2026/) — Complete Roo Code review covering its multi-agent orchestration, Boomerang Tasks, shutdown, and where to migrate in 2026.
- [Vibe Coding Tools Comparison 2026: Cursor vs Replit vs Bolt vs Lovable vs v0](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vibe-coding-tools-comparison-2026/) — Hands-on comparison of the 5 major vibe coding tools in 2026 — Cursor, Replit, Bolt, Lovable, and v0 — with pricing, use cases, and a decision framework.
- [Cline vs Roo Code 2026: Best Open-Source VS Code AI Agent Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cline-vs-roo-code-2026/) — Cline vs Roo Code compared on architecture, Boomerang Tasks, cost control, and IDE support — find the right open-source VS Code AI agent for 2026.
- [Lovable vs Bolt.new Comparison 2026: Which AI App Builder Is Right for You?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/lovable-vs-bolt-comparison-2026/) — Lovable vs Bolt.new 2026 in-depth comparison: pricing, features, backend capabilities, and which AI app builder fits your use case.
- [AI Code Review Tools 2026: CodeRabbit vs Qodo vs Greptile vs GitHub Copilot](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-code-review-tools-2026/) — Honest comparison of the top AI code review tools in 2026: bug catch rates, noise levels, pricing, and which tool actually fits your team's workflow.
- [Lovable Review 2026: The $6.6B AI App Builder That Ships Real Products](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/lovable-review-2026/) — Honest Lovable review for 2026: pricing, agent mode, real build tests, and how it compares to Bolt and v0.
- [OpenAI Agents SDK v2 Guide 2026: Configurable Memory, Sandbox Orchestration, Filesystem Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-agents-sdk-v2-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to OpenAI Agents SDK v2 (April 2026): configurable memory, apply_patch filesystem tools, 7 sandbox providers, and AGENTS.md workspace config.
- [JetBrains Air Review 2026: Multi-Agent Development Environment from JetBrains](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/jetbrains-air-review-2026/) — JetBrains Air review 2026: the agentic IDE that orchestrates Codex, Claude, Gemini, and Junie simultaneously — pricing, real-world results, and honest verdict.
- [Magistral Review 2026: Mistral Open-Weight Reasoning Model That Beats DeepSeek R1](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/magistral-mistral-reasoning-model-review-2026/) — Magistral is Mistral's first open-weight reasoning model. The 24B Small variant runs locally on a MacBook and scores 73.6% on AIME-24 — beating DeepSeek R1 Zero.
- [Devstral Small 2 Local Setup Guide 2026: Run Mistral Coding Agent on Your Laptop](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/devstral-small-2-local-setup-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to running Devstral Small 2 (24B, 68% SWE-bench) locally via Ollama, vLLM, or llama.cpp — zero API fees, full privacy.
- [GPT-5.3 Codex Spark Review 2026: OpenAI Coding Model Benchmarked](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-3-codex-spark-review-2026/) — GPT-5.3 Codex Spark delivers 1,000+ tokens/sec on Cerebras hardware — here's how it benchmarks and when to use it.
- [Claude Opus 4.7 vs 4.6 vs Mythos Comparison 2026: Which Model Should You Use?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-opus-47-vs-46-vs-mythos-comparison-2026/) — Claude Opus 4.7, 4.6, and Mythos compared on benchmarks, real cost, and migration risk — so you pick the right model for your workload.
- [Google Jules AI Agent Review 2026: Async GitHub Coding Agent Tested](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/google-jules-ai-agent-review-2026/) — Google Jules AI agent review 2026: async GitHub coding agent powered by Gemini 2.5 Pro, free beta, VM isolation, and how it stacks up against Devin and Cursor.
- [Best Ollama Models for Coding 2026: Ranked and Tested](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ollama-models-coding-2026/) — The best Ollama models for coding in 2026, ranked by benchmark scores, VRAM requirements, and real-world performance on consumer hardware.
- [Devstral 2 Review 2026: Mistral's Open-Source Coding Agent Hits 72.2% SWE-bench](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/devstral-2-review-2026/) — Devstral 2 achieves 72.2% on SWE-bench Verified at $0.40/M tokens — the most capable open-weight coding model in 2026. Full review with benchmarks.
- [OpenCode AI Review 2026: Open-Source Terminal AI Agent Compared to Claude Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/opencode-ai-review-2026/) — OpenCode AI review 2026: 121K GitHub stars, MIT license, 75+ model providers. How it compares to Claude Code for real dev workflows.
- [Tray.io Review 2026: Enterprise AI Workflow Automation Deep Dive](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/tray-io-review-2026/) — Tray.io (now Tray.ai) review 2026: pricing, Merlin AI, connectors, and how it compares to Workato and Zapier for enterprise teams.
- [Claude Opus 4.6 Review 2026: The New SWE-Bench Leader for Coding](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-4-6-opus-review-2026/) — Claude Opus 4.6 review: 80.8% SWE-bench, 83% ARC-AGI-2 reasoning leap, Agent Teams compiler demo, and whether it's worth the upgrade over 4.5.
- [Cline AI Review 2026: Open-Source VS Code Coding Agent Tested](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cline-ai-review-2026/) — Honest Cline AI review 2026: BYOK model, 5M+ installs, real-world costs, and how it compares to Cursor, Claude Code, and Roo Code.
- [Dify AI Platform Review 2026: Open-Source LLMOps for Building AI Apps](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/dify-platform-review-2026/) — Hands-on Dify review 2026: open-source LLMOps with visual workflow builder, RAG pipelines, and model-agnostic AI agent framework for teams and enterprises.
- [Flowise Review 2026: Open-Source No-Code LLM App Builder](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/flowise-review-2026/) — Honest Flowise review 2026: features, pricing, setup complexity, and who should use this open-source visual LLM app builder.
- [GPT-5 vs Claude Opus 4 vs Gemini 3: 2026 Coding Benchmark Comparison](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-vs-claude-opus-4-vs-gemini-3-coding-2026/) — GPT-5 vs Claude Opus 4 vs Gemini 3 for coding in 2026 — SWE-bench, Terminal-Bench, pricing, and workflow-by-workflow recommendations.
- [Gemini 2.5 Pro Coding Review 2026: 2M Context Window vs Claude and GPT-5](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemini-2-5-pro-coding-review-2026/) — Gemini 2.5 Pro coding review 2026: 1M context window, native thinking mode, $1.25/M pricing vs Claude Opus and GPT-5 head-to-head.
- [Sourcegraph Cody Review 2026: AI Code Assistant for Large Codebases](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/sourcegraph-cody-review-2026/) — Sourcegraph Cody delivers full-repo context awareness, multi-LLM support, and enterprise-grade deployment at $9–19/user/month — best for large codebases.
- [Augment Code Review 2026: Enterprise AI Coding Agent with 500K-File Context](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/augment-code-review-2026/) — Augment Code 2026 review: SWE-bench Pro #1 at 51.8%, 400K+ file Context Engine, ISO 42001 certified. Is it worth $60–$200/mo for enterprise teams?
- [18 Best DevOps MCP Servers for 2026: K8s, CI/CD, and Monitoring](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/devops-mcp-servers-guide-2026/) — The 18 best DevOps MCP servers for 2026 — covering Kubernetes, CI/CD, monitoring, IaC, cloud, and security with setup tips and stack recommendations.
- [Best AI QA Testing Tools 2026: Agentic Test Automation Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-qa-testing-tools-comparison-2026/) — The 8 best AI QA testing tools in 2026 compared: Testsigma, QA Wolf, Mabl, Applitools, and more — ranked by real-world agentic capability.
- [Testsigma Review 2026: Agentic AI Testing Platform Deep Dive](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/testsigma-review-2026/) — Honest Testsigma review 2026: Atto AI agents, NLP test creation, pricing, and how it compares to BrowserStack and Katalon.
- [QA Wolf Review 2026: AI-Generated Playwright Tests at Scale](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qawolf-review-2026/) — Honest QA Wolf review 2026: pricing, AI Playwright test generation, pros/cons, and how it compares to Mabl, Testim, and BrowserStack.
- [Augment Code vs Cursor vs GitHub Copilot: Enterprise AI Coding Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/augment-code-vs-cursor-vs-copilot-2026/) — Augment Code vs Cursor vs GitHub Copilot compared on architecture, pricing, benchmarks, and enterprise compliance for 2026 buyers.
- [Claude Code PR Review Guide 2026: Parallel Agent Code Review Setup](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-pr-review-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Claude Code PR review in 2026 — parallel agent setup, GitHub App configuration, pricing, and comparison with GitHub Copilot.
- [CodeRabbit vs Qodo vs Greptile: Best AI Code Review Tool 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/coderabbit-vs-qodo-vs-greptile-2026/) — CodeRabbit, Qodo, and Greptile each excel in different scenarios — here's the data-driven breakdown to pick the right AI code review tool for your team in 2026.
- [LangGraph vs CrewAI vs Dapr: Production AI Agent Framework Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langgraph-crewai-dapr-comparison-2026/) — LangGraph, CrewAI, and Dapr compared head-to-head for production AI agents — durability, speed, cost, and decision framework for 2026.
- [Greptile Review 2026: AI Code Review That Understands Your Entire Codebase](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/greptile-review-2026/) — Greptile leads AI code review benchmarks with 82% bug catch rate and 100% high-severity detection — but is it right for your team?
- [Qodo Review 2026: AI Code Quality Platform (Formerly CodiumAI)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qodo-review-2026/) — Qodo combines AI PR review with test generation. Full 2026 review with pricing and benchmarks.
- [CodeRabbit Review 2026: AI Code Review Tool with 2M+ Repositories](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/coderabbit-review-2026/) — CodeRabbit is the most-installed AI code review tool on GitHub, connecting 2M+ repos and processing 13M+ PRs — here's a complete 2026 review.
- [ProjectDiscovery Neo Review: Nuclei-Based AI Pentest Agent That Found 66 Exploitable Vulnerabilities](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/projectdiscovery-neo-pentest-guide-2026/) — ProjectDiscovery Neo is an AI pentest agent that confirmed 66 exploitable vulnerabilities in benchmarks — more than any other tool tested.
- [RunSybil AI Pentesting Review 2026: IAM and Container Security Testing Evaluated](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/runsybil-cloud-pentesting-review-2026/) — Hands-on review of RunSybil's AI-native pentesting platform: IAM misconfiguration testing, container escape, CI/CD secret exposure, and how it compares to Pentera and NodeZero.
- [Escape.tech AI API Security Review 2026: Business Logic and Complex Auth Testing](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/escape-tech-ai-api-security-review-2026/) — In-depth review of Escape.tech's AI-driven DAST for API security in 2026: business logic testing, OAuth/JWT auth, BOLA/IDOR detection, and CI/CD integration.
- [OpenAI Hosted Shell and Apply Patch: GPT-5.5 Compute Tools for Autonomous Code Execution](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-hosted-shell-apply-patch-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to GPT-5.5's hosted shell and apply_patch tools for building autonomous coding agents via the OpenAI Responses API.
- [Continue.dev vs GitHub Copilot 2026: Open-Source Alternative That's Worth Switching To](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/continue-dev-vs-github-copilot-2026/) — Compare Continue.dev and GitHub Copilot: pricing, model flexibility, PR agents, and whether the open-source alternative is worth the switch.
- [Windsurf vs Cursor Performance 2026: Speed, Latency, and Real Workflow Benchmarks](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-vs-cursor-performance-2026/) — Real benchmark data comparing Windsurf vs Cursor in 2026: inference speed, autocomplete accuracy, multi-file refactor latency, and total cost.
- [Bolt.new vs Replit vs v0 2026: Which Browser-Based AI Builder Wins?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/bolt-new-vs-replit-vs-v0-2026/) — Honest 2026 comparison of Bolt.new, Replit, and v0 — pricing, frameworks, code quality, and which AI builder fits your project.
- [Claude Code + GitHub Actions 2026: Automate PR Reviews and CI Tasks with AI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-github-actions-2026/) — Complete guide to integrating Claude Code with GitHub Actions in 2026: setup, auth options, workflow patterns, cost controls, and security guardrails.
- [LLM API Pricing Comparison 2026: GPT-5 vs Claude vs Gemini vs DeepSeek Costs](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-api-pricing-comparison-2026/) — Up-to-date LLM API pricing for GPT-5, Claude, Gemini, and DeepSeek in 2026 — with hidden costs, batch discounts, and a use-case decision guide.
- [Tabnine vs GitHub Copilot 2026: Enterprise AI Coding Assistant Showdown](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/tabnine-vs-github-copilot-2026/) — Tabnine vs GitHub Copilot 2026 compared on code quality, pricing, privacy, and enterprise features — with a decision framework for regulated industries.
- [Cursor + Claude Code Workflow 2026: Using Both Tools Together Effectively](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-claude-code-workflow-2026/) — How to combine Cursor and Claude Code in a hybrid workflow — setup methods, work division strategy, and real cost savings for developers in 2026.
- [Amazon Q Developer Review 2026: AWS's AI Coding Assistant for Enterprise Teams](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/amazon-q-developer-review-2026/) — Amazon Q Developer 2026: pricing, agentic coding, Java transformation, AWS integration, versus Cursor and Copilot.
- [Qwen3-Coder Review 2026: The Open-Source Model That Rivals GPT-5](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qwen3-coder-review-2026/) — Qwen3-Coder 2026 review: benchmarks, pricing, local setup, and head-to-head vs Claude Opus 4.6 and GPT-5 — is it worth switching?
- [How to Build an AI Agent from Scratch 2026: Python + LangChain + Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/build-ai-agent-from-scratch-2026/) — Build a production-ready AI agent from scratch using Python, LangGraph, and custom tools — with memory, error handling, and deployment included.
- [AI Code Review Tools Comparison 2026: Which Tool Catches the Most Bugs in Your PRs?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-code-review-tools-comparison-2026/) — Greptile catches 82% of bugs vs CodeRabbit's 44% — but noise ratio and pricing change the real-world picture. Here's the honest 2026 comparison.
- [AI App Builder Guide 2026: How to Ship an MVP in a Weekend with Vibe Coding Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-app-builder-mvp-guide-2026/) — The definitive 2026 guide to AI app builders — Lovable, Bolt, Replit, v0 compared with a step-by-step weekend MVP playbook.
- [Claude Code GitHub Workflow 2026: PR Reviews, Commits, and CI Integration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-github-workflow-2026/) — Complete guide to Claude Code GitHub workflow: automated PR reviews, CI failure auto-fix, and enterprise CI/CD integration using claude-code-action@v1.
- [Replit Agent Review 2026: Build Full Apps from Plain English Prompts](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/replit-agent-review-2026/) — Honest Replit Agent V2 review after building real apps: pricing, benchmarks, autonomous debugging, and how it compares to Cursor, Bolt, and Lovable.
- [AI Coding Tools Pricing Comparison 2026: Free vs Paid Plans Broken Down](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-tools-pricing-2026/) — Complete breakdown of AI coding tool pricing in 2026: free tiers, $20/month plans, power tiers, hidden costs, and budget-optimized stacks.
- [Best MCP Servers for Developers 2026: 15 Tools Worth Installing](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-mcp-servers-developers-2026/) — The 15 best MCP servers for developers in 2026, ranked by production-readiness, security, and real-world impact on dev workflows.
- [DeepSeek V3.2 vs Claude Sonnet 4.6 vs GPT-5 2026: Same Quality, 90% Cheaper](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/deepseek-v3-2-vs-claude-vs-gpt5-cost-2026/) — DeepSeek V3.2 costs 90% less than GPT-5 and Claude Sonnet 4.6. Real benchmarks, dollar scenarios, privacy risks, and when to use each model.
- [LLM Context Window Comparison 2026: GPT-4o vs Claude vs Gemini](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-context-window-comparison-2026/) — GPT-4.1, Claude Opus 4.6, and Gemini 2.5 Pro compared on context window size, effective performance, pricing cliffs, and real-world use cases.
- [vLLM vs Ollama vs LM Studio 2026: Which Local LLM Serving Stack Actually Scales?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vllm-vs-ollama-vs-lm-studio-2026/) — vLLM, Ollama, and LM Studio compared on throughput, hardware requirements, and production readiness for 2026 developers.
- [Best Free AI Coding Tools 2026: Get 80% of Cursor at Zero Cost](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-free-ai-coding-tools-2026/) — The best free AI coding tools in 2026 compared honestly — including free tiers, open-source options, and practical $0 setups that rival paid tools.
- [Devin AI vs Claude Code vs SWE-agent: Autonomous Coding Agents Compared (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/devin-vs-claude-code-vs-swe-agent-2026/) — Devin AI, Claude Code, and SWE-agent take three radically different approaches to autonomous coding. Here's how to choose the right one.
- [OpenAI Codex vs GitHub Copilot 2026: Which Is Better for Developers?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-vs-github-copilot-2026/) — OpenAI Codex vs GitHub Copilot 2026 compared on accuracy, speed, pricing, and workflow — find out which AI coding tool fits your stack.
- [Antigravity IDE Review 2026: The Dark Horse AI Code Editor Worth Watching](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/antigravity-ide-review-2026/) — Honest Antigravity IDE review 2026: agent-first architecture, multi-model support, pricing controversy, and whether the $20/mo AI Pro plan is worth it.
- [Kiro AI IDE Review 2026: AWS's New Coding Agent Tested in Real Projects](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/kiro-ai-ide-review-2026/) — Deep review of Kiro, AWS's spec-driven AI IDE. Specs, Hooks, Steering Files vs Cursor and Claude Code. Pricing, safety, enterprise use cases.
- [vLLM vs Ollama for Production LLM Serving in 2026: The Honest Comparison](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vllm-vs-ollama-production-2026/) — Direct comparison of vLLM and Ollama for production LLM serving — throughput benchmarks, cost analysis, migration paths, and when to use each tool.
- [AI Coding Tools for Beginners 2026: The No-Hype Guide to Getting Started](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-tools-beginners-guide-2026/) — Honest guide to the best AI coding tools for beginners in 2026—what they actually do, which are free, and how to start without the hype.
- [GitHub Copilot Workspace Review 2026: Agent-Mode Coding in the Browser](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-copilot-workspace-review-2026/) — A hands-on GitHub Copilot Workspace review 2026 covering the Coding Agent, Agent Mode, pricing, performance stats, and how it compares to Cursor.
- [DeepSeek V3 Cost Comparison vs GPT-5 in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/deepseek-v3-cost-comparison-2026/) — DeepSeek V3.2 vs GPT-5.4 cost comparison with pricing, benchmarks, and recommendations for developer workflows.
- [Pipedream vs n8n 2026: Which Developer Automation Platform Wins?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/pipedream-vs-n8n-2026/) — Pipedream vs n8n 2026 compared across pricing, AI agents, self-hosting, and team fit — with a clear verdict for developers and ops teams.
- [Claude Opus 4.6 vs GPT-5 for Coding 2026: Real Developer Benchmarks](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-opus-4-vs-gpt-5-coding-2026/) — Claude Opus 4.6 leads SWE-bench Pro at 74% vs GPT-5.4's 57.7%, but GPT-5 is 6x cheaper. Here's the real data developers need in 2026.
- [Best LLM for Coding 2026: Claude Opus vs GPT-5 vs Gemini 3 Benchmarked](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-llm-for-coding-2026/) — Comprehensive 2026 benchmark of top coding LLMs — Claude Opus 4.6, GPT-5.4, Gemini 3.1 Pro, and open-source models ranked by real-world performance.
- [Gemini 3.1 Pro Review 2026: Developer Benchmark and Coding Performance](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemini-3-1-pro-review-2026/) — Gemini 3.1 Pro claims #1 on AI benchmarks with 77.1% ARC-AGI-2 — but 29s latency and enterprise gaps make it a nuanced choice for developers.
- [Continue.dev Review 2026: Open-Source GitHub Copilot Alternative](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/continue-dev-review-2026/) — Comprehensive Continue.dev review 2026 — CLI-first Continuous AI agents, local LLM support, and how it compares to Copilot and Cursor.
- [Aider AI Review 2026: The Terminal Coding Assistant That Actually Works](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/aider-ai-review-2026/) — Aider AI review 2026: open-source terminal coding assistant with 40K+ GitHub stars, 75+ model providers, git-native commits, and voice coding mode.
- [AI Risk Management &amp; Fraud Detection Tools 2026: Best Tools for Financial Institutions](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-risk-management-fraud-detection-tools-2026/) — The best AI fraud detection and risk management tools for banks and financial institutions in 2026—Feedzai, Palantir, Unit21, IBM, and more compared.
- [Google Antigravity vs Cursor vs Claude Code 2026: Agent-First IDE Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/antigravity-vs-cursor-vs-claude-code-2026/) — Google Antigravity vs Cursor vs Claude Code 2026 — full comparison of pricing, benchmarks, MCP support, and which AI IDE wins for your workflow.
- [AI Coding Tools for Teams 2026: Which Tools Scale Beyond Solo Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-tools-for-teams-2026/) — A developer's guide to AI coding tools that actually scale for engineering teams in 2026 — covering governance, security, and real productivity benchmarks.
- [MCP Gateway Tools Comparison 2026: Top 10 Tools for Enterprise AI Agent Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-gateway-tools-comparison-2026/) — Compare the top 10 MCP gateway tools for enterprise AI in 2026 — covering Bifrost, Composio, TrueFoundry, Kong, Cloudflare, and more.
- [Gemini CLI vs Codex CLI 2026: Google's Free Tier vs OpenAI's Rust-Built Agent](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemini-cli-vs-codex-cli-2026/) — Gemini CLI vs Codex CLI 2026: free tier limits, Rust-powered speed, 1M token context, Terminal-Bench scores, and pricing compared.
- [JetBrains AI vs GitHub Copilot vs Cursor 2026: Best AI IDE for Java and Kotlin Devs](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/jetbrains-ai-vs-github-copilot-vs-cursor-2026/) — JetBrains AI, GitHub Copilot, and Cursor compared for Java and Kotlin developers in 2026 — pricing, benchmarks, and which to pick.
- [LLM Coding Workflow Guide 2026: How Top Developers Structure AI-Assisted Development](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-coding-workflow-guide-2026/) — A 5-phase framework for structured AI-assisted coding in 2026: spec-driven planning, context packing, iterative implementation, quality gates, and tooling.
- [n8n vs Zapier vs Make: Best AI Workflow Automation in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/n8n-vs-zapier-vs-make-automation-2026/) — n8n, Zapier, and Make.com compared for AI workflow automation in 2026 — pricing, AI features, developer experience, and when to use each.
- [Claude Code Best Practices 2026: 15 Habits of Developers Who Ship Faster](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-best-practices-2026/) — 15 proven Claude Code best practices in 2026 that senior developers use to cut coding time by 40% — from CLAUDE.md setup to MCP server integration.
- [MCP vs A2A Protocol 2026: Understanding the Two Standards for AI Agent Communication](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-vs-a2a-protocol-2026/) — MCP connects agents to tools; A2A connects agents to agents. Here's how both protocols work, when to use each, and why production systems need both.
- [.cursorrules vs CLAUDE.md vs AGENTS.md 2026: Which AI Config File Should You Use?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursorrules-vs-claude-md-vs-agents-md-2026/) — Compare AI coding config formats: .cursorrules, CLAUDE.md, AGENTS.md, .cursor/rules. Which format best fits your team in 2026?
- [AI for Backend Developers 2026: Tools, APIs, and Patterns That Actually Work](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-for-backend-developers-2026/) — The complete backend developer's guide to AI tools, patterns, and APIs in 2026 — what's actually worth using in production.
- [Best AI Documentation Generator Tools 2026: Auto-Generate Docs From Code That Actually Make Sense](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-documentation-generator-tools-2026/) — The top AI documentation generator tools of 2026 tested and ranked — which ones produce docs developers actually want to read.
- [LangSmith vs Langfuse vs Helicone 2026: Best LLM Observability Tool for Production AI Apps](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langsmith-langfuse-helicone-comparison-2026/) — LangSmith vs Langfuse vs Helicone compared for 2026: pricing, features, tracing depth, and best LLM observability tool.
- [GPT-4o vs Claude 3.5 Sonnet vs Gemini 1.5 Pro: Developer Benchmark 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt4o-vs-claude-vs-gemini-developer-2026/) — Real benchmark data comparing GPT-4o, Claude 3.5 Sonnet, and Gemini 1.5 Pro on coding, speed, cost, and developer experience in 2026.
- [Activepieces Review 2026: The Open-Source Zapier That's Actually Free](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/activepieces-review-2026/) — Activepieces 2026 review: MIT-licensed, self-hostable workflow automation with unlimited free tasks. See how it stacks up against Zapier, Make, and n8n.
- [Best AI Agent Memory Frameworks in 2026: Mem0 vs Zep vs Letta Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-agent-memory-frameworks-2026/) — Compare Mem0, Zep, and Letta — the top AI agent memory frameworks in 2026 — with benchmarks, architecture breakdowns, and a decision framework.
- [Cursor vs VS Code Copilot 2026: Which AI IDE Wins for Developers?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-vs-vscode-copilot-2026/) — Cursor vs VS Code Copilot compared on features, pricing, privacy, and performance — find out which AI IDE is right for you in 2026.
- [LangChain vs LlamaIndex 2026: Which RAG Framework Should You Choose?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langchain-vs-llamaindex-2026/) — LangChain vs LlamaIndex 2026 compared across RAG quality, agent workflows, performance, and enterprise readiness — with a clear decision guide.
- [Vector Database Comparison 2026: Pinecone vs Weaviate vs Chroma vs pgvector](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vector-database-comparison-2026/) — Pinecone, Weaviate, Chroma, and pgvector compared on performance, pricing, and use cases for production RAG systems in 2026.
- [Fine-Tuning vs RAG vs Prompt Engineering: When to Use Which in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/fine-tuning-vs-rag-vs-prompt-engineering-2026/) — A practical decision framework for choosing between fine-tuning, RAG, and prompt engineering to customize LLMs in 2026.
- [Claude Code vs GitHub Copilot 2026: Terminal Agent vs IDE Assistant](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-vs-github-copilot-2026/) — Claude Code vs GitHub Copilot 2026: terminal agent vs IDE assistant. Real comparisons, pricing, and which to use.
- [Cursor vs Windsurf vs Zed: Best AI IDE in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-vs-windsurf-vs-zed-ai-ide-2026/) — Cursor, Windsurf, and Zed compared on AI features, pricing, performance, and Claude Code integration to find the best AI IDE in 2026.
- [AI Sales Forecasting Tools 2026: Best Predictive Analytics Platforms Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-sales-forecasting-tools-2026/) — AI sales forecasting tools for 2026 compared: Clari, Salesforce Einstein, Gong, and more. Find the best for your team.
- [AI Customer Success Tools 2026: Best Platforms for Retention and Upsell](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-customer-success-tools-2026/) — Top AI customer success tools in 2026 ranked by retention impact, cost, and team fit—with real stats and platform comparisons.
- [AI for Project Management in 2026: Best Tools for Agile and Remote Teams](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-project-management-tools-2026/) — Best AI project management tools for 2026: ClickUp, Wrike, Airtable, Jira &amp; Notion. Compare features, pricing &amp; AI capabilities for agile teams.
- [AI Lead Generation Tools 2026: Best Software for B2B Sales Prospecting](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-lead-generation-tools-2026/) — Top AI lead generation tools for 2026 ranked by accuracy, intent data, and ROI — with stacks for every B2B team size.
- [AI Affiliate Marketing Tools 2026: Best Tools for Link Building and Commission Optimization](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-affiliate-marketing-tools-2026/) — The top AI affiliate marketing tools in 2026 for content creation, SEO, link building, and commission optimization—ranked by ROI and ease of use.
- [Best AI Content Writing Tools 2026: Jasper vs Copy.ai vs Writesonic](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-content-writing-tools-2026/) — Jasper leads for long-form quality, Copy.ai dominates workflow automation, and Writesonic wins on budget. Here's the complete 2026 comparison.
- [AI Code Documentation Tools in 2026: Best Auto-Doc Generators for Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-code-documentation-tools-2026/) — The best AI code documentation tools in 2026 are GitHub Copilot, Cursor Pro, and Mintlify — ranked by accuracy, IDE integration, and team fit.
- [Best AI SEO Tools in 2026: Surfer SEO vs MarketMuse vs Clearscope](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-seo-tools-2026/) — Surfer SEO wins for fast on-page optimization, Clearscope for editorial teams, and MarketMuse for content strategy. See the full comparison inside.
- [AI UI UX Design Prototyping Tools 2026: Best Options Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-ui-ux-design-prototyping-tools-2026/) — The best AI UI UX design prototyping tools in 2026—ranked by feature, price, and workflow fit for teams that want to ship faster.
- [AI for HR and Talent Acquisition in 2026: Best Tools for Recruitment](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-hr-talent-acquisition-recruitment-2026/) — Discover the best AI HR and talent acquisition tools in 2026. Compare top platforms, features, pricing, and ROI to transform your recruitment process.
- [AI Legal Document Review and Contract Analysis in 2026: Complete Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-legal-document-review-contract-analysis-2026/) — AI legal document review in 2026 cuts manual contract review time by up to 80%, with the market growing to $5.59B—here are the best tools and workflows.
- [Local AI Model Serving Frameworks 2026: vLLM vs TGI vs Ray Serve Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/local-ai-model-serving-frameworks-2026/) — vLLM leads high-concurrency APIs, SGLang excels in multi-turn chat, Ray Serve adds enterprise orchestration, and TGI is in maintenance mode as of 2026.
- [Best AI Meeting Assistants 2026: Otter.ai vs Fireflies.ai vs Fathom Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-meeting-assistants-2026/) — The best AI meeting assistants in 2026 are Fathom (best free), Fireflies.ai (best for teams), and Otter.ai (best real-time transcription).
- [AI Cloud Cost Optimization Tools 2026: ProsperOps vs CAST AI vs Kubecost Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-cloud-cost-optimization-tools-2026/) — ProsperOps automates AWS commitments, CAST AI rightsizes Kubernetes, and Kubecost provides container visibility—each excels for different teams in 2026.
- [Best AI Test Generation Tools 2026: Diffblue vs CodiumAI vs Testim Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-test-generation-tools-2026/) — Top AI test generation tools in 2026: Diffblue Cover (Java unit tests), Qodo/CodiumAI (IDE-native generation), and Testim (AI-powered E2E automation).
- [Best AI Code Review Tools in 2026: DeepCode vs SonarQube AI vs CodeRabbit](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-code-review-tools-2026/) — The best AI code review tools in 2026 are DeepSource, CodeRabbit, and GitHub Copilot — ranked by benchmark accuracy, signal quality, and enterprise fit.
- [AI for DevOps and MLOps in 2026: Best Tools for CI/CD and Monitoring](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-for-devops-mlops-2026/) — The best AI tools for DevOps and MLOps in 2026: GitHub Copilot, Datadog, MLflow, and more — ranked for CI/CD, monitoring, and model deployment.
- [Best AI Tools for Social Media Management in 2026: Lately vs Jasper vs Buffer](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-tools-for-social-media-management-2026/) — The best AI tools for social media management in 2026 are Buffer (most accessible), Jasper AI (best brand voice), and Lately (best content repurposing).
- [Best AI Tools for E-commerce Personalization in 2026: Dynamic Yield vs Klevu vs Nosto](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-tools-for-ecommerce-personalization-2026/) — Dynamic Yield leads for enterprises, Nosto excels with agentic AI, and Klevu (Athos Commerce) dominates AI search—here's the 2026 comparison.
- [Best AI Tools for Data Science in 2026: The Complete Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-tools-for-data-science-2026/) — Best AI tools for data science in 2026: TensorFlow, PyTorch, OpenAI API, LangChain, and Vertex AI — how to pick the right stack.
- [AI vs Traditional Automation: Which Is Better for Business Workflows in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-vs-traditional-automation-business-workflows-2026/) — AI automation adapts and learns; traditional automation is fast and cheap for fixed tasks. In 2026, the best enterprises use both strategically.
- [Best AI Note-Taking Apps in 2026: Notion AI vs Mem vs Obsidian vs Reflect](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-note-taking-apps-2026/) — Best AI note-taking apps 2026: Notion AI for teams, Mem for zero-friction, Obsidian for power users, Reflect for privacy. Find your fit.
- [Perplexity vs ChatGPT vs Google: The AI Search Engine Battle of 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/perplexity-vs-chatgpt-vs-google-ai-search-2026/) — Perplexity wins on accuracy (92%), Google wins on reach, ChatGPT wins on versatility. In 2026, the best strategy is using all three for different tasks.
- [AI Hardware 2026: NVIDIA H200 vs AMD MI300X vs Google TPU v5 Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-hardware-2026/) — AI hardware 2026 compared: NVIDIA H200, AMD MI300X, and Google TPU v5 across performance, price, memory bandwidth, and total cost of ownership.
- [Generative AI for Marketing 2026: Best Tools for Content Creation and Campaigns](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/generative-ai-for-marketing-2026/) — Generative AI for marketing 2026 is used by 93% of companies to cut costs, boost conversions 30-50%, and run hyper-personalized campaigns at scale.
- [Multimodal AI 2026: GPT-5 vs Gemini 2.5 Flash vs Claude 4 — The Complete Comparison Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/multimodal-ai-2026/) — Compare GPT-5, Gemini 2.5 Flash, Claude 4 &amp; Qwen3 VL. Best multimodal AI 2026 for text, image, audio, video processing. Pricing, features guide.
- [Best AI Voice Cloning Tools in 2026: ElevenLabs vs Resemble vs Play.ht](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-voice-cloning-tools-2026/) — The best AI voice cloning tools in 2026 are ElevenLabs for quality, VoiceClone AI for value, and Resemble AI for enterprise — most creators need just one.
- [Best AI Workflow Automation Tools in 2026: Zapier vs n8n vs Make](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-workflow-automation-tools-2026/) — The best AI workflow automation tools in 2026 are Zapier for ease, n8n for developer control, and Make for visual cost-efficiency.
- [MCP vs RAG vs AI Agents: How They Work Together in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-vs-rag-vs-ai-agents-2026/) — MCP, RAG, and AI agents solve different problems. MCP connects tools, RAG retrieves knowledge, and agents orchestrate actions. See how they work together.
- [Best AI Video Generators in 2026: Veo 3 vs Runway vs Kling After Sora](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-video-generators-2026/) — Best AI video generators 2026: Veo 3.1 for quality, Runway Gen-4 for professionals, Kling 3.0 for value.
- [How to Run AI Models Locally: Ollama vs LM Studio in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ollama-vs-lm-studio-local-ai-2026/) — Ollama vs LM Studio 2026: Ollama for developers (52M monthly downloads), LM Studio for GUI. Both free—most power users run both.
- [ChatGPT vs Claude vs Gemini: Which AI Is Best for Writing in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/chatgpt-vs-claude-vs-gemini-writing-2026/) — Claude writes best prose, ChatGPT is most versatile, Gemini strongest for research—smart writers use all three.
- [Best AI Image Generators in 2026: Midjourney vs Flux vs DALL-E](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-image-generators-2026/) — Best AI image generators 2026: Midjourney for art, Flux for photorealism, GPT Image 1.5 for comprehension.
- [Best AI Agent Frameworks in 2026: LangGraph vs CrewAI vs AutoGen](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-agent-frameworks-2026/) — Best AI agent frameworks 2026: LangGraph for production, CrewAI for prototyping, AutoGen for conversational agents.
- [Blog Topics for SEO: What Should You Write About in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/blog-topics-for-seo-2026/) — The best blog topics for SEO match search intent, business goals, and low-competition long-tail keywords your audience already searches.
- [Best AI Coding Assistants in 2026: The Definitive Comparison](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-coding-assistants-2026/) — The best AI coding assistants in 2026 are Cursor, Claude Code, and GitHub Copilot — but the smartest developers combine two or more into a unified stack.
### In-depth Guides & Explainers
- [Superpowers &#43; Claude Code: TDD Workflow Setup Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/superpowers-claude-code-tdd-guide-2026/) — How to set up the Superpowers framework with Claude Code for enforced TDD workflows — with real configuration examples and what changes in practice.
- [Google Agentic Terminal Agent 2026: ReAct Loop + MCP + 1M Context Setup Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/google-agentic-terminal-agent-guide-2026/) — Complete setup guide for Gemini CLI as an agentic terminal agent — ReAct loop internals, MCP server config, and 1M token context window best practices.
- [Linux Foundation Agentic AI Foundation (AAIF): MCP + A2A Governance Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/linux-foundation-agentic-ai-foundation-2026/) — The Linux Foundation's Agentic AI Foundation (AAIF) brings MCP, goose, and AGENTS.md under neutral governance. Here's what it means for developers.
- [GitHub Agent HQ Guide 2026: Run Claude, Copilot, and Codex from One Interface](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-agent-hq-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to GitHub Agent HQ: assign issues to Claude, Copilot, and Codex from a single interface, compare PRs, and optimize agent selection for every task type.
- [Qwen 3.6 Plus Agentic Coding Guide: 1M Context Window for Complex Tasks](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qwen-3-6-plus-agentic-coding-2026/) — Qwen 3.6 Plus: Alibaba's 1M-context agentic coding model with Terminal-Bench 2.0 #1 ranking, always-on CoT, and 13x cheaper output than Claude Opus 4.7.
- [MCP v2.1 Server Cards: Auto-Discovery for AI Agent Tool Registries (2026 Guide)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-v2-1-server-cards-guide-2026/) — How to implement MCP v2.1 Server Cards and .well-known/mcp.json for automatic AI agent tool discovery — with Python and Node.js examples.
- [From Copilot to Agent: How to Rethink Your AI Coding Workflow in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/copilot-to-agent-workflow-shift-2026/) — How senior developers are shifting from Copilot autocomplete to full agentic workflows — with practical frameworks for making the transition in 2026.
- [The Composable AI Coding Stack: Using Cursor, Claude Code, and Codex Together (2026 Guide)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/composable-ai-coding-stack-cursor-claude-codex-2026/) — How to combine Cursor, Claude Code, and OpenAI Codex into one composable AI coding stack that multiplies developer output without tool sprawl.
- [ReAct Agent Pattern: The Complete Developer Implementation Guide for 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/react-agent-pattern-guide-2026/) — Build production-ready ReAct agents from scratch in Python, then scale with LangGraph. Covers the Thought→Action→Observation loop, pitfalls, security, and Reflexion upgrade.
- [OpenAI Codex Plugins Guide: 90+ Enterprise AI Workflow Integrations (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-plugins-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to OpenAI Codex's 90+ plugins for enterprise teams — categories, governance, CLI setup, custom development, and competitor comparison.
- [GitHub Model Selection Guide: Choosing Claude vs Codex for GitHub Coding Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-model-selection-coding-agents-2026/) — A practical guide to choosing between Claude and Codex models for GitHub coding agents — with benchmarks, cost breakdown, and task-based decision matrix.
- [OpenAI Codex Multi-Agent Enterprise Guide: Plugins, Persistent Memory &amp; Multi-Day Workflows (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/codex-multi-agent-enterprise-2026/) — OpenAI Codex's 2026 multi-agent update ships 90+ enterprise plugins, persistent memory, and multi-day autonomous workflows. Here's what actually matters for teams.
- [Azure Bicep IaC ARM Template Alternative Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/azure-bicep-iac-arm-template-alternative-developer-guide-2026/) — Azure Bicep이 ARM JSON 템플릿을 대체하는 이유와 마이그레이션, 모듈, CI/CD 통합 방법을 다루는 완전한 개발자 가이드.
- [OpenTofu vs Terraform Migration Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/opentofu-vs-terraform-migration-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete developer guide to migrating from Terraform to OpenTofu in 2026: license comparison, step-by-step migration, CI/CD updates, and decision framework.
- [React Testing Library AI Component Integration Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/react-testing-library-ai-component-integration-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to testing AI-powered React components in 2026 using RTL, Vitest, MSW, and Vercel AI SDK mock helpers.
- [ts-jest TypeScript Unit Testing Jest Integration Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ts-jest-typescript-unit-testing-jest-integration-guide-2026/) — Complete ts-jest setup guide for Jest 30 and TypeScript 5 in 2026: installation, configuration, ESM, monorepo, and common errors fixed.
- [YOLOX Object Detection Python Deployment Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/yolox-object-detection-python-deployment-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to deploying YOLOX object detection in Python: training, ONNX/TensorRT export, FastAPI Docker API, and production benchmarks.
- [MiniGPT-4 vs LLaVA-1.5 Multimodal Fine-Tune Benchmark 2026: Developer's Definitive Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/minigpt-4-vs-llava-1-5-multimodal-fine-tune-benchmark-2026/) — LLaVA-1.5 wins on every major benchmark, but MiniGPT-4's architecture still matters for spatial tasks. Here's which to fine-tune in 2026.
- [Arize Phoenix Guide: Open-Source LLM Observability for Developers (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/arize-phoenix-observability-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to Arize Phoenix: install, instrument LLM apps, trace RAG pipelines, and run evals — all open-source, zero vendor lock-in.
- [Claude Sonnet 5 Review: 82.1% SWE-bench, Dev Team Mode &amp; Pricing Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-sonnet-5-review-2026/) — Claude Sonnet 5 hits 82.1% SWE-bench Verified, introduces Dev Team multi-agent mode, and costs $3/MTok. Full developer review with pricing and migration guide.
- [OpenAI Codex Skills Guide: Reusable Agent Behaviors for Developer Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-skills-guide-2026/) — Master OpenAI Codex Skills — the reusable agent behavior system that encodes workflows once and deploys them indefinitely across dev teams.
- [Claude Mythos Cybersecurity Guide 2026: Zero-Day Detection and Project Glasswing Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-mythos-cybersecurity-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Claude Mythos cybersecurity capabilities, zero-day vulnerability detection, and how to access Project Glasswing in 2026.
- [How Cursor Hit $2B ARR: Product Decisions That Shaped AI IDE Dominance](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-2b-revenue-analysis-2026/) — Cursor reached $2B ARR in February 2026 — the fastest SaaS growth in history. Here are the specific product decisions that made it happen.
- [OpenAI Codex Desktop Guide 2026: Full Agentic IDE Workflows and GPT-5-Codex](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-desktop-guide-2026/) — OpenAI Codex Desktop 설치부터 병렬 에이전트, AGENTS.md 설정, GitHub PR 자동화까지 — 2026년 완전 가이드.
- [Agentic Engineering: The Developer Guide Beyond Vibe Coding](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agentic-engineering-guide-2026/) — 92% of developers now use vibe coding, yet 63% waste more time debugging AI-generated code than writing it. This guide covers the practices, tools, and workflow of agentic engineering for production-ready development.
- [OpenObserve LLM Monitoring Guide 2026: Open-Source Observability for AI Applications](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openobserve-llm-monitoring-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to OpenObserve LLM monitoring in 2026: setup, integrations, cost tracking, and comparison with Helicone, LangSmith, and Portkey.
- [Z.ai API Developer Guide 2026: GLM Models, Pricing, and Setup](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/z-ai-api-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete Z.ai API guide: GLM model lineup, Coding Plan pricing, OpenAI/Anthropic-compatible endpoints, and step-by-step Claude Code setup.
- [AI Agent Governance Guide 2026: Compliance, Access Control, and Runtime Security](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-agent-governance-guide-2026/) — The AI governance market hits $9.2B by 2026. Build compliant AI agent governance with RBAC, audit trails, zero-trust, and EU AI Act mapping — practical guide for 2026.
- [Windsurf Browser Cascade Guide 2026: How Cascade Reads Your Browser Context](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-browser-guide-2026/) — How Windsurf's Cascade engine reads browser context—previews, @web, MCP tools, and the full context assembly pipeline explained.
- [AI Agent Testing Guide 2026: Practical Evaluation Framework for Multi-Step Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-agent-testing-guide-2026/) — A practical 2026 guide to evaluating multi-step AI agents — from golden datasets and trajectory metrics to CI/CD gates and production monitoring.
- [Cursor Rules Advanced Guide 2026: Framework-Specific Configs &amp; .mdc Best Practices](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-rules-advanced-2026/) — Master Cursor rules advanced configuration in 2026: .mdc frontmatter, four activation modes, framework templates for React/Next.js/FastAPI, and token optimization.
- [Windsurf Wave 10 Planning Mode Guide: Browser-Aware Cascade &amp; plan.md Workflow](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-wave-10-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Windsurf Wave 10: Planning Mode, browser-aware Cascade, plan.md workflow, and o3 pricing changes for developers.
- [ZenML Guide 2026: Production MLOps Pipelines Without the Lock-In](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/zenml-mlops-pipeline-guide-2026/) — Complete ZenML guide 2026: build production MLOps pipelines with @step/@pipeline decorators, swap infra without rewrites, and avoid vendor lock-in.
- [Gemma 4 On-Device Deployment Guide: Run Google's Open Model Locally](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemma-4-on-device-guide-2026/) — Run Gemma 4 locally with Ollama, LM Studio, or llama.cpp. Hardware requirements, quantization guide, mobile deployment, and fine-tuning with QLoRA.
- [OpenAI Agent Builder No-Code Guide: Build AI Agents Without the SDK](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-agent-builder-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to building production AI agents with OpenAI Agent Builder — no SDK, no Python, no engineering team required.
- [MCP Security Guide 2026: Risks, Prompt Injection and Safe Deployment](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-security-guide-2026/) — A developer's practical guide to MCP security risks in 2026: prompt injection, tool poisoning, rug pull attacks, and a 20-point production checklist.
- [LLM Red Teaming Guide 2026: Security Testing for AI Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-red-teaming-guide-2026/)
- [LLM Structured Outputs Guide 2026: JSON Mode, Instructor &amp; Outlines](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-structured-output-guide-2026/) — The complete 2026 guide to LLM structured outputs: why prompt-only JSON fails, Instructor vs Outlines, native APIs from OpenAI/Anthropic/Google, and production reliability patterns.
- [Continue CLI Guide: Async Cloud Agents for Developers (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/continue-cli-cloud-agents-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Continue CLI (cn) for async cloud agents — install, config.yaml, headless mode, GitHub Actions, and parallel agent execution.
- [Claude Code Max Plan Guide: Is the $100/month Worth It?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-max-plan-guide-2026/) — Claude Code Max plan explained: 5x vs 20x tiers, real token math, API billing comparison, and which developer profiles should upgrade.
- [Windsurf Pricing 2026: Plans, Credits and Real Costs Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-pricing-guide-2026/) — Complete breakdown of Windsurf's 2026 pricing: Free, Pro ($20/mo), Max ($200/mo), Teams, Enterprise, and the quota system that replaced credits.
- [Windsurf Wave 13 Guide: Arena Mode, Plan Mode and SWE-1.5 (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-wave-13-arena-mode-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Windsurf Wave 13 and Wave 14 features: SWE-1.5 free model, parallel Git worktree agents, Arena Mode, and Plan Mode.
- [SWE-bench Explained: How to Use Coding Benchmarks to Pick an LLM (2026 Guide)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/swe-bench-coding-benchmarks-guide-2026/) — SWE-bench measures how well LLMs fix real GitHub issues. Learn how to read the leaderboard, spot contaminated scores, and pick the right model for your codebase.
- [Qwen 3.5 Coding Guide: Open-Weight Model That Rivals GPT-5](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qwen-3-5-coding-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Qwen 3.5 Coder: benchmark performance, model sizes, self-hosting hardware requirements, VS Code integration, and cost-performance comparison with GPT-5.
- [Terminal-Bench 2.0 Explained: The New Standard for AI Agent Benchmarks (2026 Guide)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/terminal-bench-2026-guide/) — Terminal-Bench 2.0 evaluates AI agents on real terminal tasks — compiling code, administering systems, running security workflows. Here's how the 2026 leaderboard breaks down and how to use the scores to choose your model.
- [Qwen 3 32B Local Setup Guide 2026: Run on a 24GB GPU](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qwen-3-32b-local-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to running Qwen3 32B locally on a 24GB GPU using Ollama, llama.cpp, or LM Studio with thinking mode explained.
- [Anthropic Enterprise Security 2026: Claude, Data Handling, and Compliance Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/project-glasswing-guide-2026/) — Complete 2026 guide to Anthropic Claude enterprise security: SOC 2 Type II, HIPAA BAA, zero-day retention, GDPR, SSO, and compliance head-to-head.
- [Claude Code Worktrees Guide 2026: Run Parallel Sessions Without Conflicts](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-worktrees-guide-2026/) — A complete guide to running multiple Claude Code sessions simultaneously without file conflicts. Covers the --worktree flag, subagent isolation, real parallel workflow patterns, and lifecycle management.
- [Claude for Enterprise 2026: Security, Compliance, and Deployment Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-cowork-enterprise-security-guide-2026/) — The definitive 2026 guide to Claude Enterprise security architecture: SOC 2 Type II, HIPAA BAAs, GDPR data residency, SSO/SAML, audit logs, and side-by-side compliance comparisons against Microsoft Copilot, OpenAI Enterprise, and Google Gemini.
- [GPT-5.5 Pro API Enterprise Guide: $30 per Million Tokens, Highest Accuracy Tier](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-5-pro-enterprise-api-guide-2026/) — Complete enterprise guide to GPT-5.5 Pro API: $30/M token pricing, reasoning.effort settings, Batch API cost reduction, and benchmark comparisons against Claude Opus 4.7.
- [Claude Mythos Preview Guide 2026: What Developers Need to Know](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-mythos-preview-developer-guide-2026/) — Claude Mythos developer preview 2026: 92% SWE-bench Pro, 40% productivity gains, API access, enterprise deployment, and how it compares to Claude Opus 4.7.
- [Gemini 3.1 Ultra API Developer Guide: 2M Context Window](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemini-3-1-ultra-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete developer guide to Gemini 3.1 Ultra: 2M token context, Python SDK setup, multimodal API, pricing, benchmarks, and Vertex AI enterprise deployment.
- [Mem0 Guide 2026: Add Persistent Memory to Your AI Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mem0-agent-memory-guide-2026/) — Add persistent memory to AI agents with Mem0: architecture, quick start, memory scoping, LangChain integration, pricing, and production best practices.
- [Claude Opus 4.7 Developer Guide: xhigh Effort, Task Budgets, and Migration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-opus-4-7-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete Claude Opus 4.7 developer guide: xhigh effort levels, task budgets, adaptive thinking, breaking API changes, and migration from Opus 4.6.
- [GLM-4.7 Coding Guide 2026: The Open-Source LLM Beating Claude Sonnet](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/glm-4-7-coding-guide-2026/) — GLM-4.7 scores 73.8% on SWE-bench and 84.9% on LiveCodeBench V6 — matching Claude Sonnet 4.5 at zero API cost. Here's how to set it up and when to use it.
- [Run Gemma 4 Locally in 2026: 31B Dense Setup Guide with Ollama](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemma-4-local-setup-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to running Gemma 4 31B Dense locally with Ollama — hardware requirements, installation, Open WebUI, and API usage.
- [Claude Code Task Budgets Guide 2026: Control Token Spend in Agentic Sessions](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-task-budgets-guide-2026/) — Claude Code task budgets 2026: how to set token spend limits for agentic sessions via API and CLI, avoid cost explosions, and tune budgets for real workloads.
- [Perplexity Sonar API Guide 2026: Add Real-Time Search to Your App](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/perplexity-sonar-api-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to integrating the Perplexity Sonar API for web-grounded AI responses with citations, streaming, and domain filtering.
- [AI Agent Memory Architecture Guide 2026: Mem0, Zep, LangGraph Store Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agent-memory-architecture-guide-2026/) — AI agent memory architecture guide 2026: Mem0 vs Zep vs Letta vs LangGraph Store — benchmarks, pricing, temporal knowledge graphs, and which framework fits your use case.
- [Cloudflare Project Think Guide 2026: Build Long-Running AI Agents with Durable Execution](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cloudflare-project-think-ai-agents-guide/) — Cloudflare Project Think 2026: build long-running AI agents with durable execution, Fibers, Facets, and Workers infrastructure.
- [Windsurf Cascade Deep Dive 2026: How the AI Flow Engine Actually Works](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-cascade-deep-dive-2026/) — How Windsurf Cascade works: RAG-based context tracking, the Memories system, .windsurfrules setup, SWE-1.5, and where it beats Cursor and Copilot.
- [LLM Benchmarks Guide for Developers 2026: SWE-bench, GPQA, LiveCodeBench Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-benchmarks-guide-2026/) — A practical 2026 guide to LLM benchmarks for developers: which ones still signal real performance and which to stop trusting.
- [How to Cut Claude Code Costs by 70%: Token Limits, Caching, and Budgets](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-cost-optimization-guide-2026/) — Practical techniques to reduce Claude Code token usage by 40-70% using prompt caching, budget enforcement, and smarter context management.
- [OpenAI Agents SDK TypeScript: Complete Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-agents-sdk-typescript-2026/) — Build production-ready AI agents in TypeScript with the OpenAI Agents SDK — handoffs, tools, guardrails, sessions, MCP, and voice agents explained.
- [LangGraph TypeScript Guide: Build AI Agents in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langgraph-typescript-guide-2026/) — Complete LangGraph TypeScript guide for 2026: StateGraph, streaming, checkpointing, HITL, and multi-agent systems with real code examples.
- [MCP Streamable HTTP Production Guide 2026: stdio vs Streamable HTTP](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-production-guide-streamable-http-2026/) — Complete guide to choosing and deploying MCP transports in 2026: stdio vs Streamable HTTP, auth, scaling, and platform recipes for Cloudflare, AWS ECS, and Kubernetes.
- [MCP OAuth 2.1 Authentication: Complete Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-oauth-authentication-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to implementing OAuth 2.1 authentication for MCP servers in 2026, covering PKCE, Protected Resource Metadata, and enterprise gateway patterns.
- [Make.com AI Agents Guide 2026: Build Autonomous Workflows with Maia](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/make-ai-agents-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to building Make.com AI agents with Maia in 2026 — reasoning panel, multimodal inputs, and real-world use cases.
- [n8n MCP Integration Guide 2026: Connect Claude and AI Agents to Your Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/n8n-mcp-integration-guide-2026/) — How to integrate n8n with Model Context Protocol (MCP) in 2026 — set up n8n as an MCP server, connect Claude Desktop, and build workflows without touching the UI.
- [Local AI Agents Guide 2026: Build Offline AI Agents with Ollama and Cline](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/local-ai-agents-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to building offline AI agents with Ollama and Cline in 2026 — privacy-first, zero API costs, works air-gapped.
- [Figma MCP Server Guide 2026: Design to Code with AI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/figma-mcp-design-to-code-2026/) — Complete guide to the Figma MCP server: setup, remote vs desktop, Code Connect, and real-world design-to-code workflows with AI agents in 2026.
- [OpenAI Codex Computer Use Guide 2026: Background Agents That Operate Your Mac](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-computer-use-guide-2026/) — OpenAI Codex computer use lets background agents operate your Mac autonomously — here's the complete setup guide with security, plugins, and real use cases.
- [Cursor 2.0 Parallel Agents Guide: Run 8 Simultaneous AI Agents on Your Codebase](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-2-parallel-agents-guide/) — Run up to 8 AI agents simultaneously in Cursor 2.0 using git worktrees. Complete setup guide, /multitask command, background agents, and real-world use cases.
- [Llama 4 API Developer Guide 2026: Scout, Maverick, MoE Architecture and Integration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llama-4-api-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete developer guide to Llama 4 Scout and Maverick APIs: MoE architecture, 10M-token context, pricing, vLLM deployment, and OpenAI-compatible integration.
- [Windsurf Arena Mode Guide 2026: Run Two AI Models Side-by-Side on Your Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-arena-mode-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Windsurf Arena Mode: how blind model comparison works, SWE-1.5 vs Claude benchmarks, leaderboard mechanics, and credit cost breakdown.
- [Windsurf Wave 13 Guide 2026: What's New and How to Use the Latest Features](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-wave-13-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Windsurf Wave 13 'Shipmas Edition': free SWE-1.5 model, true parallel agents with Git worktrees, Arena Mode, Plan Mode, and more.
- [OpenAI Agents SDK v2 Guide 2026: Configurable Memory, Sandbox Orchestration, Filesystem Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-agents-sdk-v2-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to OpenAI Agents SDK v2 (April 2026): configurable memory, apply_patch filesystem tools, 7 sandbox providers, and AGENTS.md workspace config.
- [Qwen 3 Full Model Lineup Guide 2026: 0.6B to 72B with Dual-Mode Thinking](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qwen-3-full-lineup-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to every Qwen 3 model from 0.6B to 235B — specs, VRAM requirements, dual-mode thinking, benchmarks vs. DeepSeek R1 and GPT-4o.
- [Llama 4 Scout Developer Guide 2026: 10M Token Context Window for Full Codebase Analysis](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llama-4-scout-guide-2026/) — Practical guide to Llama 4 Scout's 10M token context window: API setup, full codebase loading, local deployment with Ollama and vLLM, and real pricing comparisons.
- [GPT-5.4 API Developer Guide 2026: 1M Context, Computer Use, and 5 Reasoning Levels](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-4-api-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete GPT-5.4 API guide: 1M token context, 5 reasoning effort levels, native computer use, pricing tiers, and migration from gpt-4o/gpt-5.2.
- [Devstral Small 2 Local Setup Guide 2026: Run Mistral Coding Agent on Your Laptop](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/devstral-small-2-local-setup-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to running Devstral Small 2 (24B, 68% SWE-bench) locally via Ollama, vLLM, or llama.cpp — zero API fees, full privacy.
- [Multi-Model LLM Routing Guide 2026: Cut AI Costs 85% with Smart Routing](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/multi-model-llm-routing-guide-2026/) — Smart LLM routing cuts AI costs up to 85% by directing queries to cheaper models without sacrificing quality. Here's the complete 2026 guide.
- [AI Pair Programming 2026: How to Code 10x Faster with AI Assistance](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-pair-programming-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to AI pair programming in 2026: tool comparisons, productivity strategies, and real ROI data from top developers.
- [Vibe Coding Explained: The Complete Developer Guide for 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vibe-coding-explained-the-complete-developer-guide-for-2026/) — Vibe coding lets developers build software by describing intent in natural language and letting AI write the code — here's everything you need to know in 2026.
- [Agno Framework Guide 2026: The Fastest Python AI Agent Library (Formerly Phidata)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agno-phidata-framework-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Agno (formerly Phidata): 5,000x faster than LangGraph, 100+ tools, multimodal support, and production deployment with AgentOS in 2026.
- [Cursor Worktrees Guide 2026: Parallel Agents Without File Conflicts](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-worktrees-parallel-agents-2026/) — Learn how to run multiple Cursor AI agents in parallel using Git worktrees — no file conflicts, faster feature delivery, and smarter model comparison.
- [Make.com AI Automation Guide 2026: Scenarios, Agents, and Integrations](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/make-com-ai-automation-guide-2026/) — Complete Make.com AI automation guide for 2026: scenarios, pricing, templates, and how it compares to n8n for AI agent workflows.
- [LLM Function Calling and Tool Use Guide 2026: OpenAI, Anthropic, Google](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-function-calling-tool-use-guide-2026/) — Complete 2026 guide to LLM function calling across OpenAI, Anthropic, and Google Gemini—with code, security, and production patterns.
- [GitHub Copilot Coding Agent Guide 2026: Autonomous Background Task Agent](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-copilot-coding-agent-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to GitHub Copilot's autonomous coding agent: how it works, pricing, use cases, and when to use it vs interactive agents like Claude Code.
- [Cursor Composer 2 Guide 2026: Frontier Coding Model at $0.50/M Tokens](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-composer-2-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Cursor Composer 2: benchmarks, pricing, architecture, and how it compares to Claude Code, Copilot, and GPT-5.4.
- [n8n AI Agent Nodes Guide 2026: Build Workflows That Think and Act](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/n8n-ai-agent-nodes-guide-2026/) — A hands-on guide to n8n AI Agent nodes in 2026: architecture, memory types, tool nodes, MCP patterns, and production deployment.
- [Cursor 3 Agents Window Guide: Glass Interface, Design Mode, and Worktrees Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-3-glass-agents-window-deep-dive-2026/) — A complete guide to Cursor 3 Glass — covering the Agents Window, Design Mode, and Worktrees for parallel agent-first development in 2026.
- [Claude API 300K Output Tokens: Complete Guide to Long-Form Generation (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-api-max-tokens-300k-guide-2026/) — How to unlock Claude API 300K output tokens via the Message Batches API with the output-300k-2026-03-24 beta header — with Python code examples.
- [Gemini Flash-Lite Batch API: 50% Cost Savings for High-Volume Tasks (2026 Guide)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemini-3-1-flash-lite-batch-api-cost-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Gemini 3.1 Flash-Lite Batch API: 50% discount, JSONL implementation, real cost calculators, and 90%+ savings with prompt caching.
- [Claude Opus 4.7 Tokenizer Cost Trap: Up to 35% More Tokens Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-opus-4-7-tokenizer-cost-guide-2026/) — Claude Opus 4.7 tokenizer uses 1.20x–1.47x more tokens for code. Same price, higher cost. Here's who pays more and how to reduce it.
- [OpenAI Computer Use API Developer Guide 2026: Build Browser Automation Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-computer-use-api-guide-2026/) — A complete developer guide to OpenAI Computer Use API: setup, code walkthroughs, security sandboxing, and comparison with Claude computer use.
- [ChatGPT Workspace Agents (Codex-Powered): Team Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/chatgpt-workspace-agents-guide-2026/) — Complete team guide to ChatGPT Workspace Agents powered by Codex — build, deploy, and govern autonomous agents in Slack and across your stack.
- [Claude Code PR Review Guide 2026: Parallel Agent Code Review Setup](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-pr-review-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Claude Code PR review in 2026 — parallel agent setup, GitHub App configuration, pricing, and comparison with GitHub Copilot.
- [OpenAI Codex Cloud Agent Guide 2026: Autonomous GitHub PR Generation](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-cloud-agent-guide-2026/) — OpenAI Codex cloud agent in 2026 autonomously clones repos, writes code, runs tests, and opens PRs — a complete guide to async GitHub workflows.
- [GPT-5.5 Agentic Coding Guide: Terminal-Bench 2.0, Computer Use, Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-5-agentic-coding-guide-2026/) — Complete developer guide to GPT-5.5 agentic coding: Terminal-Bench 2.0 results, computer use setup, Responses API workflows, and benchmark comparisons.
- [Zed AI Editor Guide 2026: ACP Protocol, AI Features, and Performance](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/zed-ai-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Zed AI in 2026: ACP protocol, 0.12s startup, 120fps GPU rendering, AI features, pricing, and Cursor vs VS Code.
- [1Password Unified Access for AI Agents: Developer Security Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/1password-unified-access-ai-agents-2026/) — How to use 1Password Unified Access to securely inject credentials into AI agents at runtime — no hardcoded secrets, full audit trail.
- [Databricks Managed MCP Servers Guide: Developer Setup and Unity Catalog Integration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/databricks-mcp-managed-servers-guide-2026/) — Complete developer guide for Databricks managed MCP servers: setup, authentication, Genie/Vector Search/UC Functions integration, and Unity Catalog governance.
- [How to Configure Every AI Coding Assistant 2026: CLAUDE.md, Cursor Rules, Copilot](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/configure-ai-coding-assistants-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to configuring CLAUDE.md, Cursor rules, Copilot instructions, AGENTS.md, and Windsurf in 2026—with comparison tables and best practices.
- [How to Build an MCP Server with Python 2026: Step-by-Step Tutorial](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/build-mcp-server-python-2026/) — Build a production-ready MCP server in Python using FastMCP — from 9-line hello world to Docker, auth, and security hardening.
- [OpenAI Codex CLI Guide 2026: Terminal AI Coding with the Rust-Built Agent](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-cli-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to OpenAI Codex CLI 2026: install the Rust-built terminal agent, configure AGENTS.md, set approval modes, and integrate MCP tools.
- [Windsurf SWE-1 Model Guide 2026: Benchmarks, Speed, and What It Means for Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-swe1-model-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Windsurf SWE-1 models in 2026: benchmarks, SWE-Bench scores, pricing, and how it compares to Cursor, Copilot, and Claude Code.
- [Claude Code Subagents Guide 2026: Parallel Agents for Faster Development](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-subagents-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Claude Code subagents: create custom agents, run parallel workflows, optimize costs with model routing, and ship faster.
- [How to Build an AI Agent from Scratch 2026: Python + LangChain + Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/build-ai-agent-from-scratch-2026/) — Build a production-ready AI agent from scratch using Python, LangGraph, and custom tools — with memory, error handling, and deployment included.
- [AI App Builder Guide 2026: How to Ship an MVP in a Weekend with Vibe Coding Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-app-builder-mvp-guide-2026/) — The definitive 2026 guide to AI app builders — Lovable, Bolt, Replit, v0 compared with a step-by-step weekend MVP playbook.
- [OpenAgents Framework Guide: Build Persistent AI Agent Networks with MCP and A2A Support](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openagents-framework-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to OpenAgents framework — build persistent AI agent networks with native MCP and A2A protocol support in 2026.
- [Google ADK TypeScript Guide: Build AI Agents with the Official TypeScript SDK](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/google-adk-typescript-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to building AI agents with Google ADK TypeScript — installation, tools, multi-agent orchestration, and production deployment.
- [CLAUDE.md Setup Guide 2026: The Config File That Makes Claude Code Actually Useful](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-md-setup-guide-2026/) — Complete CLAUDE.md setup guide for 2026: structure, examples, hierarchy, hooks, and best practices to maximize Claude Code in any project.
- [Windsurf Memories Feature Guide 2026: How to Make Cascade Remember Your Codebase](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-memories-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Windsurf Memories, Rules, and AGENTS.md — make Cascade remember your codebase conventions, preferences, and architecture permanently.
- [How to Set Up Cursor AI in 2026: Complete Beginner's Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-ai-setup-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step Cursor AI setup guide for 2026: install, configure models, master Tab Completion, Composer 2.0, Agent Mode, and .cursorrules in under an hour.
- [Vercel AI SDK Guide 2026: Build Streaming AI Apps in TypeScript With One SDK](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vercel-ai-sdk-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Vercel AI SDK in 2026 — streaming, tool calling, structured output, agents, and production deployment with code examples.
- [Mastra AI Guide 2026: Build TypeScript AI Agents with the Framework That Hit 300K Weekly Downloads](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mastra-ai-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Mastra AI TypeScript framework: install, build agents, add memory, create workflows, and deploy to production.
- [Cursor Background Agents Guide 2026: Run Autonomous Coding Tasks in the Background](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-background-agents-2026/) — Complete guide to Cursor background agents in 2026: setup, pricing, Computer Use, best practices, and when to use them vs Claude Code or Codex.
- [AI Coding Tools for Beginners 2026: The No-Hype Guide to Getting Started](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-tools-beginners-guide-2026/) — Honest guide to the best AI coding tools for beginners in 2026—what they actually do, which are free, and how to start without the hype.
- [GitHub Copilot Agent Mode Guide 2026: Multi-File Edits and Autonomous Tasks](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-copilot-agent-mode-2026/) — Complete guide to GitHub Copilot Agent Mode 2026 — setup, multi-file edits, coding agent, MCP integration, and cost optimization.
- [Claude Code Plan Mode Guide 2026: How to Use Plan Before You Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-plan-mode-guide-2026/) — Master Claude Code Plan Mode: activation, workflows, team adoption, and best practices to prevent AI coding mistakes. 2026 guide
- [LLM Prompt Caching Guide 2026: Cut API Costs 70% with Anthropic and OpenAI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-prompt-caching-guide-2026/) — LLM prompt caching guide 2026: Anthropic, OpenAI, Gemini code examples, cost calculators, anti-patterns, and production monitoring tips.
- [Microsoft Agent Framework 2026: AutoGen Successor Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/microsoft-agent-framework-2026/) — Microsoft Agent Framework replaces AutoGen in 2026 with native Responses API, MCP server integration, and enterprise workflow orchestration patterns.
- [AG2 (AutoGen v0.4) Guide: Event-Driven Multi-Agent Framework for Python Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ag2-autogen-v0-4-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to AG2 (AutoGen v0.4): architecture, ConversableAgent, GroupChat, async messaging, and production best practices for Python developers.
- [Zapier AI Features Guide 2026: Tables, Chatbots, and AI Actions Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/zapier-ai-features-guide-2026/) — Complete Zapier AI guide 2026: AI Actions, Agents, Chatbots, Tables, MCP, pricing, accuracy benchmarks, and cost traps.
- [Cursor Rules Guide 2026: How to Write .cursorrules and .mdc Files for Your Project](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-rules-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to writing Cursor rules in 2026: .cursorrules vs .mdc format, four activation modes, ready-to-use templates, and token budget tips.
- [LLM Coding Workflow Guide 2026: How Top Developers Structure AI-Assisted Development](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-coding-workflow-guide-2026/) — A 5-phase framework for structured AI-assisted coding in 2026: spec-driven planning, context packing, iterative implementation, quality gates, and tooling.
- [Claude Code Hooks Guide 2026: Automate Your Workflow with Shell Triggers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-hooks-guide-2026/) — Complete Claude Code hooks guide: configure shell triggers for auto-formatting, security gates, and CI/CD integration with all 18 hook events.
- [How to Use Claude API in Python 2026: Complete Developer Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-api-python-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step Claude API Python tutorial: install the SDK, send messages, use streaming, tool use, and prompt caching with real code examples.
- [Cursor 3 Guide 2026: Agents Window, Parallel Agents, and Design Mode](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-3-guide-2026/) — Cursor 3 guide: Agents Window, parallel agents, Design Mode, Composer 2 model, and cloud agents for shipping code faster in 2026.
- [AGENTS.md Guide 2026: How to Write AI Agent Instructions for Every Tool](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agents-md-guide-2026/) — AGENTS.md is the open standard for AI agent instructions that cuts agent runtime 28.6% and works across Cursor, Claude Code, Windsurf, and 20+ tools.
- [How to Set Up Windsurf IDE 2026: Installation, Config, and First Project](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-setup-tutorial-2026/) — Complete guide to setup Windsurf IDE 2026 — install on macOS, Windows, or Linux, configure .windsurfrules, and run your first Cascade flow.
- [GitHub Copilot Enterprise Guide 2026: Features, Setup, and ROI for Engineering Teams](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-copilot-enterprise-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to GitHub Copilot Enterprise in 2026: features, setup steps, ROI analysis, and security for engineering teams of all sizes.
- [Claude Code Tutorial 2026: Complete Setup and Workflow Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-tutorial-2026/) — Claude Code 2026 tutorial: installation, setup, memory, skills, hooks, MCP servers, and agentic workflows for autonomous AI coding.
- [Gemini CLI Guide 2026: How to Use Google Gemini from the Terminal](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemini-cli-guide-2026/) — Complete Gemini CLI guide 2026: install, authenticate, and use Google Gemini in your terminal with 1M token context and a generous free tier.
- [Vibe Coding Explained: The Complete Developer Guide for 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vibe-coding-guide-2026/) — The complete vibe coding guide for 2026: tools, workflows, prompts, and best practices for developers and non-technical builders.
- [AI RPA Physical Automation 2026: The Complete Developer Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-rpa-physical-automation-2026/) — AI RPA in 2026: combine agents for cognition with RPA for execution, delivering 2–3× ROI over 3 years versus standalone bots.
- [AI for Customer Support and Helpdesk Automation in 2026: The Complete Developer Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-customer-support-helpdesk-automation-2026/) — AI helpdesk automation cuts support costs, scales instantly, and improves CSAT. Here's how to implement and measure ROI.
- [AI Legal Document Review and Contract Analysis in 2026: Complete Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-legal-document-review-contract-analysis-2026/) — AI legal document review in 2026 cuts manual contract review time by up to 80%, with the market growing to $5.59B—here are the best tools and workflows.
- [Build an AI Test Generator with GPT-5 in 2026: Step-by-Step Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/build-ai-test-generator-gpt5-2026/) — Learn how to build an AI test generator using GPT-5 in 2026. Step-by-step tutorial covering setup, agent config, and CI/CD integration.
- [Best AI Tools for Data Science in 2026: The Complete Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-tools-for-data-science-2026/) — Best AI tools for data science in 2026: TensorFlow, PyTorch, OpenAI API, LangChain, and Vertex AI — how to pick the right stack.
- [How to Build an AI-Powered Chatbot with GPT-5 and RAG in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-powered-chatbot-gpt5-rag-2026/) — Build an AI chatbot with GPT-5 and RAG in 2026: vector databases, LangChain integration, and deployment with step-by-step code.
- [AI in Gaming 2026: Procedural Content Generation and NPC Intelligence Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-in-gaming-2026/) — AI in gaming 2026 is a $4.54B market reshaping how games are built and played, from infinite procedural worlds to NPCs that remember you.
- [AI in Healthcare 2026: How Machine Learning Is Changing Diagnosis and Treatment](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-in-healthcare-2026/) — AI in healthcare 2026 shifts from static algorithms to intelligent agents, transforming diagnosis, treatment, and clinical operations.
- [AI in Education 2026: How Personalized Learning and AI Tutors Are Reshaping Schools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-in-education-2026/) — AI in education 2026: personalized learning, AI tutors, and adaptive classrooms — but human teachers still lead on critical thinking and emotional support.
- [Multimodal AI 2026: GPT-5 vs Gemini 2.5 Flash vs Claude 4 — The Complete Comparison Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/multimodal-ai-2026/) — Compare GPT-5, Gemini 2.5 Flash, Claude 4 &amp; Qwen3 VL. Best multimodal AI 2026 for text, image, audio, video processing. Pricing, features guide.
- [AI in Cybersecurity 2026: How Machine Learning Is Transforming Threat Detection and Defense](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-in-cybersecurity-2026/) — AI in cybersecurity 2026 is a $35-44B market where autonomous AI defends against AI-powered attacks, cutting threat detection by 65%.
- [MCP vs RAG vs AI Agents: How They Work Together in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-vs-rag-vs-ai-agents-2026/) — MCP, RAG, and AI agents solve different problems. MCP connects tools, RAG retrieves knowledge, and agents orchestrate actions. See how they work together.
- [Agentic AI Explained: Why Autonomous AI Agents Are the Biggest Trend of 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agentic-ai-explained-2026/) — Agentic AI in 2026: what autonomous agents are, how they work, and where they're deployed—customer service, fraud detection, supply chains.
- [How to Run AI Models Locally: Ollama vs LM Studio in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ollama-vs-lm-studio-local-ai-2026/) — Ollama vs LM Studio 2026: Ollama for developers (52M monthly downloads), LM Studio for GUI. Both free—most power users run both.
### All Articles
- [Enterprise AI Coding Security Guardrails: Standards and Tools for 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/enterprise-ai-coding-security-guardrails-2026/) — How enterprise teams implement AI coding security guardrails in 2026: OWASP LLM Top 10, NIST AI RMF, key tools, and a step-by-step implementation guide.
- [The AI Productivity Paradox: 75% Use AI Tools but No Measurable Gains](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-productivity-paradox-2026/) — 75% of developers use AI coding tools, yet most orgs see no measurable gains. Here's why — and what the top 20% do differently.
- [JetBrains AI Pulse Survey 2026: 85% of Developers Now Use AI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/jetbrains-ai-pulse-survey-2026/) — JetBrains surveyed 10,000+ developers in Jan 2026: 85-90% use AI, but only 29% trust it. Full breakdown of tool market share, productivity data, and what it means.
- [AI Coding Credits Cost Optimization: Which Tools Are Burning Your Budget in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-credits-cost-optimization-2026/) — A practical guide to cutting AI coding tool costs by 40–70%: credit billing explained, agent mode hidden costs, and optimal toolkits for every budget.
- [Cursor MCP v2.1 Setup: Full Tool Discovery and Server Cards Configuration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-mcp-v2-1-setup-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to setting up MCP servers in Cursor 2.x — Server Cards, tool discovery, mcp.json config, transport selection, and security after CVE-2025-54136.
- [Natural Language Programming in 2026: From Replit to v0 to Bolt.new](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/natural-language-programming-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to natural language programming tools in 2026 — compare Replit, v0, Bolt.new, and Lovable with real use cases, pricing, and security tradeoffs.
- [GitHub Copilot Agentic Code Review: Automated PR Analysis in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-copilot-agentic-code-review-2026/) — GitHub Copilot agentic code review went GA in March 2026. Here's how to enable it, use Fix with Copilot, and decide when human review still wins.
- [AI Coding Tools for Mobile Developers: iOS &amp; Android Workflows in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-for-mobile-developers-2026/) — Which AI coding tools actually work for iOS and Android development in 2026 — covering Xcode integration, Android Studio AI, and cross-platform workflow options.
- [Google ADK vs OpenAI Agents SDK vs Mastra: Agent Framework Showdown 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/google-adk-vs-openai-agents-sdk-vs-mastra-2026/) — Hands-on comparison of Google ADK, OpenAI Agents SDK, and Mastra for building production AI agents in 2026 — with real benchmarks and decision criteria.
- [Superpowers + Claude Code: TDD Workflow Setup Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/superpowers-claude-code-tdd-guide-2026/) — How to set up the Superpowers framework with Claude Code for enforced TDD workflows — with real configuration examples and what changes in practice.
- [Google Agentic Terminal Agent 2026: ReAct Loop + MCP + 1M Context Setup Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/google-agentic-terminal-agent-guide-2026/) — Complete setup guide for Gemini CLI as an agentic terminal agent — ReAct loop internals, MCP server config, and 1M token context window best practices.
- [GitHub Copilot Semantic Code Search: Find Code by Concept, Not Keyword](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-copilot-semantic-code-search-2026/) — GitHub Copilot's semantic code search finds code by meaning, not text. 40% better context recall vs grep, 2% faster task completion—here's how it works.
- [Claude Code Security: Finding 500+ Vulnerabilities with AI in Production Codebases](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-vulnerability-detection-guide-2026/) — How to configure Claude Code to find 500+ vulnerabilities in production codebases using Semgrep MCP, GitGuardian hooks, and DryRun Security policies.
- [Linux Foundation Agentic AI Foundation (AAIF): MCP + A2A Governance Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/linux-foundation-agentic-ai-foundation-2026/) — The Linux Foundation's Agentic AI Foundation (AAIF) brings MCP, goose, and AGENTS.md under neutral governance. Here's what it means for developers.
- [Composio Agent Orchestrator: Parallel Coding Agents for CI and PR Reviews](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/composio-agent-orchestrator-guide-2026/) — Composio Agent Orchestrator review 2026: run 5+ parallel coding agents, automate CI fixes, handle full PR lifecycle, and compare with OpenAI Symphony and T3 Code.
- [GitHub Agent HQ Guide 2026: Run Claude, Copilot, and Codex from One Interface](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-agent-hq-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to GitHub Agent HQ: assign issues to Claude, Copilot, and Codex from a single interface, compare PRs, and optimize agent selection for every task type.
- [Qwen 3.6 Plus Agentic Coding Guide: 1M Context Window for Complex Tasks](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qwen-3-6-plus-agentic-coding-2026/) — Qwen 3.6 Plus: Alibaba's 1M-context agentic coding model with Terminal-Bench 2.0 #1 ranking, always-on CoT, and 13x cheaper output than Claude Opus 4.7.
- [MCP v2.1 Server Cards: Auto-Discovery for AI Agent Tool Registries (2026 Guide)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-v2-1-server-cards-guide-2026/) — How to implement MCP v2.1 Server Cards and .well-known/mcp.json for automatic AI agent tool discovery — with Python and Node.js examples.
- [LLM Gateway Comparison 2026: Portkey vs Helicone vs LiteLLM After the Shakeup](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-gateway-comparison-2026/) — Helicone was acquired and LiteLLM was compromised in 2026. Here's how Portkey, LiteLLM, Helicone, and emerging alternatives compare for routing, cost, and reliability.
- [llama-stack vs Ollama vs vLLM: Which Local LLM Stack Should You Use in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llama-stack-vs-ollama-vs-vllm-2026/) — llama-stack, Ollama, vLLM 비교: 각 도구의 역할과 2026년 최적의 로컬 LLM 스택 조합을 실제 벤치마크와 함께 설명합니다.
- [Nous Hermes Agent v0.8.0 Review: Open-Source Alternative to Claude Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/nous-hermes-agent-review-2026/) — Nous Hermes Agent v0.8.0 reached 140K GitHub stars in under 3 months. This review covers GEPA self-improvement, real coding performance, security trade-offs, and who should switch from Claude Code.
- [GitHub Trending AI Projects April 2026: What's Worth Watching](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-trending-ai-projects-april-2026/) — Five GitHub trending AI projects from April 2026 that are actually worth your time — Superpowers, llama-stack, Google ADK, MemPalace, and Archon.
- [From Copilot to Agent: How to Rethink Your AI Coding Workflow in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/copilot-to-agent-workflow-shift-2026/) — How senior developers are shifting from Copilot autocomplete to full agentic workflows — with practical frameworks for making the transition in 2026.
- [AI Coding in the Terminal vs IDE: Which Workflow Is Right for You in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-terminal-vs-ide-2026/) — Terminal agents vs IDE assistants: a 2026 breakdown of Claude Code vs Cursor, productivity data, and how to pick the right AI coding workflow.
- [Free AI Coding Tools 2026: What Actually Saves Developer Time (Tested)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/free-ai-coding-tools-comparison-2026/) — Tested 8 free AI coding tools in 2026. See which ones actually save developer time, free tier limits, and real productivity numbers.
- [Windsurf vs Claude Code vs Cursor: Full Developer Workflow Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-vs-claude-code-vs-cursor-workflow-2026/) — Cursor, Windsurf, Claude Code 세 가지 AI 코딩 도구를 실제 워크플로우 기준으로 비교 — 벤치마크, 가격, 에이전트 기능 완전 분석.
- [AI Coding Tools Market Share 2026: Real Adoption Data from 12,000+ Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-market-share-adoption-2026/) — Real market share data from 12,000+ developers: GitHub Copilot vs Cursor vs Claude Code adoption, revenue, and productivity stats for 2026.
- [The Composable AI Coding Stack: Using Cursor, Claude Code, and Codex Together (2026 Guide)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/composable-ai-coding-stack-cursor-claude-codex-2026/) — How to combine Cursor, Claude Code, and OpenAI Codex into one composable AI coding stack that multiplies developer output without tool sprawl.
- [JetBrains AI Coding Tools Survey 2026: What Developers Actually Use at Work](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/jetbrains-ai-coding-survey-2026/) — JetBrains AI Pulse January 2026 survey of 10,000+ developers: GitHub Copilot at 29%, Claude Code and Cursor tied at 18%, and Claude Code's 6x growth story explained.
- [OpenHarness: Universal Agent Harness for Any LLM (2026 Review)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openharness-universal-agent-harness-2026/) — OpenHarness is an open-source universal agent harness supporting Claude, GPT, Gemini, Ollama and any LLM under a single CLI runtime.
- [llama-stack: Meta's Unified Deployment Stack for Llama 4 Models](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llama-stack-deployment-guide-2026/) — Complete llama-stack tutorial for 2026: install, configure providers, build RAG pipelines, run agentic workflows, and add enterprise safety with PromptGuard.
- [Archon AI Benchmark: Open-Source Harness Builder for Reproducible AI Coding](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/archon-ai-benchmark-tool-2026/) — Archon is the open-source YAML workflow harness that lifts AI coding PR acceptance from 6.7% to 70% — a 10x improvement with the same LLM.
- [MemPalace Review 2026: The Highest-Scoring Free AI Memory System for Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mempalace-ai-memory-system-2026/) — MemPalace scored 96.6% on LongMemEval — the best free AI memory framework of 2026. Here's what works, what doesn't, and how to set it up.
- [AI Tools for Data Engineering 2026: dbt, Spark, and Airflow with AI Assistance](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-for-data-engineering-2026/) — How AI copilots, agents, and the dbt+Spark+Airflow stack are transforming data engineering productivity in 2026.
- [AI Agent Observability with OpenTelemetry: From Dev to Production in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-agent-observability-opentelemetry-2026/) — Complete guide to instrumenting AI agents with OpenTelemetry GenAI semantic conventions — from local Jaeger to production Grafana Cloud in 2026.
- [LLM Cost Reduction: 10 Strategies That Cut AI API Bills by 70% in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-cost-reduction-strategies-2026/) — 10 proven LLM cost reduction strategies that stack together to cut AI API bills by 70% or more in 2026—model routing, caching, batching, and more.
- [ReAct Agent Pattern: The Complete Developer Implementation Guide for 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/react-agent-pattern-guide-2026/) — Build production-ready ReAct agents from scratch in Python, then scale with LangGraph. Covers the Thought→Action→Observation loop, pitfalls, security, and Reflexion upgrade.
- [OpenAI Codex Plugins Guide: 90+ Enterprise AI Workflow Integrations (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-plugins-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to OpenAI Codex's 90+ plugins for enterprise teams — categories, governance, CLI setup, custom development, and competitor comparison.
- [Mem0 vs Zep in Production: Choosing the Right AI Agent Memory Framework](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mem0-vs-zep-production-guide-2026/) — Mem0 vs Zep compared on benchmarks, pricing, architecture, and self-hosting so you can pick the right AI agent memory framework for production.
- [GitHub Model Selection Guide: Choosing Claude vs Codex for GitHub Coding Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-model-selection-coding-agents-2026/) — A practical guide to choosing between Claude and Codex models for GitHub coding agents — with benchmarks, cost breakdown, and task-based decision matrix.
- [DryRun Security Review 2026: AI SAST Built for Agentic Coding Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/dryrun-security-ai-sast-review-2026/) — DryRun Security review: how its Contextual Security Analysis engine catches 88% of vulnerabilities that pattern-matching tools like Snyk and Semgrep miss.
- [OpenAI Codex Multi-Agent Enterprise Guide: Plugins, Persistent Memory &amp; Multi-Day Workflows (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/codex-multi-agent-enterprise-2026/) — OpenAI Codex's 2026 multi-agent update ships 90+ enterprise plugins, persistent memory, and multi-day autonomous workflows. Here's what actually matters for teams.
- [Multi-Agent System Design: Architecture Patterns for Production AI in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/multi-agent-system-design-guide-2026/) — A practitioner's guide to multi-agent system design patterns in 2026, covering foundational architectures, framework selection, cost engineering, and observability.
- [Azure Bicep IaC ARM Template Alternative Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/azure-bicep-iac-arm-template-alternative-developer-guide-2026/) — Azure Bicep이 ARM JSON 템플릿을 대체하는 이유와 마이그레이션, 모듈, CI/CD 통합 방법을 다루는 완전한 개발자 가이드.
- [OpenTofu vs Terraform Migration Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/opentofu-vs-terraform-migration-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete developer guide to migrating from Terraform to OpenTofu in 2026: license comparison, step-by-step migration, CI/CD updates, and decision framework.
- [React Testing Library AI Component Integration Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/react-testing-library-ai-component-integration-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to testing AI-powered React components in 2026 using RTL, Vitest, MSW, and Vercel AI SDK mock helpers.
- [ts-jest TypeScript Unit Testing Jest Integration Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ts-jest-typescript-unit-testing-jest-integration-guide-2026/) — Complete ts-jest setup guide for Jest 30 and TypeScript 5 in 2026: installation, configuration, ESM, monorepo, and common errors fixed.
- [Claude Sonnet 5 vs GPT-5.4 for Coding: SWE-bench Benchmark Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-sonnet-5-vs-gpt-5-4-coding-2026/) — Claude Sonnet 5 scores 82.1% vs GPT-5.4's 57.7% on SWE-bench Pro. Here's what the gap means for developers choosing an AI coding tool in 2026.
- [YOLOX Object Detection Python Deployment Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/yolox-object-detection-python-deployment-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to deploying YOLOX object detection in Python: training, ONNX/TensorRT export, FastAPI Docker API, and production benchmarks.
- [MiniGPT-4 vs LLaVA-1.5 Multimodal Fine-Tune Benchmark 2026: Developer's Definitive Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/minigpt-4-vs-llava-1-5-multimodal-fine-tune-benchmark-2026/) — LLaVA-1.5 wins on every major benchmark, but MiniGPT-4's architecture still matters for spatial tasks. Here's which to fine-tune in 2026.
- [Arize Phoenix Guide: Open-Source LLM Observability for Developers (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/arize-phoenix-observability-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to Arize Phoenix: install, instrument LLM apps, trace RAG pipelines, and run evals — all open-source, zero vendor lock-in.
- [Claude Sonnet 5 Review: 82.1% SWE-bench, Dev Team Mode &amp; Pricing Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-sonnet-5-review-2026/) — Claude Sonnet 5 hits 82.1% SWE-bench Verified, introduces Dev Team multi-agent mode, and costs $3/MTok. Full developer review with pricing and migration guide.
- [OpenAI Codex Skills Guide: Reusable Agent Behaviors for Developer Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-skills-guide-2026/) — Master OpenAI Codex Skills — the reusable agent behavior system that encodes workflows once and deploys them indefinitely across dev teams.
- [Claude Mythos Cybersecurity Guide 2026: Zero-Day Detection and Project Glasswing Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-mythos-cybersecurity-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Claude Mythos cybersecurity capabilities, zero-day vulnerability detection, and how to access Project Glasswing in 2026.
- [Google ADK vs LangGraph vs Mastra 2026: Choosing the Right Agent Framework](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/google-adk-vs-langgraph-vs-mastra-2026/) — Google ADK, LangGraph, and Mastra compared on benchmarks, production adoption, developer experience, and use cases for 2026.
- [How Cursor Hit $2B ARR: Product Decisions That Shaped AI IDE Dominance](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-2b-revenue-analysis-2026/) — Cursor reached $2B ARR in February 2026 — the fastest SaaS growth in history. Here are the specific product decisions that made it happen.
- [OpenAI Codex Desktop Guide 2026: Full Agentic IDE Workflows and GPT-5-Codex](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-desktop-guide-2026/) — OpenAI Codex Desktop 설치부터 병렬 에이전트, AGENTS.md 설정, GitHub PR 자동화까지 — 2026년 완전 가이드.
- [Langfuse Acquired by ClickHouse: What It Means for Open-Source LLM Observability](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langfuse-clickhouse-acquisition-2026/) — ClickHouse acquired Langfuse in January 2026 alongside a $400M Series D. Here's what changes — and what stays the same — for developers.
- [AI Developer Productivity Metrics 2026: Real Data From TELUS, Zapier, and Stripe](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-developer-productivity-metrics-2026/) — Real 2026 data on AI developer productivity from TELUS (30% faster shipping), Stripe (1,300 AI PRs/week), and Zapier (89% AI adoption).
- [Comet Opik Review 2026: Open-Source LLM Evaluation and Observability Platform](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/comet-opik-review-2026/) — In-depth review of Comet Opik: open-source LLM tracing, evaluation, and agent optimization with self-hosting support and 40M+ daily traces.
- [Confident AI Review: LLM Evaluation Platform With 50+ Research-Backed Metrics](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/confident-ai-review-2026/) — Honest Confident AI review covering DeepEval integration, 50+ metrics, pricing, red teaming, and how it compares to Braintrust and LangSmith in 2026.
- [LangWatch Review 2026: LLM and Agent Application Monitoring Platform](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langwatch-review-2026/) — LangWatch 2026 review: features, pricing, and competitor analysis for the open-source LLM monitoring, agent simulation, and evaluation platform.
- [Agentic Engineering: The Developer Guide Beyond Vibe Coding](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agentic-engineering-guide-2026/) — 92% of developers now use vibe coding, yet 63% waste more time debugging AI-generated code than writing it. This guide covers the practices, tools, and workflow of agentic engineering for production-ready development.
- [Helicone Alternatives 2026: Best LLM Observability Tools After the Mintlify Acquisition](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/helicone-alternatives-2026/) — Helicone was acquired by Mintlify in March 2026 and is now in maintenance mode. Here are the best alternatives: Langfuse, LangSmith, Portkey, Braintrust, and Stockyard compared.
- [OpenObserve LLM Monitoring Guide 2026: Open-Source Observability for AI Applications](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openobserve-llm-monitoring-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to OpenObserve LLM monitoring in 2026: setup, integrations, cost tracking, and comparison with Helicone, LangSmith, and Portkey.
- [The Graduate AI Coding Workflow: Prototype in Bolt/Lovable, Ship in Cursor/Claude Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/graduate-workflow-ai-coding-2026/) — The smartest developers in 2026 use two separate AI tool layers — fast prototyping in Bolt or Lovable, then production-grade shipping in Cursor or Claude Code. Here's the full playbook.
- [TrueFoundry Review 2026: MLOps and LLMOps Platform for Enterprise AI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/truefoundry-review-2026/) — TrueFoundry 2026 review: MLOps + LLMOps platform with AI Gateway, MCP Gateway, Agent Gateway, and Skills Registry. Performance benchmarks, pricing, and comparison with Sagemaker and Portkey.
- [Vibe Coding vs Agentic Engineering: Which Workflow Is Right for You?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vibe-coding-vs-agentic-engineering-2026/) — Vibe coding and agentic engineering both use AI, but the oversight model is completely different. Here's how to choose the right workflow for your situation.
- [OpenAI Codex Security Review 2026: Autonomous AI Security Researcher Agent](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-security-review-2026/) — An in-depth review of OpenAI Codex Security—how it scanned 1.2M commits, found 14 CVEs, and why it deliberately ditched traditional SAST.
- [Cisco AI Defense Review 2026: Security for AI Agents and LLM Applications](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cisco-ai-defense-review-2026/) — Hands-on review of Cisco AI Defense 2026: Zero Trust for AI agents, MCP protocol security, free Explorer Edition, and how it stacks up against Lakera and Palo Alto.
- [Microsoft Agent Governance Toolkit: Open-Source Runtime Security for AI Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/microsoft-agent-governance-toolkit-2026/) — Microsoft's Agent Governance Toolkit is the first open-source framework covering all 10 OWASP Agentic AI risks with sub-5ms deterministic policy enforcement at runtime.
- [GPT-5 Turbo Review 2026: Native Image+Audio, Better JSON, April 7 Release](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-turbo-review-2026/) — GPT-5 Turbo (GPT-5.4 mini) delivers native image+audio, strict JSON outputs, and 2x faster inference at $0.15/M tokens — here's the developer verdict for 2026.
- [Z.ai API Developer Guide 2026: GLM Models, Pricing, and Setup](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/z-ai-api-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete Z.ai API guide: GLM model lineup, Coding Plan pricing, OpenAI/Anthropic-compatible endpoints, and step-by-step Claude Code setup.
- [GLM-5.1 Review 2026: #1 SWE-bench Pro, MIT License, $1/M Tokens](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/glm-5-1-review-2026/) — GLM-5.1 is the first open-weight model to top SWE-Bench Pro at 58.4, beating GPT-5.4 and Claude Opus 4.6 — for $1.40/M input tokens under an MIT license.
- [GLM-5.1 vs Claude vs GPT-6: Open-Source Model That Beats Frontier Models](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/glm-5-1-vs-claude-gpt-2026/) — GLM-5.1 scored 58.4 on SWE-Bench Pro—beating GPT-5.4 and Claude Opus 4.6—at 5–10x lower API cost. Here's what the benchmarks actually mean.
- [AI Agent Governance Guide 2026: Compliance, Access Control, and Runtime Security](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-agent-governance-guide-2026/) — The AI governance market hits $9.2B by 2026. Build compliant AI agent governance with RBAC, audit trails, zero-trust, and EU AI Act mapping — practical guide for 2026.
- [AI Agent Security Tools 2026: Protecting Autonomous Agents in Production](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-agent-security-tools-2026/) — The complete guide to AI agent security tools in 2026 — covering runtime monitoring, prompt injection detection, RBAC, audit trails, and sandboxing for autonomous agents.
- [AWS Frontier Agents Review 2026: AI-Powered Security Testing and DevOps](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/aws-frontier-agents-review-2026/) — A deep review of AWS Frontier Agents GA — the AWS Security Agent and AWS DevOps Agent — covering architecture, benchmarks, competitive positioning, and a step-by-step deployment guide.
- [Microsoft Agent Framework 1.0: Build Production AI Agents in .NET and Python](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/microsoft-agent-framework-1-0-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Microsoft Agent Framework 1.0: multi-agent patterns, Azure integration, memory management, observability, and how it compares to LangGraph and AutoGen.
- [Blink.new Review 2026: The Best Vibe Coding Platform for Startup Founders?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/blink-new-review-2026/) — Honest Blink.new review for 2026: features, pricing, real test results, and how it compares to Bolt.new and Lovable for non-technical founders.
- [Emergent vs Bolt vs Lovable 2026: Best AI Vibe Coding App Builder](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/emergent-vs-bolt-vs-lovable-2026/) — Emergent vs Bolt vs Lovable 2026 — a hands-on breakdown of pricing, features, code quality, and which AI vibe coding tool is right for your project.
- [Mastra vs Agno vs Strands 2026: TypeScript vs Python AI Agent Framework Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mastra-vs-agno-vs-strands-2026/) — Mastra (TypeScript), Agno (Python performance), and Strands (AWS-native) compared on speed, DX, and production fit for 2026 teams.
- [Lovable vs Bubble 2026: AI-Native App Builder vs No-Code Platform](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/lovable-vs-bubble-2026/) — Lovable vs Bubble compared for 2026: AI chat interface vs visual drag-and-drop, pricing, code ownership, and which tool fits your project.
- [Best LLM for AI Agents 2026: GPT-5.5 vs Claude Opus 4.7 vs Gemini 3.1 Pro on Tool Use and Reasoning](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-llm-for-agents-2026/) — Which LLM is best for AI agents in 2026? Benchmark-by-benchmark comparison of GPT-5.5, Claude Opus 4.7, and Gemini 3.1 Pro on tool use, reasoning, and coding.
- [Claude Mythos vs GPT-6 2026: Frontier Model Showdown for Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-mythos-vs-gpt-6-2026/) — Claude Mythos scores 93.9% on SWE-bench vs GPT-5.5's 88.7%, but access and price flip the equation. Which model wins for your dev team?
- [GPT-6 vs Claude Opus 4.7 vs Gemini 3.1: Developer Benchmark Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-6-vs-claude-opus-4-7-vs-gemini-3-2026/) — GPT-6 is not out yet—here's how Claude Opus 4.7 and Gemini 3.1 Pro stack up against GPT-5.5, and what GPT-6 will change for developers.
- [Aikido Security Review 2026: All-in-One AppSec Platform for Developer Teams](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/aikido-security-review-2026/) — Aikido Security consolidates 16 scanners into one flat-rate platform trusted by 50,000+ organizations — here's how it holds up in 2026.
- [Best Claude Code Alternatives 2026: 9 Terminal and IDE AI Agents Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-alternatives-2026/) — The 9 best Claude Code alternatives in 2026 — from free terminal agents like Gemini CLI and Aider to IDE powerhouses like Cursor and Windsurf.
- [Windsurf Browser Cascade Guide 2026: How Cascade Reads Your Browser Context](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-browser-guide-2026/) — How Windsurf's Cascade engine reads browser context—previews, @web, MCP tools, and the full context assembly pipeline explained.
- [AI Coding Tools Adoption 2026: JetBrains Survey, GitHub Stats, Real Developer Data](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-tools-adoption-2026/) — JetBrains surveyed 24,534 developers in January 2026: 90% now regularly use at least one AI tool at work. Full breakdown of adoption rates, market share, productivity data, and the trust crisis.
- [AI Developer Cost Optimization 2026: Token Budgets, Caching &amp; Multi-Model Routing](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-developer-cost-optimization-2026/) — Enterprise token costs dropped 67% in 2025-2026 through multi-model routing, prompt caching, and token budgets. Here are the 9 strategies cutting real LLM spend in 2026.
- [Aikido Security vs Veracode 2026: Startup AppSec vs Enterprise SAST Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/aikido-vs-veracode-2026/) — Aikido Security raised $60M at a $1B valuation and now competes directly with Veracode's enterprise SAST. Here's how they compare on speed, coverage, pricing, and compliance in 2026.
- [Best Cline Alternatives 2026: 10 Open-Source VS Code AI Coding Agents Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cline-alternatives-2026/) — A comprehensive comparison of the 10 best Cline alternatives in 2026 — from Kilo Code and Aider to Continue.dev and OpenCode — with a decision matrix for every use case.
- [Kilo Code Review 2026: Cline Fork with Orchestrator Mode and Inline Autocomplete](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/kilo-code-review-2026/) — A thorough 2026 review of Kilo Code: the Roo Code successor with 1.5M users, Orchestrator Mode for multi-agent workflows, Memory Bank, inline autocomplete, JetBrains support, and a full comparison against Cline and Roo Code.
- [DeepEval Tutorial 2026: Pytest-Native LLM Evaluation for Production AI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/deepeval-tutorial-2026/) — Step-by-step DeepEval tutorial covering pytest-native LLM testing, RAG metrics, G-Eval, agent evaluation, and CI/CD integration in 2026.
- [Agentic Workflow Context Management 2026: Persistent Memory for AI Coding Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agentic-workflow-context-management-2026/) — How AI coding agents solve the stateless memory problem in 2026: CLAUDE.md, Mem0, Zep, Letta, and context compaction strategies compared.
- [AI Agent Testing Guide 2026: Practical Evaluation Framework for Multi-Step Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-agent-testing-guide-2026/) — A practical 2026 guide to evaluating multi-step AI agents — from golden datasets and trajectory metrics to CI/CD gates and production monitoring.
- [AI Agent Observability 2026: Braintrust vs Arize Phoenix vs Langfuse Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-agent-observability-tools-2026/) — Braintrust, Arize Phoenix, and Langfuse compared on tracing depth, evaluation capabilities, pricing, and self-hosting for production AI agents in 2026.
- [DeepEval vs Braintrust vs PromptFoo: LLM Evaluation Tools Compared 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/deepeval-vs-braintrust-vs-promptfoo-2026/) — An in-depth comparison of DeepEval, Braintrust, and PromptFoo across features, pricing, and use cases to help you pick the right LLM evaluation tool for your team in 2026.
- [Codegen (ClickUp) AI Coding Agent Review 2026: Orchestration for Enterprise Teams](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/codegen-clickup-review-2026/) — Honest 2026 review of Codegen's AI coding agent after ClickUp acquisition: parallel agents, SOC 2 compliance, enterprise pricing, and how it compares to Devin and Copilot.
- [Braintrust Review 2026: AI Observability, Evals &amp; Production Monitoring](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/braintrust-review-2026/) — An honest Braintrust review for 2026: pricing, features, Brainstore performance, and how it compares to LangSmith and Langfuse.
- [Cursor Rules Advanced Guide 2026: Framework-Specific Configs &amp; .mdc Best Practices](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-rules-advanced-2026/) — Master Cursor rules advanced configuration in 2026: .mdc frontmatter, four activation modes, framework templates for React/Next.js/FastAPI, and token optimization.
- [Best Open-Source AI Coding Agents 2026: Cline vs Roo vs Kilo vs Aider Ranked](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/open-source-ai-coding-agents-2026/) — Cline, Roo Code, Kilo Code, and Aider ranked by architecture, cost, git integration, and MCP support — find the right open-source AI coding agent for 2026.
- [Cursor Agent Best Practices 2026: Multi-File Edits, Parallel Agents &amp; Rules](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-agent-best-practices-2026/) — Master Cursor agent mode in 2026: parallel agents with git worktrees, .mdc rules migration, multi-file prompts, and the Planner-Worker-Judge architecture.
- [Windsurf Wave 10 Planning Mode Guide: Browser-Aware Cascade &amp; plan.md Workflow](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-wave-10-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Windsurf Wave 10: Planning Mode, browser-aware Cascade, plan.md workflow, and o3 pricing changes for developers.
- [Daytona Review 2026: Sub-90ms AI Agent Code Execution Infrastructure](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/daytona-review-2026/) — Hands-on Daytona review: sub-90ms cold starts, open-source self-hosting, LangChain/Claude integration, and head-to-head comparison with E2B and Modal.
- [ZenML Guide 2026: Production MLOps Pipelines Without the Lock-In](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/zenml-mlops-pipeline-guide-2026/) — Complete ZenML guide 2026: build production MLOps pipelines with @step/@pipeline decorators, swap infra without rewrites, and avoid vendor lock-in.
- [Faros AI Review 2026: Measure the Real ROI of AI Coding Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/faros-ai-coding-analytics-guide-2026/) — Faros AI review 2026: how the engineering intelligence platform measures real ROI from AI coding tools across 22,000 developers.
- [Gemma 4 On-Device Deployment Guide: Run Google's Open Model Locally](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemma-4-on-device-guide-2026/) — Run Gemma 4 locally with Ollama, LM Studio, or llama.cpp. Hardware requirements, quantization guide, mobile deployment, and fine-tuning with QLoRA.
- [OpenAI Agent Builder No-Code Guide: Build AI Agents Without the SDK](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-agent-builder-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to building production AI agents with OpenAI Agent Builder — no SDK, no Python, no engineering team required.
- [Best MCP Servers for Developers in 2026: Top 15 to Install Now](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-mcp-servers-for-developers-2026/) — The 15 best MCP servers for developers in 2026—curated by category, with security tips and starter stack recommendations.
- [MCP Security Guide 2026: Risks, Prompt Injection and Safe Deployment](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-security-guide-2026/) — A developer's practical guide to MCP security risks in 2026: prompt injection, tool poisoning, rug pull attacks, and a 20-point production checklist.
- [Langflow vs n8n vs Dify: Which AI Workflow Tool Should Developers Choose?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langflow-vs-n8n-vs-dify-2026/) — A direct comparison of Langflow, n8n, and Dify for production AI workflows in 2026. Use-case-driven guide to picking the right tool.
- [Amp vs Claude Code vs GitHub Copilot: Agentic Coding Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/amp-vs-claude-code-vs-copilot-2026/) — Amp vs Claude Code vs GitHub Copilot compared head-to-head: benchmarks, pricing, context windows, and which tool fits your 2026 workflow.
- [n8n Tutorial for Beginners 2026: Build Your First AI Workflow](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/n8n-beginner-tutorial-2026/) — Step-by-step n8n tutorial for beginners in 2026: set up n8n, build your first AI workflow, and automate real tasks in under 30 minutes.
- [GLM-5 and GLM-5.1 Review: Zhipu AI's Frontier Models for Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/glm-5-developer-review-2026/) — A developer-focused review of GLM-5 and GLM-5.1: benchmarks, pricing, self-hosting options, and when to choose them over GPT-5 or Claude.
- [Pieces for Developers Review 2026: LTM Memory + MCP Integration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/pieces-for-developers-review-2026/) — An honest 2026 review of Pieces for Developers: LTM-2.7 memory engine, MCP server integration, pricing, real drawbacks, and who should actually use it.
- [Blaxel Review 2026: Persistent AI Agent Sandbox with 25ms Resume](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/blaxel-review-2026/) — Blaxel 2026 review: persistent AI agent sandbox with 25ms resume times. See how it compares to E2B, Daytona, and Modal for long-running autonomous agents.
- [E2B vs Daytona vs Blaxel: AI Agent Code Execution Sandbox Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/e2b-vs-daytona-vs-blaxel-2026/) — E2B vs Daytona vs Blaxel: a head-to-head sandbox comparison covering cold starts, state persistence, pricing, and which provider fits which agentic workload in 2026.
- [Langflow vs n8n vs Flowise vs Dify: Full 4-Way AI Builder Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langflow-vs-n8n-vs-flowise-vs-dify-4way-2026/) — Langflow, n8n, Flowise, and Dify compared head-to-head across RAG pipelines, multi-agent systems, business automation, debugging, self-hosting, and production readiness for 2026.
- [LLM Red Teaming Guide 2026: Security Testing for AI Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-red-teaming-guide-2026/)
- [LLM Structured Outputs Guide 2026: JSON Mode, Instructor &amp; Outlines](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-structured-output-guide-2026/) — The complete 2026 guide to LLM structured outputs: why prompt-only JSON fails, Instructor vs Outlines, native APIs from OpenAI/Anthropic/Google, and production reliability patterns.
- [LM Council Benchmarks: The Independent LLM Leaderboard Developers Should Trust](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/lm-council-llm-benchmarks-guide-2026/) — LM Council benchmarks explained: SWE-bench, LiveCodeBench, GPQA Diamond, LMSYS Chatbot Arena, Artificial Analysis, and how to build your own LLM evaluation framework in 2026.
- [OpenAI Acquires PromptFoo: What It Means for AI Security Testing in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-promptfoo-acquisition-2026/) — OpenAI acquired PromptFoo, the 21,151-star open-source LLM security testing tool. Here's what changes for developers, what stays the same, and what the deal signals for AI security in 2026.
- [Continue CLI Guide: Async Cloud Agents for Developers (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/continue-cli-cloud-agents-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Continue CLI (cn) for async cloud agents — install, config.yaml, headless mode, GitHub Actions, and parallel agent execution.
- [Google ADK Tutorial: Build Multi-Agent Systems with Python (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/google-adk-python-tutorial-2026/) — Step-by-step Google ADK tutorial: install google-adk, build LlmAgent pipelines, run parallel agents, and deploy to Vertex AI in 2026.
- [Base44 Review 2026: The AI App Builder for Non-Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/base44-review-2026/) — Hands-on Base44 review 2026: pricing, features, Wix acquisition impact, and how it compares to Bolt.new and Lovable for non-developers.
- [Claude Code Max Plan Guide: Is the $100/month Worth It?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-max-plan-guide-2026/) — Claude Code Max plan explained: 5x vs 20x tiers, real token math, API billing comparison, and which developer profiles should upgrade.
- [AI-Generated Code Quality Risks: What 61% of Developers Know in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-code-quality-risks-2026/) — 61% of developers say AI-generated code looks correct but isn't reliable. Here's the complete breakdown of risks, stats, and mitigation strategies.
- [Cursor vs Windsurf vs Claude Code Pricing: Full 2026 Comparison](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-vs-windsurf-vs-claude-code-pricing-2026/) — All three tools converged at $20/month Pro in 2026. Here is what actually separates them — token efficiency, hidden agent costs, and where your money goes.
- [Windsurf Pricing 2026: Plans, Credits and Real Costs Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-pricing-guide-2026/) — Complete breakdown of Windsurf's 2026 pricing: Free, Pro ($20/mo), Max ($200/mo), Teams, Enterprise, and the quota system that replaced credits.
- [Windsurf Wave 13 Guide: Arena Mode, Plan Mode and SWE-1.5 (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-wave-13-arena-mode-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Windsurf Wave 13 and Wave 14 features: SWE-1.5 free model, parallel Git worktree agents, Arena Mode, and Plan Mode.
- [SWE-bench Explained: How to Use Coding Benchmarks to Pick an LLM (2026 Guide)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/swe-bench-coding-benchmarks-guide-2026/) — SWE-bench measures how well LLMs fix real GitHub issues. Learn how to read the leaderboard, spot contaminated scores, and pick the right model for your codebase.
- [Base44 vs Lovable vs Bolt: Which AI App Builder Wins in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/base44-vs-lovable-vs-bolt-2026/) — Base44 vs Lovable vs Bolt.new in-depth comparison for 2026: pricing, stack, code ownership, and which AI app builder fits your use case.
- [Grok 4 vs Claude Opus 4 vs Gemini 2.5 Pro: Best Coding Model Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/grok-4-vs-claude-opus-4-vs-gemini-coding/) — Grok 4, Claude Opus 4, and Gemini 2.5 Pro each lead a different benchmark in 2026. Here's which coding model actually fits your workflow, budget, and stack.
- [Qwen 3.5 Coding Guide: Open-Weight Model That Rivals GPT-5](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qwen-3-5-coding-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Qwen 3.5 Coder: benchmark performance, model sizes, self-hosting hardware requirements, VS Code integration, and cost-performance comparison with GPT-5.
- [Terminal-Bench 2.0 Explained: The New Standard for AI Agent Benchmarks (2026 Guide)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/terminal-bench-2026-guide/) — Terminal-Bench 2.0 evaluates AI agents on real terminal tasks — compiling code, administering systems, running security workflows. Here's how the 2026 leaderboard breaks down and how to use the scores to choose your model.
- [Windsurf vs Cursor for Solo Developers in 2026: Honest Comparison](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-vs-cursor-solo-developers-2026/) — Windsurf and Cursor both cost $20/month in 2026. Here's which AI IDE wins for solo devs based on real workflows, free tier, and agent quality.
- [C3 Code Review 2026: Enterprise AI Coding Platform That Turns Natural Language Into Production Apps](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/c3-code-enterprise-review-2026/) — Hands-on review of C3 Code, C3 AI's enterprise platform that converts natural language prompts into production-grade AI applications.
- [AI Code Security in Agentic Workflows 2026: SAST Tools for Cursor and Claude Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-code-security-agentic-workflows-2026/) — 92% of AI-generated codebases contain critical vulnerabilities. Here's how to secure agentic coding workflows with the right SAST tools in 2026.
- [Qwen 3 32B Local Setup Guide 2026: Run on a 24GB GPU](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qwen-3-32b-local-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to running Qwen3 32B locally on a 24GB GPU using Ollama, llama.cpp, or LM Studio with thinking mode explained.
- [GLM-5V-Turbo Review 2026: Zhipu AI Multimodal Agent Model](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/glm-5v-turbo-review-2026/) — GLM-5V-Turbo is Zhipu AI's native multimodal agent model with 94.8 Design2Code score, 202K context, and $1.20/M input pricing — the full developer review.
- [AI Agent Governance for Enterprise 2026: Regulatory Landscape, Frameworks, and Implementation](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-agent-governance-enterprise-2026/) — 21.3% rise in AI legislation across 75 countries. Govern AI agents for EU AI Act, HIPAA, SOC 2, shadow AI, and five enterprise control dimensions.
- [AI Agents SDK Comparison 2026: Strands vs OpenAI SDK vs Mastra](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-agents-sdk-comparison-2026/) — Side-by-side technical comparison of the three most important AI agent SDKs in 2026 — AWS Strands, OpenAI Agents SDK, and Mastra — covering features, pricing, and which to pick for your use case.
- [AI Coding Agents Enterprise Comparison 2026: Claude Code vs Cursor vs GitHub Copilot](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-agent-comparison-enterprise-2026/) — Enterprise comparison of Claude Code, Cursor, and GitHub Copilot in 2026 — compliance, security, pricing at scale, and deployment requirements.
- [AI Coding CLI Tools Comparison 2026: Claude Code vs Codex vs Gemini CLI vs Junie](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-cli-tools-comparison-2026/) — A direct benchmark comparison of Claude Code, Codex CLI, Gemini CLI, and Junie by accuracy, pricing, context window, and CI/CD integration for 2026.
- [AI Developer Tools Adoption Statistics 2026: The Complete Data](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-developer-tools-statistics-2026/) — 90% of developers now use at least one AI tool at work. Here is the complete 2026 dataset on adoption, market share, productivity impact, trust, ROI, and the benchmark numbers that actually matter.
- [AI for Contract Management &amp; Legal Review 2026: Best Tools for Document Analysis](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-contract-management-legal-review-2026/) — Compare the top AI contract management and legal review tools of 2026—Harvey AI, Ironclad, Spellbook, and more—with pricing, use cases, and ROI data.
- [AI for Healthcare 2026: Clinical NLP, Ambient Scribes, and Medical AI Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-healthcare-clinical-nlp-2026/) — The AI healthcare market hits $45.2B in 2026. Here is what clinical teams need to know about ambient scribes, clinical NLP, medical imaging AI, drug discovery, and compliance.
- [AI for Supply Chain Optimization &amp; Logistics 2026: Forecasting, Routing, and Control Towers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-for-supply-chain-optimization-and-logistics-2026/) — AI supply chain market hits $19.8B in 2026. Learn how ML forecasting, route optimization, and AI control towers cut costs by up to 30%.
- [AI Pair Programming ROI 2026: Real Productivity Metrics from Dev Teams](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-pair-programming-roi-2026/) — Real productivity data from 135,000+ developers on AI pair programming ROI in 2026. Includes the 4:1 enterprise return calculation, what controlled studies actually show, and how to measure true ROI for your team.
- [AI Terminal Coding Tools 2026: Claude Code vs Codex CLI vs Gemini CLI vs OpenCode](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-terminal-coding-tools-comparison-2026/) — A direct comparison of the four leading AI terminal coding agents in 2026: Claude Code, Codex CLI, Gemini CLI, and OpenCode — covering features, benchmarks, pricing, and which tool fits which team.
- [Amp Code Review 2026: Sourcegraph's Autonomous Coding Agent Tested](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/amp-code-review-2026/) — A hands-on review of Amp Code, Sourcegraph's autonomous coding agent. Covers multi-model routing, parallel subagents, Oracle Mode, Amp Tab, pricing, and how it stacks up against Cursor and Claude Code in 2026.
- [Anthropic Enterprise Security 2026: Claude, Data Handling, and Compliance Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/project-glasswing-guide-2026/) — Complete 2026 guide to Anthropic Claude enterprise security: SOC 2 Type II, HIPAA BAA, zero-day retention, GDPR, SSO, and compliance head-to-head.
- [ChatGPT Super App Review 2026: Unified AI Platform with Codex, Atlas, and GPT-6](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/chatgpt-super-app-2026/) — Full review of the ChatGPT Super App 2026: Codex coding agent, Atlas browser automation, GPT-5.5 benchmarks, pricing, and a head-to-head comparison with Claude and Gemini.
- [Claude Code vs Codex CLI vs Gemini CLI 2026: Terminal AI Agents Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-codex-cli-gemini-cli-2026/) — Claude Code, Codex CLI, and Gemini CLI compared on benchmarks, pricing, setup, and real-world performance for 2026.
- [Claude Code Worktrees Guide 2026: Run Parallel Sessions Without Conflicts](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-worktrees-guide-2026/) — A complete guide to running multiple Claude Code sessions simultaneously without file conflicts. Covers the --worktree flag, subagent isolation, real parallel workflow patterns, and lifecycle management.
- [Claude for Enterprise 2026: Security, Compliance, and Deployment Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-cowork-enterprise-security-guide-2026/) — The definitive 2026 guide to Claude Enterprise security architecture: SOC 2 Type II, HIPAA BAAs, GDPR data residency, SSO/SAML, audit logs, and side-by-side compliance comparisons against Microsoft Copilot, OpenAI Enterprise, and Google Gemini.
- [Cline vs Cursor vs GitHub Copilot 2026: VS Code AI Agent Showdown](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cline-vs-cursor-vs-copilot-2026/) — A direct comparison of Cline, Cursor, and GitHub Copilot in 2026: features, pricing, agent capabilities, and which tool fits which developer profile.
- [Cloudflare Agents Week 2026: Dynamic Workers, Sandboxes GA, and Project Think](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cloudflare-agents-week-2026/) — Cloudflare Agents Week 2026 shipped Dynamic Workers GA, Project Think, and Browser Rendering updates — a complete platform for production AI agents.
- [Comp AI Compliance Platform Review 2026: Open-Source Agentic Compliance](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/comp-ai-compliance-platform-guide-2026/) — Comp AI review 2026: open-source agentic compliance platform for SOC 2, HIPAA, ISO 27001, and GDPR—compared to Vanta, Drata, and Secureframe.
- [Cursor 3 vs Google Antigravity 2026: Which AI IDE Wins?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-3-vs-antigravity-2026/) — A direct comparison of Cursor 3 and Google Antigravity in 2026 — covering SWE-bench scores, Agents Window vs Manager View, pricing, context windows, MCP support, and security compliance.
- [Cursor Pro vs Pro Plus: Which Plan Is Right for You in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-pro-vs-pro-plus-2026/) — A direct comparison of Cursor Pro ($20/month) and Cursor Pro Plus ($40/month) covering parallel agents, Design Mode, context windows, enterprise security, and the exact scenarios where the higher tier pays for itself.
- [Cursor vs Windsurf vs Antigravity 2026: Agentic IDE Showdown](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agentic-ide-cursor-windsurf-antigravity-2026/) — A direct comparison of Cursor, Windsurf, and Google Antigravity across benchmarks, pricing, security, and parallel agent capabilities to find the best agentic IDE in 2026.
- [Cursor vs Windsurf vs GitHub Copilot 2026: Best AI Code Editor Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-vs-windsurf-vs-copilot-2026/) — Cursor, Windsurf, and GitHub Copilot compared for 2026 — features, pricing, agent modes, and which tool fits your team.
- [Gemma 4 vs Llama 4 vs Qwen 3: Best Open-Source LLM for Developers 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemma-4-vs-llama-4-vs-qwen-3-2026/) — Gemma 4 vs Llama 4 vs Qwen 3 2026: benchmarks, context windows, licensing, GPU requirements, and which open-source LLM wins for developer use cases.
- [GPT-5.5 Pro API Enterprise Guide: $30 per Million Tokens, Highest Accuracy Tier](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-5-pro-enterprise-api-guide-2026/) — Complete enterprise guide to GPT-5.5 Pro API: $30/M token pricing, reasoning.effort settings, Batch API cost reduction, and benchmark comparisons against Claude Opus 4.7.
- [Gumloop vs n8n vs Zapier 2026: AI-Native Automation Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gumloop-vs-n8n-vs-zapier-2026/) — A direct technical comparison of Gumloop, n8n, and Zapier in 2026 — covering AI architecture, pricing models, integration depth, and which platform actually belongs in your stack.
- [Kimi K2 vs Claude Opus vs GPT-5 Coding 2026: Moonshot's Model Benchmark](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/kimi-k2-vs-claude-vs-gpt5-coding-2026/) — A direct benchmark comparison of Kimi K2.5, Claude Opus 4.6, and GPT-5.3-Codex for coding in 2026. SWE-Bench, Terminal-Bench, LiveCodeBench, and pricing analysis.
- [LangGraph vs CrewAI vs AutoGen 2026: Which AI Agent Framework Should You Use?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langgraph-vs-crewai-vs-autogen-2026/) — LangGraph, CrewAI, and AutoGen compared for 2026. Architecture trade-offs, performance benchmarks, token costs, and a decision guide to pick the right AI agent framework for your project.
- [LLM Observability Tools Comparison 2026: LangSmith vs Langfuse vs Helicone vs Arize](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-observability-tools-comparison-2026/) — Compare LangSmith, Langfuse, Helicone, and Arize AI for LLM observability in 2026—pricing, features, and which tool fits your stack.
- [Mistral Small 4 Review 2026: EU-Compliant, Open-Weight, $0.40/M Input](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mistral-small-4-review-2026/) — Mistral Small 4 is a 119B MoE model unifying reasoning, vision, and coding in a single open-weight release with full GDPR compliance and Apache 2.0 licensing.
- [Modal vs Replicate 2026: Best Serverless ML Deployment for Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/modal-vs-replicate-ml-deployment-2026/) — Modal vs Replicate 2026 compared: cold starts, pricing, throughput, and which serverless ML platform fits your stack.
- [Workato vs Zapier vs n8n 2026: Enterprise Automation Platforms Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/workato-vs-zapier-vs-n8n-2026/) — A direct comparison of Workato, Zapier, n8n, and Make in 2026 — covering pricing, integrations, governance, and which platform fits your team.
- [DAST Tools Comparison 2026: Top 10 AI-Powered Dynamic Security Testing Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/dast-tools-comparison-2026/) — Compare the top 10 AI-powered DAST tools for 2026 — accuracy, CI/CD fit, API coverage, pricing, and which tool best matches your team's needs.
- [Zep AI Review 2026: Temporal Knowledge Graphs for Agent Memory](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/zep-ai-agent-memory-review-2026/) — Zep AI uses temporal knowledge graphs to give agents persistent, relationship-aware memory — outperforming Mem0 by 15 points on LongMemEval.
- [Claude Code /ultrareview Command: What It Does and When to Use It](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-ultrareview-guide-2026/) — A complete guide to /ultrareview in Claude Code — how the Find→Verify pipeline works, cost, modes, and when it pays off over /review.
- [AI Coding Tools SOC 2 Compliance 2026: Enterprise Security Scorecard](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-tools-enterprise-soc2-compliance-2026/) — SOC 2 Type II compliance scorecard for 7 AI coding tools in 2026 — data residency, HIPAA, FedRAMP, zero-retention options compared.
- [AI for Legal Contract Analysis 2026: Tools, Use Cases, and ROI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-legal-contract-analysis-2026/) — AI contract analysis in 2026 cuts review time by 80% and attorney hours by 50-70%—market hits $5.59B. Best tools, ROI data, and implementation guide.
- [AI Risk Management &amp; Fraud Detection 2026: Tools, Methods, and Best Practices](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-fraud-detection-2026/) — AI fraud detection market hits $14.7B in 2025. Compare top tools, methods, and compliance requirements for financial services in 2026.
- [AI Workflow Automation Benchmarks 2026: Real Performance Data Across Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-workflow-automation-benchmarks-2026/) — Real 2026 benchmark data for n8n, Make, and Zapier: throughput, latency, cost at scale, AI step speed, and reliability metrics compared.
- [Best AI Coding Agents 2026: Full Comparison of 7 Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-agents-full-comparison-2026/) — Full comparison of the 7 best AI coding agents in 2026 — benchmarks, pricing, context windows, and which tool fits your workflow.
- [Claude Mythos Preview Guide 2026: What Developers Need to Know](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-mythos-preview-developer-guide-2026/) — Claude Mythos developer preview 2026: 92% SWE-bench Pro, 40% productivity gains, API access, enterprise deployment, and how it compares to Claude Opus 4.7.
- [Enterprise AI Coding Governance 2026: Policy, Compliance, and Shadow AI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/enterprise-ai-coding-governance-2026/) — 78% of enterprises report unauthorized AI coding tool use. Build a five-pillar governance framework covering shadow AI, HIPAA, PCI-DSS, SOC 2, and EU AI Act.
- [Gemini 3.1 Ultra API Developer Guide: 2M Context Window](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemini-3-1-ultra-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete developer guide to Gemini 3.1 Ultra: 2M token context, Python SDK setup, multimodal API, pricing, benchmarks, and Vertex AI enterprise deployment.
- [Goose AI Agent Review 2026: Block's Open-Source Local Coding Agent](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/goose-ai-agent-review-2026/) — Goose AI agent review 2026: Apache 2.0 open-source coding agent, 15+ LLM providers, 70+ MCP extensions, local Ollama support, and comparison to Claude Code and Aider.
- [Junie CLI Review 2026: JetBrains Terminal AI Agent with BYOK Support](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/junie-cli-review-2026/) — Junie CLI reviewed: JetBrains' terminal AI agent with BYOK for Anthropic/OpenAI keys, autonomous tasks, Git awareness, and IDE integration.
- [Lovable Pricing 2026: Credits, Hidden Costs, and Whether the $25/Month Plan Is Worth It](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/lovable-pricing-2026/) — Lovable pricing 2026 explained: credit model, all four tiers, hidden costs, and an honest verdict on the $25/month Pro plan.
- [Mem0 Guide 2026: Add Persistent Memory to Your AI Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mem0-agent-memory-guide-2026/) — Add persistent memory to AI agents with Mem0: architecture, quick start, memory scoping, LangChain integration, pricing, and production best practices.
- [OpenAI o3 vs Claude Sonnet 2026: Reasoning Models for Developers Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-o3-vs-claude-reasoning-2026/) — OpenAI o3 vs Claude Sonnet 4.6 in 2026: benchmarks, pricing, API usage, and which reasoning model wins for your dev workflow.
- [Snyk vs Semgrep 2026: SAST Comparison for AI-Generated Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/snyk-vs-semgrep-comparison-2026/) — Snyk vs Semgrep 2026: accuracy, false positive rates, IDE integration, pricing, and which SAST tool wins for AI-generated code security.
- [Vellum AI Platform Review 2026: Best LLM Evaluation and Testing Tool?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vellum-ai-llm-evaluation-2026/) — Vellum AI 2026 review: prompt management, evaluation pipelines, A/B testing, and production monitoring for LLM teams. Pricing, comparisons, and verdict.
- [What Developers Actually Use: JetBrains AI Tool Survey 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/developer-ai-tool-survey-2026/) — JetBrains' 2026 survey reveals 85% of developers use AI tools regularly. Breakdown by tool, team size, region, and real productivity impact.
- [Windsurf vs Kiro for Enterprise Teams 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-vs-kiro-enterprise-2026/) — Windsurf Cascade Hooks vs Kiro MCP Registry: a deep-dive enterprise comparison covering compliance, data residency, and security architecture.
- [xAI Grok API Pricing 2026: Every Model, Context Window, and Cost Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/xai-grok-api-pricing-2026/) — Full xAI Grok API pricing breakdown for 2026: Grok 4.1 Fast, Grok 4.20, Grok Code Fast 1 — with context windows, cost tables, and competitor comparisons.
- [Claude Opus 4.7 Developer Guide: xhigh Effort, Task Budgets, and Migration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-opus-4-7-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete Claude Opus 4.7 developer guide: xhigh effort levels, task budgets, adaptive thinking, breaking API changes, and migration from Opus 4.6.
- [GLM-4.7 Coding Guide 2026: The Open-Source LLM Beating Claude Sonnet](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/glm-4-7-coding-guide-2026/) — GLM-4.7 scores 73.8% on SWE-bench and 84.9% on LiveCodeBench V6 — matching Claude Sonnet 4.5 at zero API cost. Here's how to set it up and when to use it.
- [Run Gemma 4 Locally in 2026: 31B Dense Setup Guide with Ollama](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemma-4-local-setup-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to running Gemma 4 31B Dense locally with Ollama — hardware requirements, installation, Open WebUI, and API usage.
- [Claude Code Task Budgets Guide 2026: Control Token Spend in Agentic Sessions](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-task-budgets-guide-2026/) — Claude Code task budgets 2026: how to set token spend limits for agentic sessions via API and CLI, avoid cost explosions, and tune budgets for real workloads.
- [Gemma 4 Review 2026: Google's Best Open-Source Model Yet?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemma-4-review-2026/) — Gemma 4 review: benchmarks, model variants, Apache 2.0 license, and how it stacks up against Llama 4, GPT-4, and Claude in 2026.
- [Dify vs Flowise 2026: Which Open-Source AI Workflow Builder Wins?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/dify-vs-flowise-comparison-2026/) — Dify vs Flowise compared for 2026: features, self-hosting requirements, RAG pipelines, pricing, and which to pick for your team.
- [Perplexity Sonar API Guide 2026: Add Real-Time Search to Your App](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/perplexity-sonar-api-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to integrating the Perplexity Sonar API for web-grounded AI responses with citations, streaming, and domain filtering.
- [AI Agent Memory Architecture Guide 2026: Mem0, Zep, LangGraph Store Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agent-memory-architecture-guide-2026/) — AI agent memory architecture guide 2026: Mem0 vs Zep vs Letta vs LangGraph Store — benchmarks, pricing, temporal knowledge graphs, and which framework fits your use case.
- [Claude Code Enterprise vs GitHub Copilot Enterprise 2026: Deep Comparison for Engineering Leaders](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-enterprise-github-copilot-2026/) — Claude Code hits 80.9% SWE-bench vs Copilot's inline-first model. Which enterprise AI coding tool wins for your team in 2026?
- [Cloudflare Project Think Guide 2026: Build Long-Running AI Agents with Durable Execution](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cloudflare-project-think-ai-agents-guide/) — Cloudflare Project Think 2026: build long-running AI agents with durable execution, Fibers, Facets, and Workers infrastructure.
- [Corgea Review 2026: AI-Native SAST That Fixes Vulnerabilities Automatically](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/corgea-ai-sast-review-2026/) — Corgea review 2026: AI-native SAST that auto-generates fix PRs, 80% remediation effort reduction, GitHub/GitLab integration, and how it compares to SonarQube and Semgrep.
- [Cursor 3 Review 2026: Agent-First IDE, Parallel Agents, and Design Mode](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-3-review-2026/) — Cursor 3 review: $29.3B valuation, 8 parallel agents via git worktrees, Design Mode, Glass interface, and 78.2% SWE-bench score.
- [Grok 4 Review 2026: xAI Flagship Model, grok-code-fast, Benchmarks and API](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/grok-4-review-2026/) — Grok 4 review 2026: xAI flagship reasoning model, grok-code-fast coding variant, 2M context window, API setup, and benchmarks vs Claude Opus 4.7 and GPT-5.5.
- [Make vs n8n 2026: Which Open-Source Automation Tool Wins?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/make-vs-n8n-comparison-2026/) — Make vs n8n 2026: operations vs executions billing, 1,500+ connectors vs 400+ nodes, self-hosting, AI features, and which platform fits your team.
- [Windsurf Cascade Deep Dive 2026: How the AI Flow Engine Actually Works](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-cascade-deep-dive-2026/) — How Windsurf Cascade works: RAG-based context tracking, the Memories system, .windsurfrules setup, SWE-1.5, and where it beats Cursor and Copilot.
- [LLM Benchmarks Guide for Developers 2026: SWE-bench, GPQA, LiveCodeBench Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-benchmarks-guide-2026/) — A practical 2026 guide to LLM benchmarks for developers: which ones still signal real performance and which to stop trusting.
- [Neurolink AI Framework Review 2026: One SDK for 12+ LLM Providers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/neurolink-ai-framework-review-2026/) — An honest review of NeuroLink AI framework by Juspay: unified access to 13+ LLM providers, native MCP integration, and enterprise HITL in one TypeScript SDK.
- [How to Cut Claude Code Costs by 70%: Token Limits, Caching, and Budgets](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-cost-optimization-guide-2026/) — Practical techniques to reduce Claude Code token usage by 40-70% using prompt caching, budget enforcement, and smarter context management.
- [MCP Ecosystem 2026: 97 Million Installs, New Governance, and What Comes Next](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-ecosystem-2026/) — The MCP ecosystem hit 97M monthly downloads and 10K+ servers in 2026. Here's what changed, what broke, and where it's going.
- [AutoAgent Framework 2026: Build LLM Agents with Zero Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/autoagent-llm-framework-2026/) — AutoAgent 2026 review: zero-code LLM agent framework, #1 open-source GAIA benchmark, self-play optimization, and how it compares to LangChain, CrewAI, and AutoGen.
- [Gumloop Review 2026: AI-Native Workflow Automation Platform](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gumloop-review-2026/) — Gumloop review 2026: AI-native automation platform, credit pricing, 125+ integrations, $50M Series B, and who should use it vs Zapier and n8n.
- [SonarQube AI CodeFix Review 2026: Is It Worth It for Developer Teams?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/sonarqube-ai-codefix-review-2026/) — SonarQube AI CodeFix review 2026: how it works, pricing tiers, bring-your-own-LLM support, performance vs CodeRabbit, and whether it's worth the Enterprise cost.
- [Taskade AI Agents Review 2026: No-Code Multi-Agent Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/taskade-ai-agents-review-2026/) — Taskade AI agents review 2026: Genesis no-code builder, multi-agent teams, flat-rate pricing, and how it compares to Zapier, Make, and n8n for business automation.
- [OpenAI Agents SDK TypeScript: Complete Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-agents-sdk-typescript-2026/) — Build production-ready AI agents in TypeScript with the OpenAI Agents SDK — handoffs, tools, guardrails, sessions, MCP, and voice agents explained.
- [Best Local LLM Models 2026: Benchmarks, Hardware, and Use Cases](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-local-llm-models-2026/) — The best local LLM models in 2026 ranked by benchmarks, with hardware requirements, runtime tool comparisons, and use case recommendations.
- [AI Browser Agents Comparison 2026: Comet vs Browser-Use vs Operator](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-browser-agents-comparison-2026/) — Comet, Browser-Use, and Operator compared head-to-head on benchmarks, pricing, real-world performance, and enterprise readiness in 2026.
- [Best CodeRabbit Alternatives in 2026: Top AI Code Review Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/coderabbit-alternatives-comparison-2026/) — The 7 best CodeRabbit alternatives in 2026 ranked by accuracy, price, and platform—Qodo Merge, Greptile, BugBot, and more.
- [DeepSeek V4 Review 2026: 50x Cheaper Than GPT-5.4?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/deepseek-v4-review-2026/) — DeepSeek V4-Pro delivers near-frontier coding performance at $1.74/M input tokens — 70-80x cheaper than GPT-5.4 Pro. Here's what that means for developers.
- [Perplexity Comet Browser Review 2026: AI Browser Worth Switching?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/perplexity-comet-browser-review-2026/) — Perplexity Comet browser review 2026: features, privacy risks, CometJacking security flaws, and whether it's worth replacing Chrome.
- [LangGraph TypeScript Guide: Build AI Agents in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langgraph-typescript-guide-2026/) — Complete LangGraph TypeScript guide for 2026: StateGraph, streaming, checkpointing, HITL, and multi-agent systems with real code examples.
- [MCP Streamable HTTP Production Guide 2026: stdio vs Streamable HTTP](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-production-guide-streamable-http-2026/) — Complete guide to choosing and deploying MCP transports in 2026: stdio vs Streamable HTTP, auth, scaling, and platform recipes for Cloudflare, AWS ECS, and Kubernetes.
- [MCP OAuth 2.1 Authentication: Complete Developer Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-oauth-authentication-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to implementing OAuth 2.1 authentication for MCP servers in 2026, covering PKCE, Protected Resource Metadata, and enterprise gateway patterns.
- [AWS Strands Agents SDK: Build Production AI Agents in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/strands-agents-aws-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to AWS Strands Agents SDK — install, build, deploy, and monitor production AI agents with minimal code in 2026.
- [Langflow Review 2026: Visual AI Workflow Builder for LLM Orchestration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langflow-review-2026/) — Langflow review 2026: 100K GitHub stars, MCP server export, RAG pipelines 10x faster — plus honest limits and alternatives.
- [Power Automate vs Zapier vs n8n 2026: Enterprise Automation Showdown](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/power-automate-vs-zapier-vs-n8n-2026/) — Power Automate vs Zapier vs n8n 2026: real pricing numbers, GDPR compliance, AI agent features, and which enterprise automation platform wins for your use case.
- [Cubic.dev Review 2026: The Honest Developer's Take on AI Code Review](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cubic-dev-ai-code-review-2026/) — An honest Cubic.dev review for 2026: benchmarks, pricing, real team results, and when it beats CodeRabbit and GitHub Copilot.
- [AI Workflow Automation Cost Comparison 2026: n8n vs Zapier vs Make at Scale](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-workflow-automation-cost-comparison-2026/) — Real cost math comparing n8n, Zapier, and Make.com for AI workflows at scale — billing models, self-hosting, and where each platform wins.
- [Make.com AI Agents Guide 2026: Build Autonomous Workflows with Maia](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/make-ai-agents-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to building Make.com AI agents with Maia in 2026 — reasoning panel, multimodal inputs, and real-world use cases.
- [Activepieces vs n8n 2026: Open-Source Automation Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/activepieces-vs-n8n-comparison-2026/) — Activepieces vs n8n 2026: pricing model differences, integration counts, self-hosting options, AI agent capabilities, and which open-source automation platform fits your team.
- [n8n MCP Integration Guide 2026: Connect Claude and AI Agents to Your Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/n8n-mcp-integration-guide-2026/) — How to integrate n8n with Model Context Protocol (MCP) in 2026 — set up n8n as an MCP server, connect Claude Desktop, and build workflows without touching the UI.
- [Lindy AI Review 2026: No-Code AI Agent Automation Platform](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/lindy-ai-review-2026/) — Hands-on Lindy AI review covering pricing, features, Gaia voice agent, Autopilot, and how it compares to Zapier, Make, and n8n in 2026.
- [AnythingLLM Review 2026: Local AI Knowledge Base and Agent Runtime](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/anythingllm-review-2026/) — An honest 2026 review of AnythingLLM covering RAG, agent runtime, MCP support, Docker setup, and how it compares to Open WebUI and PrivateGPT.
- [Local AI Agents Guide 2026: Build Offline AI Agents with Ollama and Cline](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/local-ai-agents-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to building offline AI agents with Ollama and Cline in 2026 — privacy-first, zero API costs, works air-gapped.
- [Cursor BugBot Review 2026: AI Security Checks in Every PR](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-bugbot-review-2026/) — Honest Cursor BugBot review: benchmarks, pricing, Autofix, learned rules, and how it stacks up against CodeRabbit and GitHub Copilot.
- [Figma MCP Server Guide 2026: Design to Code with AI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/figma-mcp-design-to-code-2026/) — Complete guide to the Figma MCP server: setup, remote vs desktop, Code Connect, and real-world design-to-code workflows with AI agents in 2026.
- [Sweep AI Review 2026: GitHub Issue to PR Automation — Is It Worth It?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/sweep-ai-review-2026/) — Honest Sweep AI review for 2026: 92% issue resolution rate, GitHub-native workflow, pricing vs Devin, and whether the JetBrains pivot changes the value proposition.
- [OpenAI Codex Computer Use Guide 2026: Background Agents That Operate Your Mac](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-computer-use-guide-2026/) — OpenAI Codex computer use lets background agents operate your Mac autonomously — here's the complete setup guide with security, plugins, and real use cases.
- [GPT-6 Review 2026: OpenAI's New Flagship Model — Benchmarks, API, and Developer Use Cases](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-6-review-2026/) — GPT-6 pre-training is done but not yet released. Here's every confirmed fact, benchmark projection, and API detail developers need to plan ahead.
- [Cursor 2.0 Parallel Agents Guide: Run 8 Simultaneous AI Agents on Your Codebase](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-2-parallel-agents-guide/) — Run up to 8 AI agents simultaneously in Cursor 2.0 using git worktrees. Complete setup guide, /multitask command, background agents, and real-world use cases.
- [Best AI SAST Tools 2026: Snyk vs Semgrep vs Checkmarx vs Corgea Ranked](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-sast-tools-comparison-2026/) — Ranked comparison of the best AI SAST tools in 2026: Snyk Code vs Semgrep vs Checkmarx vs Corgea — accuracy, false positive rates, AI auto-fix, and pricing.
- [Llama 4 API Developer Guide 2026: Scout, Maverick, MoE Architecture and Integration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llama-4-api-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete developer guide to Llama 4 Scout and Maverick APIs: MoE architecture, 10M-token context, pricing, vLLM deployment, and OpenAI-compatible integration.
- [VS Code vs Cursor vs Windsurf vs JetBrains AI 2026: Which IDE Should You Use?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vscode-cursor-windsurf-jetbrains-comparison-2026/) — Cursor leads on speed (72% autocomplete acceptance), Windsurf wins enterprise, VS Code + Copilot is safest. Full 2026 comparison with benchmarks and pricing.
- [Roo Code Review 2026: Open-Source Cline Fork with Multi-Agent Mode](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/roo-code-review-2026/) — Complete Roo Code review covering its multi-agent orchestration, Boomerang Tasks, shutdown, and where to migrate in 2026.
- [Vibe Coding Tools Comparison 2026: Cursor vs Replit vs Bolt vs Lovable vs v0](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vibe-coding-tools-comparison-2026/) — Hands-on comparison of the 5 major vibe coding tools in 2026 — Cursor, Replit, Bolt, Lovable, and v0 — with pricing, use cases, and a decision framework.
- [Cline vs Roo Code 2026: Best Open-Source VS Code AI Agent Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cline-vs-roo-code-2026/) — Cline vs Roo Code compared on architecture, Boomerang Tasks, cost control, and IDE support — find the right open-source VS Code AI agent for 2026.
- [Lovable vs Bolt.new Comparison 2026: Which AI App Builder Is Right for You?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/lovable-vs-bolt-comparison-2026/) — Lovable vs Bolt.new 2026 in-depth comparison: pricing, features, backend capabilities, and which AI app builder fits your use case.
- [AI Code Review Tools 2026: CodeRabbit vs Qodo vs Greptile vs GitHub Copilot](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-code-review-tools-2026/) — Honest comparison of the top AI code review tools in 2026: bug catch rates, noise levels, pricing, and which tool actually fits your team's workflow.
- [Windsurf Arena Mode Guide 2026: Run Two AI Models Side-by-Side on Your Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-arena-mode-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Windsurf Arena Mode: how blind model comparison works, SWE-1.5 vs Claude benchmarks, leaderboard mechanics, and credit cost breakdown.
- [Lovable Review 2026: The $6.6B AI App Builder That Ships Real Products](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/lovable-review-2026/) — Honest Lovable review for 2026: pricing, agent mode, real build tests, and how it compares to Bolt and v0.
- [Windsurf Wave 13 Guide 2026: What's New and How to Use the Latest Features](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-wave-13-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Windsurf Wave 13 'Shipmas Edition': free SWE-1.5 model, true parallel agents with Git worktrees, Arena Mode, Plan Mode, and more.
- [OpenAI Agents SDK v2 Guide 2026: Configurable Memory, Sandbox Orchestration, Filesystem Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-agents-sdk-v2-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to OpenAI Agents SDK v2 (April 2026): configurable memory, apply_patch filesystem tools, 7 sandbox providers, and AGENTS.md workspace config.
- [Cursor + Claude Code + Codex Composable Stack 2026: The New AI Coding Architecture](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-claude-code-codex-stack-2026/) — How to combine Cursor, Claude Code, and OpenAI Codex into a composable AI coding stack — with setup guide, workflow patterns, and pricing breakdown.
- [Anthropic Agentic Coding Trends Report 2026: 8 Trends Reshaping Developer Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/anthropic-agentic-coding-trends-2026/) — Breakdown of Anthropic's 2026 Agentic Coding Trends Report: all 8 trends explained with real-world examples, tool comparisons, and a practical adoption roadmap for engineering teams.
- [Qwen 3 Full Model Lineup Guide 2026: 0.6B to 72B with Dual-Mode Thinking](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qwen-3-full-lineup-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to every Qwen 3 model from 0.6B to 235B — specs, VRAM requirements, dual-mode thinking, benchmarks vs. DeepSeek R1 and GPT-4o.
- [Llama 4 Scout Developer Guide 2026: 10M Token Context Window for Full Codebase Analysis](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llama-4-scout-guide-2026/) — Practical guide to Llama 4 Scout's 10M token context window: API setup, full codebase loading, local deployment with Ollama and vLLM, and real pricing comparisons.
- [JetBrains Air Review 2026: Multi-Agent Development Environment from JetBrains](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/jetbrains-air-review-2026/) — JetBrains Air review 2026: the agentic IDE that orchestrates Codex, Claude, Gemini, and Junie simultaneously — pricing, real-world results, and honest verdict.
- [Context Engineering for AI Coding Agents 2026: Strategies That Actually Work](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/context-engineering-ai-coding-agents-2026/) — Context engineering is the #1 skill separating developers who get 10x gains from AI coding agents from those stuck at 10% productivity.
- [Magistral Review 2026: Mistral Open-Weight Reasoning Model That Beats DeepSeek R1](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/magistral-mistral-reasoning-model-review-2026/) — Magistral is Mistral's first open-weight reasoning model. The 24B Small variant runs locally on a MacBook and scores 73.6% on AIME-24 — beating DeepSeek R1 Zero.
- [GPT-5.4 API Developer Guide 2026: 1M Context, Computer Use, and 5 Reasoning Levels](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-4-api-developer-guide-2026/) — Complete GPT-5.4 API guide: 1M token context, 5 reasoning effort levels, native computer use, pricing tiers, and migration from gpt-4o/gpt-5.2.
- [Devstral Small 2 Local Setup Guide 2026: Run Mistral Coding Agent on Your Laptop](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/devstral-small-2-local-setup-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to running Devstral Small 2 (24B, 68% SWE-bench) locally via Ollama, vLLM, or llama.cpp — zero API fees, full privacy.
- [GPT-5.3 Codex Spark Review 2026: OpenAI Coding Model Benchmarked](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-3-codex-spark-review-2026/) — GPT-5.3 Codex Spark delivers 1,000+ tokens/sec on Cerebras hardware — here's how it benchmarks and when to use it.
- [Claude Opus 4.7 vs 4.6 vs Mythos Comparison 2026: Which Model Should You Use?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-opus-47-vs-46-vs-mythos-comparison-2026/) — Claude Opus 4.7, 4.6, and Mythos compared on benchmarks, real cost, and migration risk — so you pick the right model for your workload.
- [Multi-Model LLM Routing Guide 2026: Cut AI Costs 85% with Smart Routing](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/multi-model-llm-routing-guide-2026/) — Smart LLM routing cuts AI costs up to 85% by directing queries to cheaper models without sacrificing quality. Here's the complete 2026 guide.
- [Cursor 3 Parallel Agents Tutorial 2026: Run Multiple AI Agents Simultaneously](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-3-parallel-agents-tutorial-2026/) — Step-by-step tutorial for running multiple Cursor 3 AI agents simultaneously using the Agents Window, /multitask command, and git worktrees.
- [AI Pair Programming 2026: How to Code 10x Faster with AI Assistance](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-pair-programming-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to AI pair programming in 2026: tool comparisons, productivity strategies, and real ROI data from top developers.
- [Vibe Coding Explained: The Complete Developer Guide for 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vibe-coding-explained-the-complete-developer-guide-for-2026/) — Vibe coding lets developers build software by describing intent in natural language and letting AI write the code — here's everything you need to know in 2026.
- [Google Jules AI Agent Review 2026: Async GitHub Coding Agent Tested](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/google-jules-ai-agent-review-2026/) — Google Jules AI agent review 2026: async GitHub coding agent powered by Gemini 2.5 Pro, free beta, VM isolation, and how it stacks up against Devin and Cursor.
- [Best Ollama Models for Coding 2026: Ranked and Tested](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ollama-models-coding-2026/) — The best Ollama models for coding in 2026, ranked by benchmark scores, VRAM requirements, and real-world performance on consumer hardware.
- [Devstral 2 Review 2026: Mistral's Open-Source Coding Agent Hits 72.2% SWE-bench](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/devstral-2-review-2026/) — Devstral 2 achieves 72.2% on SWE-bench Verified at $0.40/M tokens — the most capable open-weight coding model in 2026. Full review with benchmarks.
- [Agno Framework Guide 2026: The Fastest Python AI Agent Library (Formerly Phidata)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agno-phidata-framework-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Agno (formerly Phidata): 5,000x faster than LangGraph, 100+ tools, multimodal support, and production deployment with AgentOS in 2026.
- [OpenCode AI Review 2026: Open-Source Terminal AI Agent Compared to Claude Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/opencode-ai-review-2026/) — OpenCode AI review 2026: 121K GitHub stars, MIT license, 75+ model providers. How it compares to Claude Code for real dev workflows.
- [Claude Code Context Management 2026: The 60% Rule and CLAUDE.md Power Tips](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-context-management-2026/) — Master claude code context management with the 60% rule, CLAUDE.md structure, and /compact command to boost productivity by 67%.
- [Tray.io Review 2026: Enterprise AI Workflow Automation Deep Dive](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/tray-io-review-2026/) — Tray.io (now Tray.ai) review 2026: pricing, Merlin AI, connectors, and how it compares to Workato and Zapier for enterprise teams.
- [Claude Opus 4.6 Review 2026: The New SWE-Bench Leader for Coding](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-4-6-opus-review-2026/) — Claude Opus 4.6 review: 80.8% SWE-bench, 83% ARC-AGI-2 reasoning leap, Agent Teams compiler demo, and whether it's worth the upgrade over 4.5.
- [Cursor Worktrees Guide 2026: Parallel Agents Without File Conflicts](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-worktrees-parallel-agents-2026/) — Learn how to run multiple Cursor AI agents in parallel using Git worktrees — no file conflicts, faster feature delivery, and smarter model comparison.
- [Cline AI Review 2026: Open-Source VS Code Coding Agent Tested](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cline-ai-review-2026/) — Honest Cline AI review 2026: BYOK model, 5M+ installs, real-world costs, and how it compares to Cursor, Claude Code, and Roo Code.
- [Make.com AI Automation Guide 2026: Scenarios, Agents, and Integrations](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/make-com-ai-automation-guide-2026/) — Complete Make.com AI automation guide for 2026: scenarios, pricing, templates, and how it compares to n8n for AI agent workflows.
- [Dify AI Platform Review 2026: Open-Source LLMOps for Building AI Apps](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/dify-platform-review-2026/) — Hands-on Dify review 2026: open-source LLMOps with visual workflow builder, RAG pipelines, and model-agnostic AI agent framework for teams and enterprises.
- [Flowise Review 2026: Open-Source No-Code LLM App Builder](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/flowise-review-2026/) — Honest Flowise review 2026: features, pricing, setup complexity, and who should use this open-source visual LLM app builder.
- [OpenAI Agents SDK Tutorial 2026: Build Multi-Agent Pipelines in Python](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-agents-sdk-tutorial-2026/) — Step-by-step guide to building production multi-agent pipelines with OpenAI Agents SDK 0.13.4 — handoffs, guardrails, tracing, and cost optimization.
- [LLM Function Calling and Tool Use Guide 2026: OpenAI, Anthropic, Google](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-function-calling-tool-use-guide-2026/) — Complete 2026 guide to LLM function calling across OpenAI, Anthropic, and Google Gemini—with code, security, and production patterns.
- [GPT-5 vs Claude Opus 4 vs Gemini 3: 2026 Coding Benchmark Comparison](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-vs-claude-opus-4-vs-gemini-3-coding-2026/) — GPT-5 vs Claude Opus 4 vs Gemini 3 for coding in 2026 — SWE-bench, Terminal-Bench, pricing, and workflow-by-workflow recommendations.
- [Gemini 2.5 Pro Coding Review 2026: 2M Context Window vs Claude and GPT-5](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemini-2-5-pro-coding-review-2026/) — Gemini 2.5 Pro coding review 2026: 1M context window, native thinking mode, $1.25/M pricing vs Claude Opus and GPT-5 head-to-head.
- [GitHub Copilot Coding Agent Guide 2026: Autonomous Background Task Agent](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-copilot-coding-agent-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to GitHub Copilot's autonomous coding agent: how it works, pricing, use cases, and when to use it vs interactive agents like Claude Code.
- [Cursor Composer 2 Guide 2026: Frontier Coding Model at $0.50/M Tokens](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-composer-2-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Cursor Composer 2: benchmarks, pricing, architecture, and how it compares to Claude Code, Copilot, and GPT-5.4.
- [Sourcegraph Cody Review 2026: AI Code Assistant for Large Codebases](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/sourcegraph-cody-review-2026/) — Sourcegraph Cody delivers full-repo context awareness, multi-LLM support, and enterprise-grade deployment at $9–19/user/month — best for large codebases.
- [Augment Code Review 2026: Enterprise AI Coding Agent with 500K-File Context](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/augment-code-review-2026/) — Augment Code 2026 review: SWE-bench Pro #1 at 51.8%, 400K+ file Context Engine, ISO 42001 certified. Is it worth $60–$200/mo for enterprise teams?
- [n8n AI Agent Nodes Guide 2026: Build Workflows That Think and Act](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/n8n-ai-agent-nodes-guide-2026/) — A hands-on guide to n8n AI Agent nodes in 2026: architecture, memory types, tool nodes, MCP patterns, and production deployment.
- [Cursor 3 Agents Window Guide: Glass Interface, Design Mode, and Worktrees Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-3-glass-agents-window-deep-dive-2026/) — A complete guide to Cursor 3 Glass — covering the Agents Window, Design Mode, and Worktrees for parallel agent-first development in 2026.
- [18 Best DevOps MCP Servers for 2026: K8s, CI/CD, and Monitoring](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/devops-mcp-servers-guide-2026/) — The 18 best DevOps MCP servers for 2026 — covering Kubernetes, CI/CD, monitoring, IaC, cloud, and security with setup tips and stack recommendations.
- [Best AI QA Testing Tools 2026: Agentic Test Automation Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-qa-testing-tools-comparison-2026/) — The 8 best AI QA testing tools in 2026 compared: Testsigma, QA Wolf, Mabl, Applitools, and more — ranked by real-world agentic capability.
- [Testsigma Review 2026: Agentic AI Testing Platform Deep Dive](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/testsigma-review-2026/) — Honest Testsigma review 2026: Atto AI agents, NLP test creation, pricing, and how it compares to BrowserStack and Katalon.
- [QA Wolf Review 2026: AI-Generated Playwright Tests at Scale](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qawolf-review-2026/) — Honest QA Wolf review 2026: pricing, AI Playwright test generation, pros/cons, and how it compares to Mabl, Testim, and BrowserStack.
- [Claude API 300K Output Tokens: Complete Guide to Long-Form Generation (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-api-max-tokens-300k-guide-2026/) — How to unlock Claude API 300K output tokens via the Message Batches API with the output-300k-2026-03-24 beta header — with Python code examples.
- [AI Coding ROI Enterprise 2026: Metrics, Case Studies and Benchmarks](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-enterprise-roi-guide-2026/) — Enterprise AI coding ROI benchmarks, case studies, and frameworks for 2026 — including DORA metrics and what separates top performers.
- [Gemini Flash-Lite Batch API: 50% Cost Savings for High-Volume Tasks (2026 Guide)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemini-3-1-flash-lite-batch-api-cost-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Gemini 3.1 Flash-Lite Batch API: 50% discount, JSONL implementation, real cost calculators, and 90%+ savings with prompt caching.
- [Claude Opus 4.7 Tokenizer Cost Trap: Up to 35% More Tokens Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-opus-4-7-tokenizer-cost-guide-2026/) — Claude Opus 4.7 tokenizer uses 1.20x–1.47x more tokens for code. Same price, higher cost. Here's who pays more and how to reduce it.
- [OpenAI Computer Use API Developer Guide 2026: Build Browser Automation Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-computer-use-api-guide-2026/) — A complete developer guide to OpenAI Computer Use API: setup, code walkthroughs, security sandboxing, and comparison with Claude computer use.
- [ChatGPT Workspace Agents (Codex-Powered): Team Guide 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/chatgpt-workspace-agents-guide-2026/) — Complete team guide to ChatGPT Workspace Agents powered by Codex — build, deploy, and govern autonomous agents in Slack and across your stack.
- [Augment Code vs Cursor vs GitHub Copilot: Enterprise AI Coding Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/augment-code-vs-cursor-vs-copilot-2026/) — Augment Code vs Cursor vs GitHub Copilot compared on architecture, pricing, benchmarks, and enterprise compliance for 2026 buyers.
- [Claude Code PR Review Guide 2026: Parallel Agent Code Review Setup](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-pr-review-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Claude Code PR review in 2026 — parallel agent setup, GitHub App configuration, pricing, and comparison with GitHub Copilot.
- [OpenAI Codex Cloud Agent Guide 2026: Autonomous GitHub PR Generation](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-cloud-agent-guide-2026/) — OpenAI Codex cloud agent in 2026 autonomously clones repos, writes code, runs tests, and opens PRs — a complete guide to async GitHub workflows.
- [CodeRabbit vs Qodo vs Greptile: Best AI Code Review Tool 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/coderabbit-vs-qodo-vs-greptile-2026/) — CodeRabbit, Qodo, and Greptile each excel in different scenarios — here's the data-driven breakdown to pick the right AI code review tool for your team in 2026.
- [LangGraph vs CrewAI vs Dapr: Production AI Agent Framework Comparison 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langgraph-crewai-dapr-comparison-2026/) — LangGraph, CrewAI, and Dapr compared head-to-head for production AI agents — durability, speed, cost, and decision framework for 2026.
- [GPT-5.5 Agentic Coding Guide: Terminal-Bench 2.0, Computer Use, Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-5-agentic-coding-guide-2026/) — Complete developer guide to GPT-5.5 agentic coding: Terminal-Bench 2.0 results, computer use setup, Responses API workflows, and benchmark comparisons.
- [Zed AI Editor Guide 2026: ACP Protocol, AI Features, and Performance](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/zed-ai-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Zed AI in 2026: ACP protocol, 0.12s startup, 120fps GPU rendering, AI features, pricing, and Cursor vs VS Code.
- [Greptile Review 2026: AI Code Review That Understands Your Entire Codebase](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/greptile-review-2026/) — Greptile leads AI code review benchmarks with 82% bug catch rate and 100% high-severity detection — but is it right for your team?
- [Qodo Review 2026: AI Code Quality Platform (Formerly CodiumAI)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qodo-review-2026/) — Qodo combines AI PR review with test generation. Full 2026 review with pricing and benchmarks.
- [CodeRabbit Review 2026: AI Code Review Tool with 2M+ Repositories](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/coderabbit-review-2026/) — CodeRabbit is the most-installed AI code review tool on GitHub, connecting 2M+ repos and processing 13M+ PRs — here's a complete 2026 review.
- [Peta AI Agent Credential Security: Scoped Credentials Without Raw API Key Exposure](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/peta-ai-agent-credential-guide-2026/) — How Peta gives AI agents scoped, policy-controlled credentials — eliminating raw API key exposure in MCP and agentic workflows.
- [1Password Unified Access for AI Agents: Developer Security Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/1password-unified-access-ai-agents-2026/) — How to use 1Password Unified Access to securely inject credentials into AI agents at runtime — no hardcoded secrets, full audit trail.
- [Claude Opus 4.7 budget_tokens Removal: Migration from Extended Thinking](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-opus-4-7-budget-tokens-breaking-change-2026/) — How to fix the 400 error from Claude Opus 4.7's budget_tokens removal and migrate to adaptive thinking in Python and TypeScript.
- [ProjectDiscovery Neo Review: Nuclei-Based AI Pentest Agent That Found 66 Exploitable Vulnerabilities](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/projectdiscovery-neo-pentest-guide-2026/) — ProjectDiscovery Neo is an AI pentest agent that confirmed 66 exploitable vulnerabilities in benchmarks — more than any other tool tested.
- [RunSybil AI Pentesting Review 2026: IAM and Container Security Testing Evaluated](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/runsybil-cloud-pentesting-review-2026/) — Hands-on review of RunSybil's AI-native pentesting platform: IAM misconfiguration testing, container escape, CI/CD secret exposure, and how it compares to Pentera and NodeZero.
- [Databricks Managed MCP Servers Guide: Developer Setup and Unity Catalog Integration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/databricks-mcp-managed-servers-guide-2026/) — Complete developer guide for Databricks managed MCP servers: setup, authentication, Genie/Vector Search/UC Functions integration, and Unity Catalog governance.
- [CAI Open-Source Security Agent Framework: Build and Deploy Offensive AI Security Agents](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cai-open-source-security-agent-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to CAI, the open-source cybersecurity AI framework that won 41/45 CTF flags and delivers 91% solve rates for automated pentesting.
- [Escape.tech AI API Security Review 2026: Business Logic and Complex Auth Testing](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/escape-tech-ai-api-security-review-2026/) — In-depth review of Escape.tech's AI-driven DAST for API security in 2026: business logic testing, OAuth/JWT auth, BOLA/IDOR detection, and CI/CD integration.
- [GPT-5.5 Batch API and Flex Mode: 50% Cost Savings for High-Volume AI Coding Tasks](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt-5-5-batch-flex-pricing-guide-2026/) — GPT-5.5 Batch and Flex mode cut your API bill by 50%. Learn which coding workflows qualify and how to implement batch jobs in Python.
- [OpenAI Hosted Shell and Apply Patch: GPT-5.5 Compute Tools for Autonomous Code Execution](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-hosted-shell-apply-patch-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to GPT-5.5's hosted shell and apply_patch tools for building autonomous coding agents via the OpenAI Responses API.
- [Continue.dev vs GitHub Copilot 2026: Open-Source Alternative That's Worth Switching To](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/continue-dev-vs-github-copilot-2026/) — Compare Continue.dev and GitHub Copilot: pricing, model flexibility, PR agents, and whether the open-source alternative is worth the switch.
- [How to Configure Every AI Coding Assistant 2026: CLAUDE.md, Cursor Rules, Copilot](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/configure-ai-coding-assistants-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to configuring CLAUDE.md, Cursor rules, Copilot instructions, AGENTS.md, and Windsurf in 2026—with comparison tables and best practices.
- [Windsurf vs Cursor Performance 2026: Speed, Latency, and Real Workflow Benchmarks](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-vs-cursor-performance-2026/) — Real benchmark data comparing Windsurf vs Cursor in 2026: inference speed, autocomplete accuracy, multi-file refactor latency, and total cost.
- [Bolt.new vs Replit vs v0 2026: Which Browser-Based AI Builder Wins?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/bolt-new-vs-replit-vs-v0-2026/) — Honest 2026 comparison of Bolt.new, Replit, and v0 — pricing, frameworks, code quality, and which AI builder fits your project.
- [Claude Code + GitHub Actions 2026: Automate PR Reviews and CI Tasks with AI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-github-actions-2026/) — Complete guide to integrating Claude Code with GitHub Actions in 2026: setup, auth options, workflow patterns, cost controls, and security guardrails.
- [How to Build an MCP Server with Python 2026: Step-by-Step Tutorial](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/build-mcp-server-python-2026/) — Build a production-ready MCP server in Python using FastMCP — from 9-line hello world to Docker, auth, and security hardening.
- [OpenAI Codex CLI Guide 2026: Terminal AI Coding with the Rust-Built Agent](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-cli-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to OpenAI Codex CLI 2026: install the Rust-built terminal agent, configure AGENTS.md, set approval modes, and integrate MCP tools.
- [LLM API Pricing Comparison 2026: GPT-5 vs Claude vs Gemini vs DeepSeek Costs](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-api-pricing-comparison-2026/) — Up-to-date LLM API pricing for GPT-5, Claude, Gemini, and DeepSeek in 2026 — with hidden costs, batch discounts, and a use-case decision guide.
- [Tabnine vs GitHub Copilot 2026: Enterprise AI Coding Assistant Showdown](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/tabnine-vs-github-copilot-2026/) — Tabnine vs GitHub Copilot 2026 compared on code quality, pricing, privacy, and enterprise features — with a decision framework for regulated industries.
- [Cursor + Claude Code Workflow 2026: Using Both Tools Together Effectively](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-claude-code-workflow-2026/) — How to combine Cursor and Claude Code in a hybrid workflow — setup methods, work division strategy, and real cost savings for developers in 2026.
- [Amazon Q Developer Review 2026: AWS's AI Coding Assistant for Enterprise Teams](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/amazon-q-developer-review-2026/) — Amazon Q Developer 2026: pricing, agentic coding, Java transformation, AWS integration, versus Cursor and Copilot.
- [Windsurf SWE-1 Model Guide 2026: Benchmarks, Speed, and What It Means for Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-swe1-model-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Windsurf SWE-1 models in 2026: benchmarks, SWE-Bench scores, pricing, and how it compares to Cursor, Copilot, and Claude Code.
- [Qwen3-Coder Review 2026: The Open-Source Model That Rivals GPT-5](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/qwen3-coder-review-2026/) — Qwen3-Coder 2026 review: benchmarks, pricing, local setup, and head-to-head vs Claude Opus 4.6 and GPT-5 — is it worth switching?
- [Claude Code Subagents Guide 2026: Parallel Agents for Faster Development](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-subagents-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Claude Code subagents: create custom agents, run parallel workflows, optimize costs with model routing, and ship faster.
- [Superpowers Framework: TDD Methodology for AI Coding Agents 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/superpowers-framework-ai-coding-2026/) — Superpowers is the open-source framework that enforces TDD discipline on AI coding agents—here's how to install it and why it works.
- [How to Build an AI Agent from Scratch 2026: Python + LangChain + Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/build-ai-agent-from-scratch-2026/) — Build a production-ready AI agent from scratch using Python, LangGraph, and custom tools — with memory, error handling, and deployment included.
- [Lovable Pricing 2026: Credits, Hidden Costs, and Whether the Free Plan Is Worth It](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/lovable-pricing-guide-2026/) — Complete breakdown of Lovable pricing in 2026: credit system explained, plan comparisons, hidden costs, and honest verdict on which plan fits your project.
- [Windsurf Arena Mode Deep Dive: Compare AI Models Side-by-Side in Your IDE](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-arena-mode-swe-1-5-review-2026/) — Windsurf Arena Mode lets you run two AI models simultaneously on the same prompt and vote for the winner — here's how to use it effectively.
- [AI Code Review Tools Comparison 2026: Which Tool Catches the Most Bugs in Your PRs?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-code-review-tools-comparison-2026/) — Greptile catches 82% of bugs vs CodeRabbit's 44% — but noise ratio and pricing change the real-world picture. Here's the honest 2026 comparison.
- [AI App Builder Guide 2026: How to Ship an MVP in a Weekend with Vibe Coding Tools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-app-builder-mvp-guide-2026/) — The definitive 2026 guide to AI app builders — Lovable, Bolt, Replit, v0 compared with a step-by-step weekend MVP playbook.
- [OpenAgents Framework Guide: Build Persistent AI Agent Networks with MCP and A2A Support](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openagents-framework-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to OpenAgents framework — build persistent AI agent networks with native MCP and A2A protocol support in 2026.
- [CrewAI A2A Protocol Tutorial: Build Interoperable Agents with Agent2Agent Support](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/crewai-a2a-protocol-tutorial-2026/) — Step-by-step tutorial on using the A2A protocol with CrewAI to build cross-framework multi-agent systems in 2026.
- [Google ADK TypeScript Guide: Build AI Agents with the Official TypeScript SDK](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/google-adk-typescript-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to building AI agents with Google ADK TypeScript — installation, tools, multi-agent orchestration, and production deployment.
- [Claude Code GitHub Workflow 2026: PR Reviews, Commits, and CI Integration](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-github-workflow-2026/) — Complete guide to Claude Code GitHub workflow: automated PR reviews, CI failure auto-fix, and enterprise CI/CD integration using claude-code-action@v1.
- [Replit Agent Review 2026: Build Full Apps from Plain English Prompts](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/replit-agent-review-2026/) — Honest Replit Agent V2 review after building real apps: pricing, benchmarks, autonomous debugging, and how it compares to Cursor, Bolt, and Lovable.
- [Aider + Ollama Local Coding Setup 2026: Free AI Pair Programming Offline](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/aider-ollama-local-coding-2026/) — Complete setup guide for Aider + Ollama local AI pair programming — zero API costs, full privacy, works offline in 2026.
- [AI Coding Tools Pricing Comparison 2026: Free vs Paid Plans Broken Down](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-tools-pricing-2026/) — Complete breakdown of AI coding tool pricing in 2026: free tiers, $20/month plans, power tiers, hidden costs, and budget-optimized stacks.
- [CLAUDE.md Setup Guide 2026: The Config File That Makes Claude Code Actually Useful](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-md-setup-guide-2026/) — Complete CLAUDE.md setup guide for 2026: structure, examples, hierarchy, hooks, and best practices to maximize Claude Code in any project.
- [Windsurf Memories Feature Guide 2026: How to Make Cascade Remember Your Codebase](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-memories-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Windsurf Memories, Rules, and AGENTS.md — make Cascade remember your codebase conventions, preferences, and architecture permanently.
- [Best MCP Servers for Developers 2026: 15 Tools Worth Installing](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-mcp-servers-developers-2026/) — The 15 best MCP servers for developers in 2026, ranked by production-readiness, security, and real-world impact on dev workflows.
- [How to Set Up Cursor AI in 2026: Complete Beginner's Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-ai-setup-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step Cursor AI setup guide for 2026: install, configure models, master Tab Completion, Composer 2.0, Agent Mode, and .cursorrules in under an hour.
- [DeepSeek V3.2 vs Claude Sonnet 4.6 vs GPT-5 2026: Same Quality, 90% Cheaper](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/deepseek-v3-2-vs-claude-vs-gpt5-cost-2026/) — DeepSeek V3.2 costs 90% less than GPT-5 and Claude Sonnet 4.6. Real benchmarks, dollar scenarios, privacy risks, and when to use each model.
- [LLM Context Window Comparison 2026: GPT-4o vs Claude vs Gemini](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-context-window-comparison-2026/) — GPT-4.1, Claude Opus 4.6, and Gemini 2.5 Pro compared on context window size, effective performance, pricing cliffs, and real-world use cases.
- [vLLM vs Ollama vs LM Studio 2026: Which Local LLM Serving Stack Actually Scales?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vllm-vs-ollama-vs-lm-studio-2026/) — vLLM, Ollama, and LM Studio compared on throughput, hardware requirements, and production readiness for 2026 developers.
- [Vercel AI SDK Guide 2026: Build Streaming AI Apps in TypeScript With One SDK](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vercel-ai-sdk-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Vercel AI SDK in 2026 — streaming, tool calling, structured output, agents, and production deployment with code examples.
- [Best Free AI Coding Tools 2026: Get 80% of Cursor at Zero Cost](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-free-ai-coding-tools-2026/) — The best free AI coding tools in 2026 compared honestly — including free tiers, open-source options, and practical $0 setups that rival paid tools.
- [Pydantic AI Tutorial 2026: Type-Safe Python Agents With Automatic Validation and Self-Correction](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/pydantic-ai-tutorial-2026/) — Build production-ready AI agents with Pydantic AI — type-safe structured outputs, tool calling, dependency injection, and automatic validation retries.
- [Mastra AI Guide 2026: Build TypeScript AI Agents with the Framework That Hit 300K Weekly Downloads](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mastra-ai-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to Mastra AI TypeScript framework: install, build agents, add memory, create workflows, and deploy to production.
- [Devin AI vs Claude Code vs SWE-agent: Autonomous Coding Agents Compared (2026)](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/devin-vs-claude-code-vs-swe-agent-2026/) — Devin AI, Claude Code, and SWE-agent take three radically different approaches to autonomous coding. Here's how to choose the right one.
- [OpenAI Codex vs GitHub Copilot 2026: Which Is Better for Developers?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-codex-vs-github-copilot-2026/) — OpenAI Codex vs GitHub Copilot 2026 compared on accuracy, speed, pricing, and workflow — find out which AI coding tool fits your stack.
- [Antigravity IDE Review 2026: The Dark Horse AI Code Editor Worth Watching](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/antigravity-ide-review-2026/) — Honest Antigravity IDE review 2026: agent-first architecture, multi-model support, pricing controversy, and whether the $20/mo AI Pro plan is worth it.
- [Kiro AI IDE Review 2026: AWS's New Coding Agent Tested in Real Projects](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/kiro-ai-ide-review-2026/) — Deep review of Kiro, AWS's spec-driven AI IDE. Specs, Hooks, Steering Files vs Cursor and Claude Code. Pricing, safety, enterprise use cases.
- [Cursor Background Agents Guide 2026: Run Autonomous Coding Tasks in the Background](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-background-agents-2026/) — Complete guide to Cursor background agents in 2026: setup, pricing, Computer Use, best practices, and when to use them vs Claude Code or Codex.
- [vLLM vs Ollama for Production LLM Serving in 2026: The Honest Comparison](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vllm-vs-ollama-production-2026/) — Direct comparison of vLLM and Ollama for production LLM serving — throughput benchmarks, cost analysis, migration paths, and when to use each tool.
- [AI Coding Tools for Beginners 2026: The No-Hype Guide to Getting Started](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-tools-beginners-guide-2026/) — Honest guide to the best AI coding tools for beginners in 2026—what they actually do, which are free, and how to start without the hype.
- [GitHub Copilot Agent Mode Guide 2026: Multi-File Edits and Autonomous Tasks](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-copilot-agent-mode-2026/) — Complete guide to GitHub Copilot Agent Mode 2026 — setup, multi-file edits, coding agent, MCP integration, and cost optimization.
- [Claude Code Plan Mode Guide 2026: How to Use Plan Before You Code](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-plan-mode-guide-2026/) — Master Claude Code Plan Mode: activation, workflows, team adoption, and best practices to prevent AI coding mistakes. 2026 guide
- [LLM Prompt Caching Guide 2026: Cut API Costs 70% with Anthropic and OpenAI](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-prompt-caching-guide-2026/) — LLM prompt caching guide 2026: Anthropic, OpenAI, Gemini code examples, cost calculators, anti-patterns, and production monitoring tips.
- [GitHub Copilot Workspace Review 2026: Agent-Mode Coding in the Browser](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-copilot-workspace-review-2026/) — A hands-on GitHub Copilot Workspace review 2026 covering the Coding Agent, Agent Mode, pricing, performance stats, and how it compares to Cursor.
- [OpenAI Responses API Tutorial 2026: Build Stateful AI Apps in Python](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/openai-responses-api-tutorial-2026/) — Complete OpenAI Responses API tutorial 2026: stateful conversations, built-in tools, function calling, and migration from Chat Completions.
- [DeepSeek V3 Cost Comparison vs GPT-5 in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/deepseek-v3-cost-comparison-2026/) — DeepSeek V3.2 vs GPT-5.4 cost comparison with pricing, benchmarks, and recommendations for developer workflows.
- [Mastra AI: The TypeScript AI Agent Framework for 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mastra-ai-typescript-framework-2026/) — A practical guide to Mastra AI, the TypeScript-first framework for building production AI agents. Covers setup, agents, tools, MCP, workflows, RAG, evals
- [Pipedream vs n8n 2026: Which Developer Automation Platform Wins?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/pipedream-vs-n8n-2026/) — Pipedream vs n8n 2026 compared across pricing, AI agents, self-hosting, and team fit — with a clear verdict for developers and ops teams.
- [n8n AI Workflow Tutorial 2026: Build Your First AI-Powered Automation](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/n8n-ai-workflow-tutorial-2026/) — Step-by-step n8n AI workflow tutorial for 2026 — from setup to a production AI agent with tools, memory, and RAG in under 2 hours.
- [Claude Opus 4.6 vs GPT-5 for Coding 2026: Real Developer Benchmarks](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-opus-4-vs-gpt-5-coding-2026/) — Claude Opus 4.6 leads SWE-bench Pro at 74% vs GPT-5.4's 57.7%, but GPT-5 is 6x cheaper. Here's the real data developers need in 2026.
- [Best LLM for Coding 2026: Claude Opus vs GPT-5 vs Gemini 3 Benchmarked](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-llm-for-coding-2026/) — Comprehensive 2026 benchmark of top coding LLMs — Claude Opus 4.6, GPT-5.4, Gemini 3.1 Pro, and open-source models ranked by real-world performance.
- [Gemini 3.1 Pro Review 2026: Developer Benchmark and Coding Performance](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemini-3-1-pro-review-2026/) — Gemini 3.1 Pro claims #1 on AI benchmarks with 77.1% ARC-AGI-2 — but 29s latency and enterprise gaps make it a nuanced choice for developers.
- [Continue.dev Review 2026: Open-Source GitHub Copilot Alternative](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/continue-dev-review-2026/) — Comprehensive Continue.dev review 2026 — CLI-first Continuous AI agents, local LLM support, and how it compares to Copilot and Cursor.
- [LangGraph Tutorial 2026: Build Stateful AI Agents with Graphs](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langgraph-tutorial-2026/) — Step-by-step LangGraph tutorial 2026: install, define state, build graph nodes, add memory, deploy production agents.
- [Microsoft Agent Framework 2026: AutoGen Successor Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/microsoft-agent-framework-2026/) — Microsoft Agent Framework replaces AutoGen in 2026 with native Responses API, MCP server integration, and enterprise workflow orchestration patterns.
- [AG2 (AutoGen v0.4) Guide: Event-Driven Multi-Agent Framework for Python Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ag2-autogen-v0-4-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to AG2 (AutoGen v0.4): architecture, ConversableAgent, GroupChat, async messaging, and production best practices for Python developers.
- [CrewAI Tutorial 2026: Build Multi-Agent Systems in Python Step by Step](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/crewai-tutorial-2026/) — Complete CrewAI tutorial for 2026: install, configure agents, add tools, implement memory, and deploy multi-agent Python systems to production.
- [Aider AI Review 2026: The Terminal Coding Assistant That Actually Works](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/aider-ai-review-2026/) — Aider AI review 2026: open-source terminal coding assistant with 40K+ GitHub stars, 75+ model providers, git-native commits, and voice coding mode.
- [AI Risk Management &amp; Fraud Detection Tools 2026: Best Tools for Financial Institutions](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-risk-management-fraud-detection-tools-2026/) — The best AI fraud detection and risk management tools for banks and financial institutions in 2026—Feedzai, Palantir, Unit21, IBM, and more compared.
- [Zapier AI Features Guide 2026: Tables, Chatbots, and AI Actions Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/zapier-ai-features-guide-2026/) — Complete Zapier AI guide 2026: AI Actions, Agents, Chatbots, Tables, MCP, pricing, accuracy benchmarks, and cost traps.
- [Google Antigravity vs Cursor vs Claude Code 2026: Agent-First IDE Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/antigravity-vs-cursor-vs-claude-code-2026/) — Google Antigravity vs Cursor vs Claude Code 2026 — full comparison of pricing, benchmarks, MCP support, and which AI IDE wins for your workflow.
- [AI Coding Tools for Teams 2026: Which Tools Scale Beyond Solo Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-coding-tools-for-teams-2026/) — A developer's guide to AI coding tools that actually scale for engineering teams in 2026 — covering governance, security, and real productivity benchmarks.
- [Cursor Rules Guide 2026: How to Write .cursorrules and .mdc Files for Your Project](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-rules-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to writing Cursor rules in 2026: .cursorrules vs .mdc format, four activation modes, ready-to-use templates, and token budget tips.
- [MCP Gateway Tools Comparison 2026: Top 10 Tools for Enterprise AI Agent Workflows](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-gateway-tools-comparison-2026/) — Compare the top 10 MCP gateway tools for enterprise AI in 2026 — covering Bifrost, Composio, TrueFoundry, Kong, Cloudflare, and more.
- [Gemini CLI vs Codex CLI 2026: Google's Free Tier vs OpenAI's Rust-Built Agent](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemini-cli-vs-codex-cli-2026/) — Gemini CLI vs Codex CLI 2026: free tier limits, Rust-powered speed, 1M token context, Terminal-Bench scores, and pricing compared.
- [JetBrains AI vs GitHub Copilot vs Cursor 2026: Best AI IDE for Java and Kotlin Devs](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/jetbrains-ai-vs-github-copilot-vs-cursor-2026/) — JetBrains AI, GitHub Copilot, and Cursor compared for Java and Kotlin developers in 2026 — pricing, benchmarks, and which to pick.
- [LLM Coding Workflow Guide 2026: How Top Developers Structure AI-Assisted Development](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/llm-coding-workflow-guide-2026/) — A 5-phase framework for structured AI-assisted coding in 2026: spec-driven planning, context packing, iterative implementation, quality gates, and tooling.
- [Claude Code Hooks Guide 2026: Automate Your Workflow with Shell Triggers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-hooks-guide-2026/) — Complete Claude Code hooks guide: configure shell triggers for auto-formatting, security gates, and CI/CD integration with all 18 hook events.
- [How to Use Claude API in Python 2026: Complete Developer Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-api-python-guide-2026/) — Step-by-step Claude API Python tutorial: install the SDK, send messages, use streaming, tool use, and prompt caching with real code examples.
- [Agentic Coding Patterns 2026: 8 Workflows That Ship Code 10x Faster](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agentic-coding-patterns-2026/) — 8 agentic coding patterns senior developers use to ship code 10x faster with AI agents: spec-first, iterative loops, quality gates, and more.
- [Cursor 3 Guide 2026: Agents Window, Parallel Agents, and Design Mode](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-3-guide-2026/) — Cursor 3 guide: Agents Window, parallel agents, Design Mode, Composer 2 model, and cloud agents for shipping code faster in 2026.
- [n8n vs Zapier vs Make: Best AI Workflow Automation in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/n8n-vs-zapier-vs-make-automation-2026/) — n8n, Zapier, and Make.com compared for AI workflow automation in 2026 — pricing, AI features, developer experience, and when to use each.
- [Claude Code Best Practices 2026: 15 Habits of Developers Who Ship Faster](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-best-practices-2026/) — 15 proven Claude Code best practices in 2026 that senior developers use to cut coding time by 40% — from CLAUDE.md setup to MCP server integration.
- [AGENTS.md Guide 2026: How to Write AI Agent Instructions for Every Tool](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agents-md-guide-2026/) — AGENTS.md is the open standard for AI agent instructions that cuts agent runtime 28.6% and works across Cursor, Claude Code, Windsurf, and 20+ tools.
- [How to Set Up Windsurf IDE 2026: Installation, Config, and First Project](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/windsurf-setup-tutorial-2026/) — Complete guide to setup Windsurf IDE 2026 — install on macOS, Windows, or Linux, configure .windsurfrules, and run your first Cascade flow.
- [MCP vs A2A Protocol 2026: Understanding the Two Standards for AI Agent Communication](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-vs-a2a-protocol-2026/) — MCP connects agents to tools; A2A connects agents to agents. Here's how both protocols work, when to use each, and why production systems need both.
- [.cursorrules vs CLAUDE.md vs AGENTS.md 2026: Which AI Config File Should You Use?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursorrules-vs-claude-md-vs-agents-md-2026/) — Compare AI coding config formats: .cursorrules, CLAUDE.md, AGENTS.md, .cursor/rules. Which format best fits your team in 2026?
- [AI for Backend Developers 2026: Tools, APIs, and Patterns That Actually Work](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-for-backend-developers-2026/) — The complete backend developer's guide to AI tools, patterns, and APIs in 2026 — what's actually worth using in production.
- [Best AI Documentation Generator Tools 2026: Auto-Generate Docs From Code That Actually Make Sense](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-documentation-generator-tools-2026/) — The top AI documentation generator tools of 2026 tested and ranked — which ones produce docs developers actually want to read.
- [LangSmith vs Langfuse vs Helicone 2026: Best LLM Observability Tool for Production AI Apps](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langsmith-langfuse-helicone-comparison-2026/) — LangSmith vs Langfuse vs Helicone compared for 2026: pricing, features, tracing depth, and best LLM observability tool.
- [GitHub Copilot Enterprise Guide 2026: Features, Setup, and ROI for Engineering Teams](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/github-copilot-enterprise-guide-2026/) — Complete guide to GitHub Copilot Enterprise in 2026: features, setup steps, ROI analysis, and security for engineering teams of all sizes.
- [GPT-4o vs Claude 3.5 Sonnet vs Gemini 1.5 Pro: Developer Benchmark 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gpt4o-vs-claude-vs-gemini-developer-2026/) — Real benchmark data comparing GPT-4o, Claude 3.5 Sonnet, and Gemini 1.5 Pro on coding, speed, cost, and developer experience in 2026.
- [Claude Code Tutorial 2026: Complete Setup and Workflow Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-tutorial-2026/) — Claude Code 2026 tutorial: installation, setup, memory, skills, hooks, MCP servers, and agentic workflows for autonomous AI coding.
- [Activepieces Review 2026: The Open-Source Zapier That's Actually Free](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/activepieces-review-2026/) — Activepieces 2026 review: MIT-licensed, self-hostable workflow automation with unlimited free tasks. See how it stacks up against Zapier, Make, and n8n.
- [MCP Server Tutorial 2026: Build Your First Model Context Protocol Server](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-server-tutorial-2026/) — Step-by-step MCP server tutorial: build, test, and deploy your first Model Context Protocol server using Python FastMCP or TypeScript in 2026.
- [Gemini CLI Guide 2026: How to Use Google Gemini from the Terminal](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/gemini-cli-guide-2026/) — Complete Gemini CLI guide 2026: install, authenticate, and use Google Gemini in your terminal with 1M token context and a generous free tier.
- [Best AI Agent Memory Frameworks in 2026: Mem0 vs Zep vs Letta Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-agent-memory-frameworks-2026/) — Compare Mem0, Zep, and Letta — the top AI agent memory frameworks in 2026 — with benchmarks, architecture breakdowns, and a decision framework.
- [Cursor vs VS Code Copilot 2026: Which AI IDE Wins for Developers?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-vs-vscode-copilot-2026/) — Cursor vs VS Code Copilot compared on features, pricing, privacy, and performance — find out which AI IDE is right for you in 2026.
- [LangChain vs LlamaIndex 2026: Which RAG Framework Should You Choose?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/langchain-vs-llamaindex-2026/) — LangChain vs LlamaIndex 2026 compared across RAG quality, agent workflows, performance, and enterprise readiness — with a clear decision guide.
- [Vector Database Comparison 2026: Pinecone vs Weaviate vs Chroma vs pgvector](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vector-database-comparison-2026/) — Pinecone, Weaviate, Chroma, and pgvector compared on performance, pricing, and use cases for production RAG systems in 2026.
- [Advanced Prompt Engineering Techniques Every Developer Should Know in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/prompt-engineering-techniques-2026/) — Advanced prompt engineering 2026: Chain-of-Symbol to DSPy 3.0 compilation, with strategies for Claude 4.6, GPT-5.4, and Gemini 2.5.
- [Fine-Tuning vs RAG vs Prompt Engineering: When to Use Which in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/fine-tuning-vs-rag-vs-prompt-engineering-2026/) — A practical decision framework for choosing between fine-tuning, RAG, and prompt engineering to customize LLMs in 2026.
- [Vibe Coding Explained: The Complete Developer Guide for 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/vibe-coding-guide-2026/) — The complete vibe coding guide for 2026: tools, workflows, prompts, and best practices for developers and non-technical builders.
- [Claude Code vs GitHub Copilot 2026: Terminal Agent vs IDE Assistant](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/claude-code-vs-github-copilot-2026/) — Claude Code vs GitHub Copilot 2026: terminal agent vs IDE assistant. Real comparisons, pricing, and which to use.
- [Cursor vs Windsurf vs Zed: Best AI IDE in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/cursor-vs-windsurf-vs-zed-ai-ide-2026/) — Cursor, Windsurf, and Zed compared on AI features, pricing, performance, and Claude Code integration to find the best AI IDE in 2026.
- [AI Sales Forecasting Tools 2026: Best Predictive Analytics Platforms Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-sales-forecasting-tools-2026/) — AI sales forecasting tools for 2026 compared: Clari, Salesforce Einstein, Gong, and more. Find the best for your team.
- [AI Customer Success Tools 2026: Best Platforms for Retention and Upsell](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-customer-success-tools-2026/) — Top AI customer success tools in 2026 ranked by retention impact, cost, and team fit—with real stats and platform comparisons.
- [AI for Project Management in 2026: Best Tools for Agile and Remote Teams](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-project-management-tools-2026/) — Best AI project management tools for 2026: ClickUp, Wrike, Airtable, Jira &amp; Notion. Compare features, pricing &amp; AI capabilities for agile teams.
- [AI Lead Generation Tools 2026: Best Software for B2B Sales Prospecting](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-lead-generation-tools-2026/) — Top AI lead generation tools for 2026 ranked by accuracy, intent data, and ROI — with stacks for every B2B team size.
- [AI Affiliate Marketing Tools 2026: Best Tools for Link Building and Commission Optimization](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-affiliate-marketing-tools-2026/) — The top AI affiliate marketing tools in 2026 for content creation, SEO, link building, and commission optimization—ranked by ROI and ease of use.
- [Best AI Content Writing Tools 2026: Jasper vs Copy.ai vs Writesonic](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-content-writing-tools-2026/) — Jasper leads for long-form quality, Copy.ai dominates workflow automation, and Writesonic wins on budget. Here's the complete 2026 comparison.
- [AI Code Documentation Tools in 2026: Best Auto-Doc Generators for Developers](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-code-documentation-tools-2026/) — The best AI code documentation tools in 2026 are GitHub Copilot, Cursor Pro, and Mintlify — ranked by accuracy, IDE integration, and team fit.
- [Best AI SEO Tools in 2026: Surfer SEO vs MarketMuse vs Clearscope](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-seo-tools-2026/) — Surfer SEO wins for fast on-page optimization, Clearscope for editorial teams, and MarketMuse for content strategy. See the full comparison inside.
- [AI RPA Physical Automation 2026: The Complete Developer Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-rpa-physical-automation-2026/) — AI RPA in 2026: combine agents for cognition with RPA for execution, delivering 2–3× ROI over 3 years versus standalone bots.
- [AI UI UX Design Prototyping Tools 2026: Best Options Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-ui-ux-design-prototyping-tools-2026/) — The best AI UI UX design prototyping tools in 2026—ranked by feature, price, and workflow fit for teams that want to ship faster.
- [AI for Customer Support and Helpdesk Automation in 2026: The Complete Developer Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-customer-support-helpdesk-automation-2026/) — AI helpdesk automation cuts support costs, scales instantly, and improves CSAT. Here's how to implement and measure ROI.
- [AI for HR and Talent Acquisition in 2026: Best Tools for Recruitment](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-hr-talent-acquisition-recruitment-2026/) — Discover the best AI HR and talent acquisition tools in 2026. Compare top platforms, features, pricing, and ROI to transform your recruitment process.
- [AI Legal Document Review and Contract Analysis in 2026: Complete Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-legal-document-review-contract-analysis-2026/) — AI legal document review in 2026 cuts manual contract review time by up to 80%, with the market growing to $5.59B—here are the best tools and workflows.
- [Local AI Model Serving Frameworks 2026: vLLM vs TGI vs Ray Serve Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/local-ai-model-serving-frameworks-2026/) — vLLM leads high-concurrency APIs, SGLang excels in multi-turn chat, Ray Serve adds enterprise orchestration, and TGI is in maintenance mode as of 2026.
- [Best AI Meeting Assistants 2026: Otter.ai vs Fireflies.ai vs Fathom Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-meeting-assistants-2026/) — The best AI meeting assistants in 2026 are Fathom (best free), Fireflies.ai (best for teams), and Otter.ai (best real-time transcription).
- [Build an AI Test Generator with GPT-5 in 2026: Step-by-Step Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/build-ai-test-generator-gpt5-2026/) — Learn how to build an AI test generator using GPT-5 in 2026. Step-by-step tutorial covering setup, agent config, and CI/CD integration.
- [AI Cloud Cost Optimization Tools 2026: ProsperOps vs CAST AI vs Kubecost Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-cloud-cost-optimization-tools-2026/) — ProsperOps automates AWS commitments, CAST AI rightsizes Kubernetes, and Kubecost provides container visibility—each excels for different teams in 2026.
- [Best AI Test Generation Tools 2026: Diffblue vs CodiumAI vs Testim Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-test-generation-tools-2026/) — Top AI test generation tools in 2026: Diffblue Cover (Java unit tests), Qodo/CodiumAI (IDE-native generation), and Testim (AI-powered E2E automation).
- [Best AI Code Review Tools in 2026: DeepCode vs SonarQube AI vs CodeRabbit](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-code-review-tools-2026/) — The best AI code review tools in 2026 are DeepSource, CodeRabbit, and GitHub Copilot — ranked by benchmark accuracy, signal quality, and enterprise fit.
- [AI for DevOps and MLOps in 2026: Best Tools for CI/CD and Monitoring](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-for-devops-mlops-2026/) — The best AI tools for DevOps and MLOps in 2026: GitHub Copilot, Datadog, MLflow, and more — ranked for CI/CD, monitoring, and model deployment.
- [Best AI Tools for Social Media Management in 2026: Lately vs Jasper vs Buffer](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-tools-for-social-media-management-2026/) — The best AI tools for social media management in 2026 are Buffer (most accessible), Jasper AI (best brand voice), and Lately (best content repurposing).
- [Best AI Tools for E-commerce Personalization in 2026: Dynamic Yield vs Klevu vs Nosto](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-tools-for-ecommerce-personalization-2026/) — Dynamic Yield leads for enterprises, Nosto excels with agentic AI, and Klevu (Athos Commerce) dominates AI search—here's the 2026 comparison.
- [Best AI Tools for Data Science in 2026: The Complete Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-tools-for-data-science-2026/) — Best AI tools for data science in 2026: TensorFlow, PyTorch, OpenAI API, LangChain, and Vertex AI — how to pick the right stack.
- [AI vs Traditional Automation: Which Is Better for Business Workflows in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-vs-traditional-automation-business-workflows-2026/) — AI automation adapts and learns; traditional automation is fast and cheap for fixed tasks. In 2026, the best enterprises use both strategically.
- [How to Build an AI-Powered Chatbot with GPT-5 and RAG in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-powered-chatbot-gpt5-rag-2026/) — Build an AI chatbot with GPT-5 and RAG in 2026: vector databases, LangChain integration, and deployment with step-by-step code.
- [AI in Gaming 2026: Procedural Content Generation and NPC Intelligence Explained](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-in-gaming-2026/) — AI in gaming 2026 is a $4.54B market reshaping how games are built and played, from infinite procedural worlds to NPCs that remember you.
- [AI in Finance 2026: Algorithmic Trading, Fraud Detection, and the Future of Money](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-in-finance-2026/) — AI in finance 2026 powers 70-80% of US equity trading, cuts fraud losses in real-time, and reshapes credit scoring—here's what you need to know.
- [AI in Healthcare 2026: How Machine Learning Is Changing Diagnosis and Treatment](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-in-healthcare-2026/) — AI in healthcare 2026 shifts from static algorithms to intelligent agents, transforming diagnosis, treatment, and clinical operations.
- [Best AI Note-Taking Apps in 2026: Notion AI vs Mem vs Obsidian vs Reflect](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-note-taking-apps-2026/) — Best AI note-taking apps 2026: Notion AI for teams, Mem for zero-friction, Obsidian for power users, Reflect for privacy. Find your fit.
- [Perplexity vs ChatGPT vs Google: The AI Search Engine Battle of 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/perplexity-vs-chatgpt-vs-google-ai-search-2026/) — Perplexity wins on accuracy (92%), Google wins on reach, ChatGPT wins on versatility. In 2026, the best strategy is using all three for different tasks.
- [AI in Education 2026: How Personalized Learning and AI Tutors Are Reshaping Schools](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-in-education-2026/) — AI in education 2026: personalized learning, AI tutors, and adaptive classrooms — but human teachers still lead on critical thinking and emotional support.
- [AI Hardware 2026: NVIDIA H200 vs AMD MI300X vs Google TPU v5 Compared](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-hardware-2026/) — AI hardware 2026 compared: NVIDIA H200, AMD MI300X, and Google TPU v5 across performance, price, memory bandwidth, and total cost of ownership.
- [Generative AI for Marketing 2026: Best Tools for Content Creation and Campaigns](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/generative-ai-for-marketing-2026/) — Generative AI for marketing 2026 is used by 93% of companies to cut costs, boost conversions 30-50%, and run hyper-personalized campaigns at scale.
- [Multimodal AI 2026: GPT-5 vs Gemini 2.5 Flash vs Claude 4 — The Complete Comparison Guide](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/multimodal-ai-2026/) — Compare GPT-5, Gemini 2.5 Flash, Claude 4 &amp; Qwen3 VL. Best multimodal AI 2026 for text, image, audio, video processing. Pricing, features guide.
- [AI in Cybersecurity 2026: How Machine Learning Is Transforming Threat Detection and Defense](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ai-in-cybersecurity-2026/) — AI in cybersecurity 2026 is a $35-44B market where autonomous AI defends against AI-powered attacks, cutting threat detection by 65%.
- [Best AI Voice Cloning Tools in 2026: ElevenLabs vs Resemble vs Play.ht](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-voice-cloning-tools-2026/) — The best AI voice cloning tools in 2026 are ElevenLabs for quality, VoiceClone AI for value, and Resemble AI for enterprise — most creators need just one.
- [Best AI Workflow Automation Tools in 2026: Zapier vs n8n vs Make](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-workflow-automation-tools-2026/) — The best AI workflow automation tools in 2026 are Zapier for ease, n8n for developer control, and Make for visual cost-efficiency.
- [MCP vs RAG vs AI Agents: How They Work Together in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/mcp-vs-rag-vs-ai-agents-2026/) — MCP, RAG, and AI agents solve different problems. MCP connects tools, RAG retrieves knowledge, and agents orchestrate actions. See how they work together.
- [Best AI Video Generators in 2026: Veo 3 vs Runway vs Kling After Sora](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-video-generators-2026/) — Best AI video generators 2026: Veo 3.1 for quality, Runway Gen-4 for professionals, Kling 3.0 for value.
- [Agentic AI Explained: Why Autonomous AI Agents Are the Biggest Trend of 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/agentic-ai-explained-2026/) — Agentic AI in 2026: what autonomous agents are, how they work, and where they're deployed—customer service, fraud detection, supply chains.
- [How to Run AI Models Locally: Ollama vs LM Studio in 2026](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/ollama-vs-lm-studio-local-ai-2026/) — Ollama vs LM Studio 2026: Ollama for developers (52M monthly downloads), LM Studio for GUI. Both free—most power users run both.
- [ChatGPT vs Claude vs Gemini: Which AI Is Best for Writing in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/chatgpt-vs-claude-vs-gemini-writing-2026/) — Claude writes best prose, ChatGPT is most versatile, Gemini strongest for research—smart writers use all three.
- [Best AI Image Generators in 2026: Midjourney vs Flux vs DALL-E](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-image-generators-2026/) — Best AI image generators 2026: Midjourney for art, Flux for photorealism, GPT Image 1.5 for comprehension.
- [Best AI Agent Frameworks in 2026: LangGraph vs CrewAI vs AutoGen](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-agent-frameworks-2026/) — Best AI agent frameworks 2026: LangGraph for production, CrewAI for prototyping, AutoGen for conversational agents.
- [Blog Topics for SEO: What Should You Write About in 2026?](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/blog-topics-for-seo-2026/) — The best blog topics for SEO match search intent, business goals, and low-competition long-tail keywords your audience already searches.
- [Best AI Coding Assistants in 2026: The Definitive Comparison](https://baeseokjae.github.io/posts/best-ai-coding-assistants-2026/) — The best AI coding assistants in 2026 are Cursor, Claude Code, and GitHub Copilot — but the smartest developers combine two or more into a unified stack.
## Key Pages
- [About](https://baeseokjae.github.io/about/)
- [Contact](https://baeseokjae.github.io/contact/)
- [Privacy Policy](https://baeseokjae.github.io/privacy/)
- [RSS Feed](https://baeseokjae.github.io/index.xml)
## Citation Guidelines
Content on RockB may be cited by AI systems. All factual claims include source attributions. Statistics are sourced from primary research, industry reports (Gartner, IDC, McKinsey), and vendor disclosures. If citing RockB content, please attribute to "RockB (baeseokjae.github.io)".